<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>D:/Exavault/My Modding Projects/Darkest Dungeon Modding/Enigma Class Mod/data/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>Exaelus&apos; Enigma Class Mod</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>public</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>0</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>0</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>0</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>Character Mod</Tags>
		<Tags>Class Mod</Tags>
		<Tags>New Class</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>[h1]The Enigma Class Mod[/h1]
Supports Color of Madness: Yes
Supports Crimson Court: Yes
Mod Version: 2.5d
Language: English, French, Polish, S-Chinese, Korean


[h1]Latest News[/h1]

Enigma can now find shards after battles and by investigating curios.
This has been uploaded as a new mod because it requires CoM DLC.
if you own it (CoM), click on the banner below to subscribe:

[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1676306512][img]https://i.imgur.com/jFy3PaR.png[/img][/url]


[h1]Class Introduction[/h1]
Well another 3 weeks of work and i have made yet another unique class. 
Screenshots are all just for visual effect display nothing more.

Enigma is the first buffer type hero, that empowers his group and also empowers himself. This hero comes with quite a lot of unique mechanics. He is a mystic that was cursed and turned to stone. He is a mixture between an illusionist, arcanist and mystic. Let me explain how he works. He has an offensive buff &quot;Arcane Fervor&quot; and defensive buff &quot;Esoteric Barrier&quot;. You pick one of these 2 buffs since one cancels the other so you can&apos;t use both. ^^

Arcane Fervor gives 5% damage increase to your group until the end of the current battle and empowers Enigma&apos;s abilities offensively. Enigma does not get the passive buff but rather a random ability buff that lasts 2 rounds, either you increase the damage of your abilities, heal or you give some of them the capability to bleed the enemies.

Esoteric Barrier on the other hand, gives your group 5% protection until the end of the current battle and Enigma gets defensive benefits to his skills, it gives some of your abilities the chance to stun or debuff or you can also receive a crit buff. So as you see the longer the battle lasts the stronger your team becomes because the buff keeps stacking.

He has passive 40% protection and once he reaches 66% of health he loses 20% of his passive protection and under 33% loses the other 20% protection. This is supposed to simulate his stone skin being chipped away by his enemies. His health pool is the lowest of all classes though. Only one Enigma is allowed per group and the only other class he cannot travel with is the Revenant. He also provides a shovel on your missions.


[h1]Fragments &amp; Trinkets[/h1]
Now let&apos;s talk about his other unique thing and those are his trinkets and fragments. He has a unique camping ability called &quot;Enigmatic Manifestation&quot;. This ability manifests fragments of power that buff the main stat of a hero until the end of quest, you can stack these and bring them back to the Hamlet so you can bring them to new missions even if Enigma isn&apos;t present. The purpose of this is to help you with very hard missions, so now you can go farm fragments and decide what you will bring home, treasure or fragments to help you on your next hard mission. I had to increase the provision inventory in order to fit all my fragments, but i expanded it in a way so it makes sense, it can sell up to 32 items now. You can also get lucky during fragment crafting and create his enigmatic rarity trinkets which can only be obtained through this skill. Every hero can use each fragment once per mission.

[img]https://i.imgur.com/3J23aAj.png[/img]

Fragment list from left to right:

Fragment: Lethality - Increases CRIT by 5%. 
Fragment: Haste - Increases SPEED by 3.
Fragment: Evasion - Increases DODGE by 10.
Fragment: Precision - Increases ACCURACY by 5.
Fragment: Vigor - Increases DAMAGE by 15%
Fragment: Armor - Increases PROT by 10%
Fragment: Endurance - Increases MAX HP by 15%.
Fragment: Vitality - Restores 2 health every round for 10 rounds.


[h1]Combat Skills[/h1]
[b] Mystic Bolt: [/b] Attack position: 2,3 / Targets 1,2,3 / Effect: Dmg, can stun with ESO. BARRIER
[b] Illusionary Slash: [/b] Attack position: 2,3 / Targets 1+2 / Effect: Dmg, can bleed with ARC. FERVOR
[b] Phantasmal Pistol: [/b] Attack position: 2,3 / Targets 2+3+4 / Effect: Dmg, can bleed or dbf with buff.
[b] Delusional Exertion:[/b] A. Position: 2,3 / Targets 1+2+3 / Effect: Dmg, can stun or debuff with buff.
[b] Unusual Dynamism:[/b]A. Position: 2,3 / Targets: Self / Effect: Heals and increases ACC.
[b] Arcane Fervor:[/b]A. Position: 1,2,3,4 / Targets: ALL ALLY / Effect: +5% Dmg to group, offensive buff.
[b] Esoteric Barrier:[/b] A. Position: 1,2,3,4 / Targets: ALL ALLY / Effect: +5% Prot to group, defensive buff. 


[h1]Camping Skills[/h1]
[b] Enigmatic Manifestation: [/b]Creates fragments or trinkets that can be taken back to base.
[b] Puzzling Riddles: [/b] Reduces party stress by a small amount or large amount.
[b] Esoteric Arcanist: [/b] Gives Enigma&apos;s abilities chance to bleed, debuff and stun for 4 battles.
[b] Stone Skin:[/b] Gives group max hp and heal.

If you find any bugs/glitches, spelling errors or balance issues, you can give me your feedback in the comments section below or just add me, i prefer direct feedback. I hope you enjoy playing this class as much as i had fun making it and if a lot of people like it, i might make another one. ^^

Here are my other classes if you want to try them out:

[url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=913178378][img]https://i.imgur.com/B8Duftl.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=924245318][img]https://i.imgur.com/a1YoES1.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=934967620][img]https://i.imgur.com/EvnjeGp.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=947715735][img]https://i.imgur.com/wtvL4QS.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1100450515][img]https://i.imgur.com/bBYf01L.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1138503289][img]https://i.imgur.com/Wccrwn4.png[/img][/url][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1441036778][img]https://i.imgur.com/Ratr9w8.png[/img][/url]


[h1]Support[/h1]
Due to health issues my modding has been put on hold, but If you like what you see and you want me to do more in the future, you can support my mods by donating here:

[url=https://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_s-xclick&amp;hosted_button_id=PC3886U2YM8C6][img]https://i.imgur.com/6qUg1Xz.gif[/img][/url]


Thank you for all the positive feedback and your support, it does motivate me quite a bit!

Special thanks to &quot;Finezyjny&quot;(Polish), &quot;Rainfoxest&quot; &amp; &quot;Foxical&quot;(S-Chinese), &quot;halfmoon515&quot;(Korean)
and &quot;Chocostar&quot;(French) for translating my mod.

Special thanks to RedHook for making this great game and giving players the ability to mod it!

This mod is not an official Red Hook Studios product or product modification, and Red Hook Studios Inc. is not responsible in any way for changes or damages that may result from using the mod. Furthermore, “Darkest Dungeon” and the Darkest Dungeon logo are trademarks of Red Hook Studios Inc. All content in the game is Copyright Red Hook Studios Inc. All rights reserved.
</ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>970030269</PublishedFileId>
</project>

