<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>G:/steam/steamapps/workshop/content/262060/1201791082/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>[Remod]Inquisitor 圣裁官</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>public</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>0</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>0</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>0</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>character mod</Tags>
		<Tags>new class</Tags>
		<Tags>Remod</Tags>
		<Tags>Chinese</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>This is a Remake Mod. The oringinal Mod calls &quot;exorcist&quot; , I cant find it in steam workshop.I use its art work because i dont know anything about drawing. Thanks the original artist .

What i do : remake/redesign all skills and photoshop some icons and write almost all dialogs . 
重做内容：全部技能 ，部分图标，全部对白。

The mod isnt compatible with &quot;exorcist&quot; because they share the same id.
这是一个重做mod,原mod叫驱魔人。不与其兼容。

Support English and Schinese
支持英文和简体中文。

=====================================================
The inquisitor doesnt believe that they can save the day in darkness just by blessing or praying. He prefer to cleanse the evil by his hammer and sceptre.

Maybe he&apos;s not a warrior with excellent killing skills,but a valiant stares into the darkness without fear. He has variant ways to inquisite different kinds of blasphemers ,and any damage and stress he received will only firm his impenetrable faith.

====================================================
Skills descreption :

1、Fanatic Crush：every time he use this skill will improve his chance to stun the unholy
狂热碾压：轻微击晕，每次使用后会增加自身对邪秽的击晕几率。

2、Fervor : Award the warrior who fighting in the front line,of course,that &apos;s also who he considers himself as.
热诚：微量治愈前排及自身。

3、Banishment： He doesnt know much about the Eldritch,but enough to understand that they dont belong the world created by God. Push and Banish them away !
放逐：推开敌人，对来至异界的恶魔加成。

4、exorcism ： Stop fearing（dotStress) and wake him from coma and clear debuffs
驱邪： 驱除恐惧和眩晕和减益，加减益抗性。

5、soul trial ：Ignore the armor , judge their soul. But remember, you cant trial something&apos;s soul effectively by your faith if they have no concept about you god.
灵魂审判：无视护甲，对人类加成。

6、holly asylum：improve a compaion&apos;s protection and stress resistance
神圣庇护：增加同伴防御和压力抗性。

7、martyr ：prepare to sacrifice.More possible to get resolve when in high stress but also more possible to reach death when in zero HP.
殉道：增加美德几率，减死抗。

Camping skills:
1、Stair To Heaven： same with &quot;martyr&quot; 
天堂阶梯：殉道的扎营版。

2、Unbreakable Faith：stress damage to himself and improve the protection
不灭信仰：增压，加防。

3、Heathen Inquisition：stress damage to faithless teammates and make the believers relax
异端审判：增压无信者，减压信徒。

4、God Save Believers ：heal all the believers in team
天佑信徒：治愈全队信徒。

=======================

trinkets           饰品： 
written judgement  判决书
truncheon of light 圣光权杖
dedication chalice 奉献圣杯
fervor crest       热诚徽章 


========================================

player need to pay more attention to adjust his skills\teammates\trinkets\position according to different condition ,He can be very functional if you put him in the right situtation.
总体来说是一个功能型战士，比起其他英雄，他更需要你去按各种情况来调整站位、技能和饰品，才能打出最佳效果。</ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>1201791082</PublishedFileId>
</project>

