<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>c:/Program Files (x86)/Steam/steamapps/workshop/content/262060/Bloodclot Beta/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>The Bloodclot</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>hidden</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>0</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>0</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>0</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>bloodclot</Tags>
		<Tags>new class</Tags>
		<Tags>class mod</Tags>
		<Tags>bleed</Tags>
		<Tags>blight</Tags>
		<Tags>bleed/blight</Tags>
		<Tags>crimson court</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>&quot;The Feast Shortly Begins.
	
The Bloodclot is a highly variable and self sufficient hero. From the front, he savages enemies at close range. He pierces shell, bone, and armor alike with vampiric fangs that ravage those weakened by blight and bleed. He rips and consumes his foes flesh with mutated flesh that hungers for blood to sustain himself. With the strength granted by his curse, he tears targets to pieces with his claws, heightening his frenzied ability to consume his enemies. In the back rows, he rains hell down on the battlefield, no shuffling mosquito or retreating cultist able to escape him. He lobs balls of his own cursed festering blood at foes, opening their own wounds, or sprays accumulated bile to clear his thoughts. His most dangerous ability is utilized through Litmus, drowning the enemies in the very malignancies they inflict upon him. His body is ravenous and bottomless, and can consume the suffering of his allies, curing them of their ailments while bringing out his own.

-- This class mod is my first to properly be released here on steam, and I’m very happy to have come this far with it. Nearly all the art for this class is completed, though some trinkets are still using placeholders and I plan to improve upon the current icons and awkward looking animations in the future as my skill increases. Fx on attacks are still underway, but the Class is mechanically stable and completely usable. Please don’t hesitate to inform me of any bugs or glitches you happen to come across, and I will continue to work on updating this mod in the future to keep it fully functional. Thanks, and I hope your siege upon the courtyard is assisted by this hero. --

-- SKILLS --

LITMUS
Ranged
O O O O | O-O-O-O
A low damage move that hits the entire enemy team, slowing their speed and inflicting blight or bleed while you are blighted or bleeding respectively.

SHRED
Melee
- - O O | O O O -
The highest damaging melee move at your disposal, increases his healing done on hit, synchronizing with his other abilities.

PURGEFANG
Melee
- O O O | O O O -
A moderate damaging move with innate armor piercing. When used on a Blighted or Bleeding target, gains a massive damage boost, but cures the target. Use wisely.

LEECHBITE
Melee
- O O - | O O O -
A moderate damage dealing attack that heals yourself on hit. Useful for keeping him alive on the frontline or mitigating DOT damage.

CONSUMING CURSE
Friendly
O O O - | @O-O-O-O
A mild aoe heal that targets your full team, and cures allies. Beware overusing this ability, as it can inflict blight or bleed on yourself which racks up fast.

PUREBILE
Ranged
O O - - | O O O O
A low damage ranged attack with high blight damage. Stress heals self when used, hit or miss.

BLOODBURST
Ranged
O O - - | - O O O
A high damage ranged attack with high bleed damage, that also can lower enemy speed. Beware overuse of this ability, as this move inflicts bleed on yourself when used.

-- TRINKETS --

MAGGOT TEETH
Common
+20% Stun Resist
+20% Move Resist
-1 Speed

GANGRENE LUMP
Common
+10% Max Hp
+10% Blight Chance
-1 Speed

TWITCHING WING
Uncommon 
+8 Dodge
+3 Speed
+15% Stress Damage Taken

SILVER SPOON
Rare 
+10% Prot
-20% Stress Taken
+1 Speed
-20% Blight Chance
-20% Bleed Chance

SHED LEECH SKIN
Very Rare
+15% Max Hp
+30% Healing Skills

-- CRIMSON COURT TRINKETS --

MANSERVANT’S COLLAR
Crimson Court
+10% Crit while Bleeding
+30% Healing Skills while Bleeding

STAINED WINE GLASS
Crimson Court
+20% Damage
-20% Blight Resist
-20% Bleed Resist

SET BONUS
+15% Stress Taken
+10 Dodge while Bleeding
+3 Speed while Bleeding

-- CAMP SKILLS --

SHED SELF
Time Cost: 4
Heal 50% Hp
Cure Blight/Bleed
+1 Speed

OVERPOWER INSTINCTS
Time Cost: 3
Heal 20 Stress
+5 Accuracy
+10 Prot

EMBRACE BLOODTHIRST
Time Cost: 3
+20% Damage
+10 Dodge
Party: +25 Stress

PURIFY BLOOD
Time Cost: 1
Uses: 3
Cure Allies Disease
Cure Self Disease
Heal 10% Max Hp

-- BACKSTORY --
[img]https://imgur.com/T1RQW3L.jpeg[/img]

The Bloodclot was once a common peasant, scraping by to support himself and his family. The bitter years that took Miller&apos;s farm ruined many crop yields beyond the farmstead, including his own. Fell upon hard times, with no money, no food, he was growing desperate, when one fateful day, the Letter came. 

An invitation, from the prestigious Court of the Estate, offering him a chance of a lifetime. He departed immediately, bright with hope and confidence that this would ease their burdens. Upon arrival, he was inducted as a Manservant, but soon, much darker purposes they would use him for behind the sealed gate of the courtyard. After the arrival of the Countess, and the virulent curse she brought with her, the depravity of the Court only grew in its vileness. 

He was force fed cursed blood for their amusement, only to find his body did not yield to the curse so easily. They found him to be a bottomless vessel for the curse, and locked him in chains, feeding him ever more and more of the cursed blood. His body warped and the buzzing of the mosquitoes filled his mind but he did not give in. 

Eventually, his chains rusted and he broke free, only to find himself in the ever corrupting mire. He survived there for ages, hiding in the marsh, feeding on any pitiable cursed thing he could catch, and avoiding the watchful eyes of the great predators that now called the marsh their home. 

Until, the seal on the courtyard gate was broken at last, and the curse flowed forth unto the estate like a gaping wound. But, when a creature bleeds, the blood thickens, and the flow is stopped. And staggering out of the courtyard gates in the wake, came that Blood Clot.

	 &quot;</ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>2060478391</PublishedFileId>
</project>

