<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>E:\ProjectAndStuff\Darkest Dungeon Mods\Mods\Darkest Soul Variety Project</ModDataPath>
	<Title>Darkest Soul Variety Project</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails>
		Updated Loc for other languages
	</UpdateDetails>
	<Visibility>public</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>1</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>0</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>0</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>Monsters</Tags>
		<Tags>Dark Souls</Tags>
		<Tags>Undead</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>
	The mod aims to expand the dark souls monster content in Darkest Dungeon. 
	This mod is build around CarnifeX&apos;s Order of Sunlight, aiming to supplement the mod.
	
	[h1]Features[/h1]
	- 1 mini-boss based on Warrior of Sunlight made by CarnifeX
	- 7 undead monsters themed after the hollows from Dark Souls
	
	Most monsters are losely based on their Dark Souls counterparts which means that they have a simple parry mechanic and several Dark Souls inspired skills.
	
	You will encounter these guys in all regions (pretty low chance). 
	The Invader acts as a mini boss and will drop trinkets from &apos;Order of Sunlight&apos;.
	
	If you go on a mission with heroes that have the faction quirk you will have an increased chance of running into the Invader.
	
	[h1]Compatibility[/h1]
	Should be compatible with all mods as I use custom named files.
	
	For it to play nice with other monster mods it&apos;s advised to add -disable_monster_pre_loading to your launch options in steam.
	This parameter makes it so it doesn&apos;t load all monster files at the start of the dungeon.
	This helps with loading times and crashes.
	
	[h1]Load Order[/h1]
	Here is what my load order looks like in general:
	[Mods that overwrite vanilla files]
	[Quirk Mods]
	[Overhauls]
	Darkest Soul Variety Project
	Monster Variety Project
	[Monster Mods]
	[Mini-boss Mods]
	Order of Sunlight
	[Trinket Mods]
	[Classes]
	[Skins]
	
	
	[h1]Credits[/h1]
	CarnifeX for Order of Sunlight and helping me in general - [url=https://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198046434526/myworkshopfiles/?appid=262060]Workshop Carnifex[/url]
	AceroSteel for the art - [url=https://www.nexusmods.com/darkestdungeon/users/3564670]Nexus Page Acero[/url]
	
	[h1]Moonlit Dungeon[/h1]
	Come by the [url=https://discord.gg/VkXB87M]Moonlit Dungeon Discord[/url], 
	the modding hub for Darkest Dungeon and the best place to see previews of upcoming mods, 
	learn to mod, find artists and animators, beta test mods, give feedback to mod authors 
	or generally hang out and talk about DD!
	
	[h1]Donation[/h1]
	If you like what I do and want to support me you are free to donate some cents to me using the paypal link below.
	My mods will always be free and you should in no way feel obliged to donate. 
	
	[url=https://www.paypal.me/JensSels]Donate via PayPal[/url]
	
	</ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>1833932889</PublishedFileId>
</project>

