<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
  <language id="english">

    <entry id="journal_page_title_79"><![CDATA[The Whispers of my Mind (1/3)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_80"><![CDATA[The Whispers of my Mind (2/3)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_81"><![CDATA[The Whispers of my Mind (3/3)]]></entry>

    <entry id="journal_page_text_79"><![CDATA[Father has returned home in a drunken state once more. I stay in my bedroom while Mother tries her best to calm him down. I can hear him yell, hear him blame our plights on us, and hear him strike Mother with misdirected anger. As he grows louder, so too do the voices. I must not listen to them, for my Husband will return from his conscription soon and I will be here to welcome him. I am blessed to have someone so kind to love me, to care for me, despite my afflictions. Upon his return, I will show him how much I have missed him.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_80"><![CDATA[My Husband returned, but his first visit was not our home. I had waited for him faithfully all morning, all evening, and as the night grew darker I began to worry. I searched for him throughout the village. Through the window of the tavern I saw him, slathering his manhood between the legs of a bar wench. It could not be true. This was not my Husband, he would never break the vows we made so long ago. This was an imposter, some insidious demon that had killed my Husband and now mockingly wears his skin. I could not let this creature walk the earth any longer, and the voices agreed...]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_81"><![CDATA[With Father’s axe, I entered the tavern and landed its bladed head into the demon's heart. The Wench met her demise soon after, and the aftermath was gruesome. I had lost control of myself and hacked at the corpses of the two lovers, leaving them maimed and unrecognizable. My mind went blank, save for the voices. They instructed me to head home, and so I did. I returned to find Mother in a pool of blood. Father was asleep, the end of another bender. The voices guided me, and I landed my axe into the back of Father’s skull. My family, my beloved, all dead. The voices tell me of one more that must be put to rest...]]></entry>	
  </language>  

  <language id="brazilian">

    <entry id="journal_page_title_79"><![CDATA[Os Sussurros de Minha Mente (1/3)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_80"><![CDATA[Os Sussurros de Minha Mente (2/3)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_81"><![CDATA[Os Sussurros de Minha Mente (3/3)]]></entry>

    <entry id="journal_page_text_79"><![CDATA[O Pai voltou para casa em estado embriagado mais uma vez. Eu fico no meu quarto enquanto minha Mãe tenta o melhor para acalmá-lo. Consigo ouvi-lo gritar, ouço ele culpar nosso apuro em nós, e o ouço bater em Mãe com raiva mal direcionada. Quanto mais alto ele grita, o mesmo vale para as vozes. Eu não devo ouvi-las, pois meu Marido retornará de sua conscrição em breve e estarei aqui para recebê-lo. Sou abençoada de ter alguém tão gentil para me amar, para cuidar de mim, apesar de minhas aflições. Sob seu retorno, eu mostrarei o quanto senti sua falta.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_80"><![CDATA[Meu marido voltou, mas sua primeira visita não foi o nosso lar. Eu estive esperando por ele fielmente toda a manhã, toda a tarde, e assim que noite ficou mais e mais escura eu comecei a me preocupar. Eu o procurei por toda a parte do vilarejo. Pela janela da taverna eu o vi, esfregando sua virilidade entre as pernas de uma prostituta de bar. Não podia ser verdade. Este não era meu Marido, ele nunca quebraria os votos que fizemos a tanto tempo atrás. Este era um impostor, algum demônio traiçoeiro que matou meu Marido e agora veste sua pele ridicularmente. Eu não podia deixar esta criatura perambular na terra nem mais um minuto, e as vozes concordaram...]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_81"><![CDATA[Com o machado do Pai, eu entrei na taverna e desci sua cabeça laminada no coração do demônio. A prostituta encontrou seu fim logo depois, e o desfecho foi horrível. Eu perdi o controle de mim mesma e piquei os cadáveres dos dois amantes, deixando-os mutilados e irreconhecíveis. Minha mente se tornou branca, com exceção pelas vozes. Elas me instruíram a ir para casa, e assim o fiz. Eu voltei para encontrar a Mãe em uma poça de sangue. Pai estava dormindo, o final de mais uma bebedeira. As vozes me guiaram, e desci meu machado na nuca do crânio do Pai. Minha família, meu amado, todos mortos. As vozes me contam de mais uma que precisa ser colocada para dormir...]]></entry>	
  </language>  

  <language id="czech">

    <entry id="journal_page_title_79"><![CDATA[Šepot mé Mysli (1/3)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_80"><![CDATA[Šepot mé Mysli (2/3)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_81"><![CDATA[Šepot mé Mysli (3/3)]]></entry>

    <entry id="journal_page_text_79"><![CDATA[Otec se vrátil domů opět opilí. Zůstávám ve svém pokoji mezitím co se ho Matka pokouší uklidnit. Slyším jak řve, jak svádí vinu za náš nepříznivý stav na nás a slyším jak ve hněvu udeřuje Matku.Čím víc hlasitější je, tím víc jsou i hlasy. Nesmím je poslechnout, poněvadž se můj Manžel již brzy vrátí z odvodu a já tady budu, abych ho přivítala.Jsem požehnána, že mě někdo tak miluje,že se o mě stará, nehledíc na mé utrpení. Až se vrátí, ukážu mu, jak moc mi chyběl.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_80"><![CDATA[Můj Manžel se vrátil,ale jeho první návštěva nebyl náš dům.Čekala jsem na něj věrně celé ráno,celý večer, a jak se noc stávala temnější, začala jsem se bát. Hledala jsem ho po celé vesnici. Zahlédla jsem ho skrze okno hospody, jak rve své mužství mezi nohy hospodské dívky. To nemohla být pravda.Tohle nebyl můj Manžel, nikdy by neporušil náš slib který jsme složili již dávno. Tohle byl podvodník, nějaký zákeřný démon, který zabil mého Manžela a nyní posměšně nosí jeho kůži. Nemohla jsem toto stvoření nechat nadále chodit po zemi a hlasy souhlasily.]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_81"><![CDATA[S Otcovou sekerou jsem vstoupila do hospody a zabořila její ostří do démonova srdce. Dívka se setkala s osudem krátce poté a následky byly hrozné. Ztratila jsem nad sebou kontrolu a sekala jsem do mrtvol dvou milenců, dokud nezůstaly znetvoření a nepoznatelní. Moje mysl se zatemnila, až na hlasy, které přetrvaly. Poručili mi , abych šla domů a to jsme také udělala. Vrátila jsem se jen, abych našla Matku ležet v louži krve. Otec spal, konec dalšího pití.Hlasy mě vedly a já jsem zarazila sekeru do Otcova týlu.Má rodina,mý milovaní, všichni mrtví. Hlasy mi říkají ještě o jednom, který musí být zabit...]]></entry>	
  </language>  

  <language id="french">

    <entry id="journal_page_title_79"><![CDATA[Les Chuchotements de mon Esprit (1/3)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_80"><![CDATA[Les Chuchotements de mon Esprit (2/3)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_81"><![CDATA[Les Chuchotements de mon Esprit (3/3)]]></entry>

    <entry id="journal_page_text_79"><![CDATA[Père est revenu à la maison dans un état d’ivresse une fois de plus. Je reste dans ma chambre pendant que Mère fait de son mieux pour le calmer. Je l’entends hurler, je l’entends nous blâmer pour toutes nos misères, et je l’entends la frapper avec une colère mal dirigée. Plus il devient bruyant, les voix le deviennent aussi. Je ne dois pas les écouter, parce que mon Mari reviendra bientôt de sa conscription et je serai là pour l’accueillir. Je suis bénie d’avoir quelqu’un de si attentionné pour m’aimer, pour me prendre soin en dépit de mes afflictions. À son retour, je lui montrerai à quel point il m’a manqué.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_80"><![CDATA[Mon Mari est revenu, mais sa première visite n’était pas notre foyer. J’ai attendu fidèlement toute la matinée, tout l’après-midi, et, alors que la nuit commençait à tomber j’ai commencé à m’inquiéter. Je l’ai cherché partout dans le village. À travers la fenêtre de la taverne je l’ai aperçu, en train de plonger son membre entre les jambes d’une coureuse. Ça ne pouvait être vrai. Ce n’était pas mon Mari, il n’aurait jamais brisé le serment que nous avons fait il y a si longtemps. C’était un imposteur, un démon insidieux qui a tué mon Mari et porte maintenant sa peau d’un air moqueur. Je ne pouvais pas laisser cette créature sur terre un instant de plus, et les voix étaient d’accord...]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_81"><![CDATA[Avec la hache de Père, j’ai entré dans la taverne et porté sa lame en plein dans le cœur du démon. La coureuse a connu sa perte quelques instants plus tard, et les séquelles étaient macabres. J’ai perdu le contrôle de moi-même et taillé les cadavres des deux amants, les laissant estropiés et méconnaissables. Mon esprit est devenu vide, mis à part les voix. Ils m’ont dit de retourner à la maison, et donc j’y suis retourné. Je suis revenue pour découvrir Mère gisant dans son propre sang. Père était endormi, la fin d’une autre beuverie. Les voix m’ont guidée, et j’ai planté ma hache à l’arrière de son crâne. Ma famille, mon bien-aimé, tous morts. Les voix me parlent d’une autre qui doit être mise au repos...]]></entry>	
  </language>  

  <language id="german">

    <entry id="journal_page_title_79"><![CDATA[The Whispers of my Mind (1/3)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_80"><![CDATA[The Whispers of my Mind (2/3)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_81"><![CDATA[The Whispers of my Mind (3/3)]]></entry>

    <entry id="journal_page_text_79"><![CDATA[Father has returned home in a drunken state once more. I stay in my bedroom while Mother tries her best to calm him down. I can hear him yell, hear him blame our plights on us, and hear him strike Mother with misdirected anger. As he grows louder, so too do the voices. I must not listen to them, for my Husband will return from his conscription soon and I will be here to welcome him. I am blessed to have someone so kind to love me, to care for me, despite my afflictions. Upon his return, I will show him how much I have missed him.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_80"><![CDATA[My Husband returned, but his first visit was not our home. I had waited for him faithfully all morning, all evening, and as the night grew darker I began to worry. I searched for him throughout the village. Through the window of the tavern I saw him, slathering his manhood between the legs of a bar wench. It could not be true. This was not my Husband, he would never break the vows we made so long ago. This was an imposter, some insidious demon that had killed my Husband and now mockingly wears his skin. I could not let this creature walk the earth any longer, and the voices agreed...]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_81"><![CDATA[With Father’s axe, I entered the tavern and landed its bladed head into the demon's heart. The Wench met her demise soon after, and the aftermath was gruesome. I had lost control of myself and hacked at the corpses of the two lovers, leaving them maimed and unrecognizable. My mind went blank, save for the voices. They instructed me to head home, and so I did. I returned to find Mother in a pool of blood. Father was asleep, the end of another bender. The voices guided me, and I landed my axe into the back of Father’s skull. My family, my beloved, all dead. The voices tell me of one more that must be put to rest...]]></entry>	
  </language>  

  <language id="italian">

    <entry id="journal_page_title_79"><![CDATA[I Sussurri della mia Mente (1/3)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_80"><![CDATA[I Sussurri della mia Mente (2/3)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_81"><![CDATA[I Sussurri della mia Mente (3/3)]]></entry>

    <entry id="journal_page_text_79"><![CDATA[Mio padre è tornato a casa, ancora una volta, ubriaco. Sono nella mia stanza mentre Madre cerca di fare del suo meglio per calmarlo. Lo sento urlare, lo sento dare a noi la colpa dei nostri problemi, e lo sento colpire Madre con rabbia male indirizzata. Più forte lui grida, più le voci diventano forti. Non devo ascoltarle, perché presto mio Marito tornerà a casa dalla sua coscrizione e io sarò lì a dargli il benvenuto. Sono davvero fortunata ad avere un uomo così buono che mi ama, che si prende cura di me, nonostante le mie afflizioni. Quando tornerà gli mostrerò quanto mi è mancato.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_80"><![CDATA[Mio Marito è tornato, ma la sua prima visita non è stata la nostra casa. L’ho aspettato fedelmente tutta la mattina, tutta la sera, e una volta che s’è fatto tardi ho iniziato a preoccuparmi. L’ho cercato in lungo e in largo per il villaggio. Attraverso la finestra della taverna l’ho visto, mentre spalmava la sua mascolinità tra le gambe di una puttana. Non poteva essere vero. Non era mio Marito, lui non avrebbe mai rotto i voti che ci siamo fatti così tanto tempo fa. Questo era un impostore, qualche demone insidioso che ha ucciso mio Marito e che ora indossa la sua pelle per farsi gioco di me. Non potevo permettere a questa creatura di camminare ulteriormente su questa terra, e le voci concordavano...]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_81"><![CDATA[Con l’ascia di mio Padre, sono entrata nella taverna e ho colpito il cuore del demone. La Sgualdrina ha incontrato la sua fine poco dopo, e i postumi sono stati raccapriccianti. Ho perso controllo di me stessa e ho violato i corpi ormai morti dei due amanti, lasciandoli mutilati ed irriconoscibili. La mia mente si è annebbiata, eccetto per il fatto che riuscivo comunque a sentire le voci. Mi hanno detto di tornare a casa, e così ho fatto. Al mio ritorno ho visto mia Madre in una pozza di sangue. Padre era collassato per terra a causa dell’ennesima sbronza. Le voci mi hanno guidata ancora e con l’ascia ho colpito mio Padre dietro al cranio. La mia famiglia, il mio amato, tutti morti. Le voci, però, mi sussurrano che ancora una persona deve vedere la sua fine...]]></entry>	
  </language>  

  <language id="japanese">

    <entry id="journal_page_title_79"><![CDATA[The Whispers of my Mind (1/3)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_80"><![CDATA[The Whispers of my Mind (2/3)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_81"><![CDATA[The Whispers of my Mind (3/3)]]></entry>

    <entry id="journal_page_text_79"><![CDATA[Father has returned home in a drunken state once more. I stay in my bedroom while Mother tries her best to calm him down. I can hear him yell, hear him blame our plights on us, and hear him strike Mother with misdirected anger. As he grows louder, so too do the voices. I must not listen to them, for my Husband will return from his conscription soon and I will be here to welcome him. I am blessed to have someone so kind to love me, to care for me, despite my afflictions. Upon his return, I will show him how much I have missed him.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_80"><![CDATA[My Husband returned, but his first visit was not our home. I had waited for him faithfully all morning, all evening, and as the night grew darker I began to worry. I searched for him throughout the village. Through the window of the tavern I saw him, slathering his manhood between the legs of a bar wench. It could not be true. This was not my Husband, he would never break the vows we made so long ago. This was an imposter, some insidious demon that had killed my Husband and now mockingly wears his skin. I could not let this creature walk the earth any longer, and the voices agreed...]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_81"><![CDATA[With Father’s axe, I entered the tavern and landed its bladed head into the demon's heart. The Wench met her demise soon after, and the aftermath was gruesome. I had lost control of myself and hacked at the corpses of the two lovers, leaving them maimed and unrecognizable. My mind went blank, save for the voices. They instructed me to head home, and so I did. I returned to find Mother in a pool of blood. Father was asleep, the end of another bender. The voices guided me, and I landed my axe into the back of Father’s skull. My family, my beloved, all dead. The voices tell me of one more that must be put to rest...]]></entry>	
  </language>  

  <language id="koreana">

    <entry id="journal_page_title_79"><![CDATA[내 마음속의 속삭임 (1/3)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_80"><![CDATA[내 마음속의 속삭임 (2/3)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_81"><![CDATA[내 마음속의 속삭임 (3/3)]]></entry>

    <entry id="journal_page_text_79"><![CDATA[아버지는 다시 한 번 술 취한 상태로 집으로 돌아오셨다. 나는 어머니가 그를 진정시키려고 최선을 다하는 동안 내 침실에 있다. 나는 그가 고함치는 것을 들을 수 있고, 그가 우리의 곤경을 우리에게 탓하는 것을 들을 수 있고, 그가 잘못된 분노로 어머니를 때리는 것을 들을 수 있다. 그가 더 크게 소리칠수록, 목소리도 그만큼 더 커진다. 나는 그들의 말을 듣지 말아야 한다. 왜냐하면 내 남편은 곧 징병에서 돌아오고 나는 그를 맞이하기 위해 여기에 있을 것이기 때문이다. 나를 사랑하고, 나를 돌봐줄 수 있는, 나의 괴로움에도 불구하고, 나는 축복받은 사람이다. 그가 돌아오면, 나는 그에게 내가 얼마나 그를 그리워했는지 보여줄 것이다.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_80"><![CDATA[남편이 돌아왔지만 그의 첫 방문이 우리 집은 아니었다. 나는 아침 내내, 저녁 내내 성실하게 그를 기다렸으며, 밤이 깊어지자 걱정이 되기 시작했다. 나는 마을 곳곳에서 그를 찾아다녔다. 나는 주점의 창문을 통해 그가 남자다움을 술집 아가씨의 다리 사이로 날려보내는 것을 보았다. 그게 사실일 리 없어. 이 사람은 내 남편이 아니야. 그는 우리가 오래전에 했던 맹세를 절대 어기지 않을 거야. 이것은 내 남편을 죽이고 조롱하듯이 그의 피부를 입었던 사기꾼이자, 어떤 음흉한 악마인 게 분명했다. 나는 이 생물이 더 이상 지구를 걷게 할 수 없었고, 그리고 그 목소리는 동의했다...]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_81"><![CDATA[아버지의 도끼로, 나는 여관으로 들어가 날이 선 앞부분을 악마의 심장에 내리쳤다. 아가씨도 얼마 지나지 않아 그녀의 죽음을 맞이했고, 그리고 그 여파는 끔찍했다. 나는 나 자신을 통제하지 못하고 두 연인의 시체를 난도질하여 그들을 불구로 만들고 알아볼 수 없게 만들었다. 내 마음은 텅텅 비었고, 그 목소리를 위해 아껴뒀다. 그들은 나에게 집으로 향하라고 지시했고, 그래서 나는 그렇게 했다. 나는 피투성이의 어머니를 찾기 위해 돌아왔다. 아버지는 잠들어 계셨고, 또 다른 주정 거림의 끝이었다. 그 목소리가 나를 인도하여 주었고, 나는 아버지의 두개골 뒤쪽에 도끼를 내리꽂았다. 나의 가족, 내가 사랑하던 사람은 모두 죽었다. 그 목소리가 마무리 지어야 할 일이 한가지 더 있다고 말하였다...]]></entry>	
  </language>  

  <language id="koreanb">

    <entry id="journal_page_title_79"><![CDATA[내 마음속의 속삭임 (1/3)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_80"><![CDATA[내 마음속의 속삭임 (2/3)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_81"><![CDATA[내 마음속의 속삭임 (3/3)]]></entry>

    <entry id="journal_page_text_79"><![CDATA[아버지는 다시 한 번 술 취한 상태로 집으로 돌아오셨다. 나는 어머니가 그를 진정시키려고 최선을 다하는 동안 내 침실에 있다. 나는 그가 고함치는 것을 들을 수 있고, 그가 우리의 곤경을 우리에게 탓하는 것을 들을 수 있고, 그가 잘못된 분노로 어머니를 때리는 것을 들을 수 있다. 그가 더 크게 소리칠수록, 목소리도 그만큼 더 커진다. 나는 그들의 말을 듣지 말아야 한다. 왜냐하면 내 남편은 곧 징병에서 돌아오고 나는 그를 맞이하기 위해 여기에 있을 것이기 때문이다. 나를 사랑하고, 나를 돌봐줄 수 있는, 나의 괴로움에도 불구하고, 나는 축복받은 사람이다. 그가 돌아오면, 나는 그에게 내가 얼마나 그를 그리워했는지 보여줄 것이다.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_80"><![CDATA[남편이 돌아왔지만 그의 첫 방문이 우리 집은 아니었다. 나는 아침 내내, 저녁 내내 성실하게 그를 기다렸으며, 밤이 깊어지자 걱정이 되기 시작했다. 나는 마을 곳곳에서 그를 찾아다녔다. 나는 주점의 창문을 통해 그가 남자다움을 술집 아가씨의 다리 사이로 날려보내는 것을 보았다. 그게 사실일 리 없어. 이 사람은 내 남편이 아니야. 그는 우리가 오래전에 했던 맹세를 절대 어기지 않을 거야. 이것은 내 남편을 죽이고 조롱하듯이 그의 피부를 입었던 사기꾼이자, 어떤 음흉한 악마인 게 분명했다. 나는 이 생물이 더 이상 지구를 걷게 할 수 없었고, 그리고 그 목소리는 동의했다...]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_81"><![CDATA[아버지의 도끼로, 나는 여관으로 들어가 날이 선 앞부분을 악마의 심장에 내리쳤다. 아가씨도 얼마 지나지 않아 그녀의 죽음을 맞이했고, 그리고 그 여파는 끔찍했다. 나는 나 자신을 통제하지 못하고 두 연인의 시체를 난도질하여 그들을 불구로 만들고 알아볼 수 없게 만들었다. 내 마음은 텅텅 비었고, 그 목소리를 위해 아껴뒀다. 그들은 나에게 집으로 향하라고 지시했고, 그래서 나는 그렇게 했다. 나는 피투성이의 어머니를 찾기 위해 돌아왔다. 아버지는 잠들어 계셨고, 또 다른 주정 거림의 끝이었다. 그 목소리가 나를 인도하여 주었고, 나는 아버지의 두개골 뒤쪽에 도끼를 내리꽂았다. 나의 가족, 내가 사랑하던 사람은 모두 죽었다. 그 목소리가 마무리 지어야 할 일이 한가지 더 있다고 말하였다...]]></entry>	
  </language>  

  <language id="polish">

    <entry id="journal_page_title_79"><![CDATA[Szepty mojego umysłu (1/3)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_80"><![CDATA[Szepty mojego umysłu (2/3)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_81"><![CDATA[Szepty mojego umysłu (3/3)]]></entry>

    <entry id="journal_page_text_79"><![CDATA[Ojciec wrócił do domu pijany jak zwykle. Siedzę w mojej sypialni, kiedy matka z całych sił próbuje go uspokoić. Słyszę jak krzyczy, słyszę jak wini nas za naszą ciężką sytuację i słyszę jak uderza matkę w niepotrzebnej złości. Staje się coraz głośniejszy, tak samo jak głosy. Nie mogę ich słuchać, gdyż mój mąż powróci niedługo  z poboru, a ja będę tu, aby go powitać. Jestem błogosławiona, że mam kogoś kto kocha mnie i opiekuje się mną, pomimo moich dolegliwości. Po powrocie pokażę mu, jak bardzo za nim tęskniłam.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_80"><![CDATA[Mój mąż powrócił, ale jego pierwsza wizyta nie była w naszym domu. Czekałam na niego, cały ranek, cały wieczór, a gdy nastała ciemna noc, zaczęłam się martwić. Szukałam go w całej wiosce. Przez okno tawerny zobaczyłam go, rozpościerającego jego męskość między nogami barowej dziewki.To nie może być prawda. To nie był mój mąż, on nigdy nie złamałby przyczeczeń które złożyliśmy sobie dawno temu To był oszust, jakiś podstępny demon, który zabił mojego męża, a teraz kpiąco nosi jego skórę. Nie mogłam pozwolić temu stworzeniu chodzić po ziemi, a głosy zgodziły się...]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_81"><![CDATA[Weszłam do tawerny z ojcowskim toporem i zanurzyłam jego ostrze w sercu demona. Dziewka spotkała swoją śmiercią niedługo po tym, a następstwa były makabryczne. Straciłam kontrolę nad sobą i ociosałam ciała kochanków, zostawiając ich okaleczonych i nierozpoznawalnych. Moje zmysły zniknęły, z wyjątkiem głosów. Kazały mi wrócić do domu i tak zrobiłam. Wróciłam, aby zobaczyć matkę w kałuży krwi. Ojciec spał, koniec kolejnej popijawy. Głosy mnie prowadziły, a ja umieściłam topór w tył ojcowskiej czaszki. Moja rodzina, mój ukochany, wszyscy zmarli. Głosy mówią mi o jeszcze jedenej osobie, która musi zaznać odpoczynku...]]></entry>	
  </language>  

  <language id="russian">

    <entry id="journal_page_title_79"><![CDATA[Шёпот Моего Разума (1/3)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_80"><![CDATA[Шёпот Моего Разума (2/3)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_81"><![CDATA[Шёпот Моего Разума (3/3)]]></entry>

    <entry id="journal_page_text_79"><![CDATA[Отец снова вернулся домой пьяный. Я остаюсь в своей спальне, пока Мать изо всех сил пытается успокоить его. Я слышу его крик, слышу, как он обвиняет нас во всех наших бедах, и слышу, как он бьёт Маму в пьяном гневе. Чем громче он становится звук снаружи, тем громче становятся голоса. Я не должна их слушать, ведь скоро мой муж вернётся с военного призыва, и я буду здесь, чтобы встретить его. Я счастлива, что кто-то так любит меня, заботится обо мне, несмотря на мои страдания. Когда он вернётся, я покажу ему, как сильно я по нему скучала.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_80"><![CDATA[Мой муж вернулся, но первым он посетил не наш дом. Я ждала его всё утро, весь вечер, и с наступлением темноты я начала волноваться. Я искала его по всей деревне. Через окно таверны я увидела его, просовывающего своё мужское достоинство между ног барной девки. Это не могло быть правдой. Это не мой муж, он никогда не нарушит обетов, которые мы давали друг другу давным-давно. Это был самозванец, какой-то коварный демон, который убил моего Мужа и теперь насмешливо носит его кожу.  Я не могла позволить этому существу больше ходить по земле, и голоса согласились...]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_81"><![CDATA[С отцовским топором я вошла в таверну и пустила его лезвие в сердце демона. Девка встретила свою кончину сразу после него, и последствия были ужасными. Я потеряла контроль над собой и вскрыла тела двух возлюбленных, оставляя их искалеченными и изуродованными. Мой разум опустел, и только голоса оставались в голове. Они приказали мне вернуться домой, что я и сделала. Я вернулась, чтобы найти Мать в луже собственной крови. Отец лежал, отсыпаясь после очередного запоя. Голоса велели мне, и я замахнулась топором в затылок Отца. Моя семья, мой любимый, все мертвы. Голоса говорят мне ещё о том, что нужно упокоить...]]></entry>	
  </language>    
 
  <language id="schinese">

    <entry id="journal_page_title_79"><![CDATA[我心中的低语 (1/3)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_80"><![CDATA[我心中的低语 (2/3)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_81"><![CDATA[我心中的低语 (3/3)]]></entry>

    <entry id="journal_page_text_79"><![CDATA[父亲又喝到酩酊大醉才回家。我待在卧室里，而母亲则尽力使他平静下来。我可以听到他大吵大闹，听到他把我们的困境都归咎于我们，并听到他在盆怒中殴打击母亲。随着外面的声音越来越大，脑海中的声音也越来越大。我不可以听下去，因为我的丈夫很快就会从他的征兵中回来，而我会快乐地迎接他。尽管很痛苦，但我庆幸有一位如此善良的人爱我，照顾我。等他回来后，我会告诉他我有多想念他。]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_80"><![CDATA[我的丈夫回来了，但他的第一时间访问的并不是我们的家。我忠诚地等候着他，由早到晚，然后随着夜幕渐渐变暗，我开始担心。我走遍整个村庄寻找他。在一间酒馆的窗户内，我看到了他，与一名女侍交缠在一起。那不可能是真的，那不是我的丈夫，他绝对不会打破我们的誓言。他是假冒者，是邪恶的恶魔杀死了我的丈夫，并穿上他的皮。我不能让这生物在这片土地上行走，然后声音们也同意了...]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_81"><![CDATA[我对自己失去了控制，并且继续劈砍那两名恋人的尸体，直到变得支离破碎、面目全非。我的心变得一片空白，只剩下一把声音。它们指示我回家，所以我回家了。我发现母亲倒在血泊之中。父亲已经睡着，安眠在酒意之中。声音们引导着我，手斧牢牢地砍在父亲头颅的正后方。我的家人、我的至爱，全都死了。声音们告诉我还有一个人必须要安眠...]]></entry>	
  </language>  
  
  <language id="spanish">

    <entry id="journal_page_title_79"><![CDATA[Los susurros de mi mente (1/3)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_80"><![CDATA[Los susurros de mi mente (2/3)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_81"><![CDATA[Los susurros de mi mente (3/3)]]></entry>

    <entry id="journal_page_text_79"><![CDATA[Mi Padre ha vuelto a casa en estado de ebriedad una vez más. Me quedo en mi habitación mientras mi Madre hace todo lo posible por calmarlo. Puedo escucharlo gritar, escucharlo culparnos de nuestros sufrimientos y escucharlo golpear a mi Madre por su frustración. A medida que crece más fuerte, también lo hacen las voces. No debo escucharlos, porque mi esposo volverá pronto de su servicio militar y estaré aquí para darle la bienvenida.Tengo la bendición de tener a alguien tan amable de amarme, de cuidarme, a pesar de mis aflicciones. A su regreso, le mostraré cuánto lo he extrañado.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_80"><![CDATA[Mi esposo regresó, pero su primera visita no fue nuestra casa. Lo había esperado fielmente toda la mañana, toda la tarde, y a medida que la noche se hacía más oscura comencé a preocuparme. Lo busqué por todo el pueblo. A través de la ventana de la taberna, lo vi, deslizando su miembro viril entre las piernas de una moza. No podía ser cierto. Este no era mi marido, nunca rompería los votos que hicimos hace tanto tiempo. Este era un impostor, un demonio insidioso que había matado a mi Esposo y ahora llevaba su piel burlonamente. No podía dejar que esta criatura caminara por la tierra por más tiempo, y las voces estuvieron de acuerdo...]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_81"><![CDATA[Con el hacha de mi Padre, entré en la taberna y aterricé su cabeza afilada en el corazón del demonio. La moza se encontró con su fallecimiento poco después, y las consecuencias fueron espantosas. Mi mente se quedó en blanco, salvo por las voces. Me ordenaron que me fuera a casa, y así lo hice. Al volver encontré a mi Madre en un charco de sangre. Mi Padre estaba dormido, al final de otra juerga. Las voces me guiaron, y aterricé mi hacha en la parte posterior del cráneo de mi Padre. Mi familia, mi amado, todos muertos. Las voces me hablan de una más que hay que poner a descansar...]]></entry>	
  </language>  

  <language id="tchinese">

    <entry id="journal_page_title_79"><![CDATA[The Whispers of my Mind (1/3)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_80"><![CDATA[The Whispers of my Mind (2/3)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_81"><![CDATA[The Whispers of my Mind (3/3)]]></entry>

    <entry id="journal_page_text_79"><![CDATA[Father has returned home in a drunken state once more. I stay in my bedroom while Mother tries her best to calm him down. I can hear him yell, hear him blame our plights on us, and hear him strike Mother with misdirected anger. As he grows louder, so too do the voices. I must not listen to them, for my Husband will return from his conscription soon and I will be here to welcome him. I am blessed to have someone so kind to love me, to care for me, despite my afflictions. Upon his return, I will show him how much I have missed him.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_80"><![CDATA[My Husband returned, but his first visit was not our home. I had waited for him faithfully all morning, all evening, and as the night grew darker I began to worry. I searched for him throughout the village. Through the window of the tavern I saw him, slathering his manhood between the legs of a bar wench. It could not be true. This was not my Husband, he would never break the vows we made so long ago. This was an imposter, some insidious demon that had killed my Husband and now mockingly wears his skin. I could not let this creature walk the earth any longer, and the voices agreed...]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_81"><![CDATA[With Father’s axe, I entered the tavern and landed its bladed head into the demon's heart. The Wench met her demise soon after, and the aftermath was gruesome. I had lost control of myself and hacked at the corpses of the two lovers, leaving them maimed and unrecognizable. My mind went blank, save for the voices. They instructed me to head home, and so I did. I returned to find Mother in a pool of blood. Father was asleep, the end of another bender. The voices guided me, and I landed my axe into the back of Father’s skull. My family, my beloved, all dead. The voices tell me of one more that must be put to rest...]]></entry>	
  </language>    
 
</root>

