<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
  <language id="english">
    <entry id="journal_page_title_82"><![CDATA[The Teacher and the Student (1/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_83"><![CDATA[The Teacher and the Student (2/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_84"><![CDATA[The Teacher and the Student (3/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_85"><![CDATA[The Teacher and the Student (4/4)]]></entry>
	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_82"><![CDATA[Words hang in the air. My courtesans loosen lips and secrets flow like wine from a bottle. There is talk of a new warrior generation being trained. The Shoguns are preparing for war and they have assigned the best of the elder generation as mentors for their bloody art. Many are harsh and unforgiving, but there is talk of a different kind. A Teacher that shows compassion for his students. One that teaches through kindness rather than cruelty.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_83"><![CDATA[Men and women talk, and they speak of a budding secret from the kind Teacher. Whispers of the Teacher and the Student. No one knows who the Student is, but he arrived one day to train under the Teacher. “The Student is a skilled swordsman”, one would whisper. “He has much to learn from the Teacher”, another would say. As time passed, the Teacher would spend more and more time with the Student, neglecting his other pupils. Then, sweetened lips let loose talk of the two seen under a blossom tree, sharing a kiss.]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_84"><![CDATA[The Pleasure District remains quiet tonight, for a great tragedy has arisen. The kind Teacher and his pupils have been slaughtered. Words found in dark places tell that the Student has vanished, that perhaps he was an assassin sent to sabotage the Shoguns’ plans. Perhaps the Teacher could not face that his lover was not who he thought he was, and that his heart led him to failure. Whispers among the rats spit insults at the Teacher. They speak of his weakness, that he is a shameful warrior, that he will be forgotten.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_85"><![CDATA[A most interesting secret has been leaked from noble lips. The Teacher did not die. They speak that he has returned from the dead, that the wound believed to have pierced his heart had actually missed. He begs at the Shoguns’ feet for forgiveness, but the warlords are not so easily swayed. The Teacher had already died, and his name tarnished and shamed. They decree that with his second life, he must collect 666 souls for the Shoguns, and only when this impossible deed is complete will his name be redeemed. Whether it is truth or lie, this is a most intriguing secret indeed.]]></entry>	
	</language>  
  <language id="brazilian">
    <entry id="journal_page_title_82"><![CDATA[O professor e a estudante (1/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_83"><![CDATA[O professor e a estudante (2/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_84"><![CDATA[O professor e a estudante (3/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_85"><![CDATA[O professor e a estudante (4/4)]]></entry>
	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_82"><![CDATA[Palavras pairam no ar. Minhas cortesãs soltam seus lábios e segredos fluem como vinho de uma garrafa. Fala-se de uma nova geração guerreira sendo treinada. Os Shoguns estão se preparando para a guerra e atribuíram o melhor da geração mais velha como mentores de sua arte sangrenta. Muitos são duros e implacáveis, mas fala-se de um tipo diferente. Um professor que mostra compaixão por seus alunos. Aquele que ensina com bondade e não com crueldade.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_83"><![CDATA[Homens e mulheres conversam, e eles falam de um segredo do gentil Mestre. Sussurros entre o professor e o aluno. Ninguém sabe quem é o aluno, mas chegou um dia desses para treinar com o professor. “O estudante é um espadachim habilidoso”, alguém sussurrava. "Ele tem muito a aprender com o professor", outro sussurrava. Com o passar do tempo, o professor passava cada vez mais e mais tempo com o aluno, negligenciando seus outros pupilos. Então, os lábios adocicados soltaram uma fofoca dos dois sendo vistos debaixo de uma árvore florida, se beijando.]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_84"><![CDATA[O Distrito do Prazer permanece quieto esta noite, pois uma grande tragédia aconteceu. Aquele gentil Professor e seus adoráveis alunos foram completamente massacrados! Palavras ouvidas em lugares escuros dizem e até mesmo afirmam que o Estudante particular do professor desapareceu, que talvez ele fosse um assassino enviado para sabotar os planos dos Shoguns.Talvez o Mestre não conseguiu encarar o fato de que seu "amante" não era quem ele pensava ser, e que seu coração o levou ao fracasso. Sussurros entre os ratos cuspiram insultos ao pobre professor. Eles falam de sua fraqueza em meio ao combate, que ele é uma vergonha como guerreiro, que ele será esquecido.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_85"><![CDATA[Um segredo muito mais interessante vazou dos lábios nobres. O professor na verdade não morrera. Dizem que ele voltou dos mortos, que a ferida que se acreditava ter perfurado seu coração tinha realmente sumido. Ele implora pelo perdão aos pés dos Shoguns, mas os senhores da guerra não são influenciados tão facilmente. O Professor que já havia morrido e tido seu nome manchado por tamanha vergonha foi condenado a uma tarefa hedionda. Os Shoguns decretaram que com sua segunda vida, ele deverá coletar 666 almas para o Império, e somente quando este ato impossível for completado seu nome será redimido. Se é verdade ou mentira, este é um segredo muito intrigante de fato.]]></entry>	
	</language>  
  <language id="czech">
    <entry id="journal_page_title_82"><![CDATA[The Teacher and the Student (1/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_83"><![CDATA[The Teacher and the Student (2/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_84"><![CDATA[The Teacher and the Student (3/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_85"><![CDATA[The Teacher and the Student (4/4)]]></entry>
	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_82"><![CDATA[Words hang in the air. My courtesans loosen lips and secrets flow like wine from a bottle. There is talk of a new warrior generation being trained. The Shoguns are preparing for war and they have assigned the best of the elder generation as mentors for their bloody art. Many are harsh and unforgiving, but there is talk of a different kind. A Teacher that shows compassion for his students. One that teaches through kindness rather than cruelty.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_83"><![CDATA[Men and women talk, and they speak of a budding secret from the kind Teacher. Whispers of the Teacher and the Student. No one knows who the Student is, but he arrived one day to train under the Teacher. “The Student is a skilled swordsman”, one would whisper. “He has much to learn from the Teacher”, another would say. As time passed, the Teacher would spend more and more time with the Student, neglecting his other pupils. Then, sweetened lips let loose talk of the two seen under a blossom tree, sharing a kiss.]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_84"><![CDATA[The Pleasure District remains quiet tonight, for a great tragedy has arisen. The kind Teacher and his pupils have been slaughtered. Words found in dark places tell that the Student has vanished, that perhaps he was an assassin sent to sabotage the Shoguns’ plans. Perhaps the Teacher could not face that his lover was not who he thought he was, and that his heart led him to failure. Whispers among the rats spit insults at the Teacher. They speak of his weakness, that he is a shameful warrior, that he will be forgotten.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_85"><![CDATA[A most interesting secret has been leaked from noble lips. The Teacher did not die. They speak that he has returned from the dead, that the wound believed to have pierced his heart had actually missed. He begs at the Shoguns’ feet for forgiveness, but the warlords are not so easily swayed. The Teacher had already died, and his name tarnished and shamed. They decree that with his second life, he must collect 666 souls for the Shoguns, and only when this impossible deed is complete will his name be redeemed. Whether it is truth or lie, this is a most intriguing secret indeed.]]></entry>	
	</language>  
  <language id="french">
    <entry id="journal_page_title_82"><![CDATA[Le Maître et l’Élève (1/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_83"><![CDATA[Le Maître et l’Élève (2/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_84"><![CDATA[Le Maître et l’Élève (3/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_85"><![CDATA[Le Maître et l’Élève (4/4)]]></entry>
	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_82"><![CDATA[Les mots courent. Mes courtisans desserrent leurs lèvres et les secrets coulent à flot comme le vin d’une bouteille. On parle d’une nouvelle génération de guerrier en entraînement. Les Shoguns se préparent pour la guerre et ont assignés les meilleurs de la génération d’aînés en tant que mentors pour leur art sanglant. De nombreux sont durs et impitoyables, mais on parle d’un qui est différent. Un Maître montrant de la compassion pour ses étudiant. Un qui enseigne à travers la gentillesse plutôt que la cruauté.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_83"><![CDATA[Hommes et femmes parlent, et ils parlent d’un secret bourgeonnant du doux Maître. Des murmures du Maître et de l’Étudiant. Personne ne sait qui est l’Étudiant, mais il est un jour arrivé pour s’entraîner sous ce Maître. “L’Étudiant est un épéiste doué”, l’un chuchoterais. “Il a encore beaucoup à apprendre du Maître”, un autre dirait. Tandis que l temps passa, le Maître passa de plus en plus de temps avec l’Étudiant, négligeant ses autres élèves. Puis des lèvres sucrées lâchent des mots parlant de ces deux hommes sous un arbre en fleur, partageant un baiser.]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_84"><![CDATA[Le Quartier des Plaisirs reste calme cette nuit, car une grande tragédie est survenue. Le gentil Maître et ses élèves ont étés massacrés. Des mots trouvés dans de sombres lieux disent que l’Étudiant a disparu, qu’il était peut-être un assassin envoyé pour saboter les plans du Shogun. Peut-être le Maître ne pouvait confronter le fait que son amoureux n’était pas celui qu’il pensait, et cela l’as mené à l’échec. Des murmures parmis les rats crachent des insultes au Maître. Ils parlent de sa faiblesse, qu’il n’est qu’un guerrier honteux, qu’il sera oublié.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_85"><![CDATA[Un secret des plus intéressant as coulé de lèvres nobles. Le Maître n’est pas mort. Ils disent qu’il est revenu des morts, que la blessure crue comme ayant percé son coeur avait manqué. Il supplie aux pieds du Shogun pour sa clémence, mais les seigneurs de guerre ne sont pas si facilement influencés. Le Maître était déjà mort, et son nom terni et déshonoré. Ils ont décrétés que dans sa seconde vie, il doit collecter 666 âmes pour les Shoguns, et uniquement quand cette tâche impossible est complété son nom sera racheté. Que ce soit la vérité ou un mensonge, c’est un secret des plus intrigants.]]></entry>	
	</language>  
  <language id="german">
    <entry id="journal_page_title_82"><![CDATA[The Teacher and the Student (1/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_83"><![CDATA[The Teacher and the Student (2/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_84"><![CDATA[The Teacher and the Student (3/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_85"><![CDATA[The Teacher and the Student (4/4)]]></entry>
	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_82"><![CDATA[Words hang in the air. My courtesans loosen lips and secrets flow like wine from a bottle. There is talk of a new warrior generation being trained. The Shoguns are preparing for war and they have assigned the best of the elder generation as mentors for their bloody art. Many are harsh and unforgiving, but there is talk of a different kind. A Teacher that shows compassion for his students. One that teaches through kindness rather than cruelty.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_83"><![CDATA[Men and women talk, and they speak of a budding secret from the kind Teacher. Whispers of the Teacher and the Student. No one knows who the Student is, but he arrived one day to train under the Teacher. “The Student is a skilled swordsman”, one would whisper. “He has much to learn from the Teacher”, another would say. As time passed, the Teacher would spend more and more time with the Student, neglecting his other pupils. Then, sweetened lips let loose talk of the two seen under a blossom tree, sharing a kiss.]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_84"><![CDATA[The Pleasure District remains quiet tonight, for a great tragedy has arisen. The kind Teacher and his pupils have been slaughtered. Words found in dark places tell that the Student has vanished, that perhaps he was an assassin sent to sabotage the Shoguns’ plans. Perhaps the Teacher could not face that his lover was not who he thought he was, and that his heart led him to failure. Whispers among the rats spit insults at the Teacher. They speak of his weakness, that he is a shameful warrior, that he will be forgotten.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_85"><![CDATA[A most interesting secret has been leaked from noble lips. The Teacher did not die. They speak that he has returned from the dead, that the wound believed to have pierced his heart had actually missed. He begs at the Shoguns’ feet for forgiveness, but the warlords are not so easily swayed. The Teacher had already died, and his name tarnished and shamed. They decree that with his second life, he must collect 666 souls for the Shoguns, and only when this impossible deed is complete will his name be redeemed. Whether it is truth or lie, this is a most intriguing secret indeed.]]></entry>	
	</language>  
  <language id="italian">
    <entry id="journal_page_title_82"><![CDATA[Il Maestro e lo Studente (1/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_83"><![CDATA[Il Maestro e lo Studente (2/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_84"><![CDATA[Il Maestro e lo Studente (3/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_85"><![CDATA[Il Maestro e lo Studente (4/4)]]></entry>
	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_82"><![CDATA[Le parole sono appese in aria. Le mie cortigiane allentano le loro labbra e i segreti circolano come vino da una bottiglia. Si parla di una nuova generazione di guerrieri che si sta formando. Gli Shogun si stanno preparando alla guerra e hanno assegnato ai migliori della generazione più anziana il compito di mentore della loro arte sanguinaria. Molti sono duri e spietati, ma si parla anche di un tipo differente. Un Maestro che mostra compassione per i suoi studenti. Uno che insegna attraverso con la gentilezza anziché con la crudeltà.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_83"><![CDATA[Gli uomini e le donne parlano, e parlano di un giovane segreto riguardo al Maestro gentile. Bisbigli riguardo al Maestro e allo Studente. Nessuno sa chi egli sia, ma è arrivato un giorno per farsi istruire dal Maestro. “Lo Studente è un abile spadaccino”, uno mi ha sussurrato. “Ha molto da imparare dal Maestro”, un altro mi ha detto. Il tempo passa e il Maestro spende sempre più e più tempo con lo studente, ignorando i suoi altri pupilli. Poi, labbra dolci hanno parlato dei due che si son fatti cogliere sotto ad un albero in fiore, durante un bacio appassionato.]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_84"><![CDATA[Il Distretto del Piacere stanotte rimane quiero, poiché una grande tragedia è emersa. Il Maestro gentile e i suoi pupilli sono stati tutti massacrati. Parole trovate in posti bui dicono che lo Studente è svanito, che probabilmente era un assassino mandato a sabotare i piani dello Shogun. Forse il Maestro non riusciva a sopportare che il suo amante non era chi pensava che fosse, e che il suo cuore l’avesse accompagnato al fallimento. I sussurri tra i ratti sputano insulti al Maestro. Parlano della sua debolezza, che è un guerriero deplorevole, che sarà dimenticato.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_85"><![CDATA[Un segreto alquanto interessante è stato trapelato da delle labbra nobili. Il Maestro non è morto. Dicono che è tornato dalla morte, che la ferita che gli avrebbe trafitto il cuore in realtà è andata a vuoto. Lui ha pregato lo Shogun ai suoi piedi, chiedendo pietà e perdono, ma i signori della guerra non sono influenzati così facilmente. Il Maestro è già morto, e il suo nome, perciò, è stato sporcato. Il loro decreto è che con questa seconda vita lui debba raccogliere 666 anime per gli Shogun, e solamente quando questo accordo impossibile sarà completato i suoi peccati saranno assolti. Che ciò sia vero o falso, rimane il fatto che è certamente un segreto alquanto intrigante.]]></entry>	
	</language>  
  <language id="japanese">
    <entry id="journal_page_title_82"><![CDATA[The Teacher and the Student (1/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_83"><![CDATA[The Teacher and the Student (2/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_84"><![CDATA[The Teacher and the Student (3/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_85"><![CDATA[The Teacher and the Student (4/4)]]></entry>
	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_82"><![CDATA[Words hang in the air. My courtesans loosen lips and secrets flow like wine from a bottle. There is talk of a new warrior generation being trained. The Shoguns are preparing for war and they have assigned the best of the elder generation as mentors for their bloody art. Many are harsh and unforgiving, but there is talk of a different kind. A Teacher that shows compassion for his students. One that teaches through kindness rather than cruelty.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_83"><![CDATA[Men and women talk, and they speak of a budding secret from the kind Teacher. Whispers of the Teacher and the Student. No one knows who the Student is, but he arrived one day to train under the Teacher. “The Student is a skilled swordsman”, one would whisper. “He has much to learn from the Teacher”, another would say. As time passed, the Teacher would spend more and more time with the Student, neglecting his other pupils. Then, sweetened lips let loose talk of the two seen under a blossom tree, sharing a kiss.]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_84"><![CDATA[The Pleasure District remains quiet tonight, for a great tragedy has arisen. The kind Teacher and his pupils have been slaughtered. Words found in dark places tell that the Student has vanished, that perhaps he was an assassin sent to sabotage the Shoguns’ plans. Perhaps the Teacher could not face that his lover was not who he thought he was, and that his heart led him to failure. Whispers among the rats spit insults at the Teacher. They speak of his weakness, that he is a shameful warrior, that he will be forgotten.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_85"><![CDATA[A most interesting secret has been leaked from noble lips. The Teacher did not die. They speak that he has returned from the dead, that the wound believed to have pierced his heart had actually missed. He begs at the Shoguns’ feet for forgiveness, but the warlords are not so easily swayed. The Teacher had already died, and his name tarnished and shamed. They decree that with his second life, he must collect 666 souls for the Shoguns, and only when this impossible deed is complete will his name be redeemed. Whether it is truth or lie, this is a most intriguing secret indeed.]]></entry>	
	</language>  
  <language id="koreana">
    <entry id="journal_page_title_82"><![CDATA[스승과 제자 (1/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_83"><![CDATA[스승과 제자 (2/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_84"><![CDATA[스승과 제자 (3/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_85"><![CDATA[스승과 제자 (4/4)]]></entry>
	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_82"><![CDATA[말이 허공에 맴돈다. 창녀들이 나의 입술을 느슨하게 만들고 비밀은 기울어진 술병에 든 술처럼 흐른다. 술병에서 비밀이 청주처럼 흘러 넘친다. 사무라이의 새 시대가 열릴 것이라는 이야기다. 쇼군들은 전쟁 준비를 시작했고, 그들 늙은 세대의 수장은 이 피비린내 나는 예술 활동의 적임자로 임명되었다. 많은 이가 가혹하고 무자비했으나, 모두가 그런 것은 아니었다. 제자에게 동정심을 가르쳐준 스승. 잔학보다는 친절을 구가했던 이가 있었다.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_83"><![CDATA[한 남녀가 이야기한다. 그들의 친절한 스승으로부터 싹튼 비밀에 대해서. 그 은밀한 밀담은 어느 스승과 제자에 관한 것이다. 그 제자가 어디로부터 왔는지는 아무도 모르나, 그는 어느 순간부터 그곳에 있었다. 그저 가르침을 받기 위해 거기 있었다는 듯이.  “그는 정말 탁월한 검사야”, 남자는 속닥거렸다. “사부의 많은 가르침 덕분이지”, 여자가 말을 받았다. 시간은 흘러, 스승은 다른 제자들을 등한시한 채 그 제자하고만 시간을 보내가 시작했다. 그런 뒤, 달콤한 입술이 주고받는 입맞춤과 벚나무 아래로 흩날리는 꽃잎에 감싸인 두 사람이 교차하며, 이야기는 막을 내렸다.]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_84"><![CDATA[매우 커다란 비극이 일어났던 탓으로, 그날 밤의 홍등가는 적막했다. 친절한 스승과 그의 수많은 제자들이 한 날에 모두 살해된 것이다. 암흑 속에서 발견된 단서는 총애를 받던 제자가 사라졌음을 암시했다. 아마도 그는 쇼군의 계획을 방해하기 위해 보낸 암살자였을 것이다. 스승은 자신이 쏟았던 애정이 그릇된 곳을 향하고 있었으며, 그 대상이 자신을 나락으로 이끄리라는 것을 받아들일 수 없었던 모양이다. 더러운 시궁쥐 같은 작자들은 스승에게로의 모욕을 서슴지 않았다. 그들은 스승의 나약함에 대해 부르짖으며 그가 부끄러운 전사고, 얼마 안 가 모두가 그를 잊을 것이라고 말했다.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_85"><![CDATA[고귀한 입술에서 가장 흥미로운 비밀이 새어나왔다. 스승이 죽지 않았다는 것이다. 그들은 그가 죽음으로부터 생환했고, 심장을 관통하여 치명상이라고 믿었던 상처가 실은 빗나간 것이라고 하였다. 그는 쇼군들의 발밑에 비참하게 엎드려 자비를 구걸하였지만, 그들은 흔들리지 않았다. 스승은 이미 죽은 몸이었고, 그의 가문과 이름은 진창에 고꾸라졌다. 그들은 그의 두 번째 생명으로 그가 쇼군을 위해 666개의 영혼들을 수집해야 하며, 이 불가능한 행위가 완성되어야만 그의 이름을 되찾아 주겠다고 선언했다. 이것이 설령 진실이든 거짓이든, 참으로 흥미로운 이야기임에는 변함이 없다.]]></entry>	
	</language>  
  <language id="koreanb">
    <entry id="journal_page_title_82"><![CDATA[스승과 제자 (1/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_83"><![CDATA[스승과 제자 (2/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_84"><![CDATA[스승과 제자 (3/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_85"><![CDATA[스승과 제자 (4/4)]]></entry>
	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_82"><![CDATA[말이 허공에 맴돈다. 창녀들이 나의 입술을 느슨하게 만들고 비밀은 기울어진 술병에 든 술처럼 흐른다. 술병에서 비밀이 청주처럼 흘러 넘친다. 사무라이의 새 시대가 열릴 것이라는 이야기다. 쇼군들은 전쟁 준비를 시작했고, 그들 늙은 세대의 수장은 이 피비린내 나는 예술 활동의 적임자로 임명되었다. 많은 이가 가혹하고 무자비했으나, 모두가 그런 것은 아니었다. 제자에게 동정심을 가르쳐준 스승. 잔학보다는 친절을 구가했던 이가 있었다.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_83"><![CDATA[한 남녀가 이야기한다. 그들의 친절한 스승으로부터 싹튼 비밀에 대해서. 그 은밀한 밀담은 어느 스승과 제자에 관한 것이다. 그 제자가 어디로부터 왔는지는 아무도 모르나, 그는 어느 순간부터 그곳에 있었다. 그저 가르침을 받기 위해 거기 있었다는 듯이.  “그는 정말 탁월한 검사야”, 남자는 속닥거렸다. “사부의 많은 가르침 덕분이지”, 여자가 말을 받았다. 시간은 흘러, 스승은 다른 제자들을 등한시한 채 그 제자하고만 시간을 보내가 시작했다. 그런 뒤, 달콤한 입술이 주고받는 입맞춤과 벚나무 아래로 흩날리는 꽃잎에 감싸인 두 사람이 교차하며, 이야기는 막을 내렸다.]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_84"><![CDATA[매우 커다란 비극이 일어났던 탓으로, 그날 밤의 홍등가는 적막했다. 친절한 스승과 그의 수많은 제자들이 한 날에 모두 살해된 것이다. 암흑 속에서 발견된 단서는 총애를 받던 제자가 사라졌음을 암시했다. 아마도 그는 쇼군의 계획을 방해하기 위해 보낸 암살자였을 것이다. 스승은 자신이 쏟았던 애정이 그릇된 곳을 향하고 있었으며, 그 대상이 자신을 나락으로 이끄리라는 것을 받아들일 수 없었던 모양이다. 더러운 시궁쥐 같은 작자들은 스승에게로의 모욕을 서슴지 않았다. 그들은 스승의 나약함에 대해 부르짖으며 그가 부끄러운 전사고, 얼마 안 가 모두가 그를 잊을 것이라고 말했다.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_85"><![CDATA[고귀한 입술에서 가장 흥미로운 비밀이 새어나왔다. 스승이 죽지 않았다는 것이다. 그들은 그가 죽음으로부터 생환했고, 심장을 관통하여 치명상이라고 믿었던 상처가 실은 빗나간 것이라고 하였다. 그는 쇼군들의 발밑에 비참하게 엎드려 자비를 구걸하였지만, 그들은 흔들리지 않았다. 스승은 이미 죽은 몸이었고, 그의 가문과 이름은 진창에 고꾸라졌다. 그들은 그의 두 번째 생명으로 그가 쇼군을 위해 666개의 영혼들을 수집해야 하며, 이 불가능한 행위가 완성되어야만 그의 이름을 되찾아 주겠다고 선언했다. 이것이 설령 진실이든 거짓이든, 참으로 흥미로운 이야기임에는 변함이 없다.]]></entry>	
  </language>  
  <language id="polish">
    <entry id="journal_page_title_82"><![CDATA[The Teacher and the Student (1/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_83"><![CDATA[The Teacher and the Student (2/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_84"><![CDATA[The Teacher and the Student (3/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_85"><![CDATA[The Teacher and the Student (4/4)]]></entry>
	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_82"><![CDATA[Words hang in the air. My courtesans loosen lips and secrets flow like wine from a bottle. There is talk of a new warrior generation being trained. The Shoguns are preparing for war and they have assigned the best of the elder generation as mentors for their bloody art. Many are harsh and unforgiving, but there is talk of a different kind. A Teacher that shows compassion for his students. One that teaches through kindness rather than cruelty.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_83"><![CDATA[Men and women talk, and they speak of a budding secret from the kind Teacher. Whispers of the Teacher and the Student. No one knows who the Student is, but he arrived one day to train under the Teacher. “The Student is a skilled swordsman”, one would whisper. “He has much to learn from the Teacher”, another would say. As time passed, the Teacher would spend more and more time with the Student, neglecting his other pupils. Then, sweetened lips let loose talk of the two seen under a blossom tree, sharing a kiss.]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_84"><![CDATA[The Pleasure District remains quiet tonight, for a great tragedy has arisen. The kind Teacher and his pupils have been slaughtered. Words found in dark places tell that the Student has vanished, that perhaps he was an assassin sent to sabotage the Shoguns’ plans. Perhaps the Teacher could not face that his lover was not who he thought he was, and that his heart led him to failure. Whispers among the rats spit insults at the Teacher. They speak of his weakness, that he is a shameful warrior, that he will be forgotten.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_85"><![CDATA[A most interesting secret has been leaked from noble lips. The Teacher did not die. They speak that he has returned from the dead, that the wound believed to have pierced his heart had actually missed. He begs at the Shoguns’ feet for forgiveness, but the warlords are not so easily swayed. The Teacher had already died, and his name tarnished and shamed. They decree that with his second life, he must collect 666 souls for the Shoguns, and only when this impossible deed is complete will his name be redeemed. Whether it is truth or lie, this is a most intriguing secret indeed.]]></entry>	
	</language>  
  <language id="russian">
    <entry id="journal_page_title_82"><![CDATA[Учитель и ученик (1/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_83"><![CDATA[Учитель и ученик (2/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_84"><![CDATA[Учитель и ученик (3/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_85"><![CDATA[Учитель и ученик (4/4)]]></entry>
	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_82"><![CDATA[Слова повисают в воздухе. Мои куртизанки расслабляют губы, и секреты текут, как вино из бутылки. Поговаривают о подготовке нового поколения воинов. Сегуны готовятся к войне, и они назначили лучших из старшего поколения наставников для своего кровавого искусства. Многие из них суровы и неумолимы, но слухи ходят о другом. Об учителе, который проявляет сострадание к своим ученикам. Тот, который учит добротой, а не жестокостью.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_83"><![CDATA[Среди народа ходят слухи о секрете доброго учителя и его ученике. Никто не знает, кто этот ученик, но однажды он приехал тренироваться под руководством учителя. "Ученик - искусный фехтовальщик", - шептал один. Он должен многому научиться у учителя", - говорил другой. Со временем учитель проводил все больше времени с этим учеником, пренебрегая другими. Затем сладкие губы заговорили о тех двух целующихся, которых видели под цветущим деревом.]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_84"><![CDATA[В районе развлечений сегодня тихо, потому что произошла большая трагедия. Добрый учитель и его ученики были убиты. Слухи говорят о том, что ученик исчез, и что, возможно, он и был убийцей, посланным сорвать планы сегунов. Возможно также и то, учитель не мог смириться с тем, что его возлюбленный не тот, за кого себя выдает, и что его сердце ведет его к неудаче. Шепот среди крыс плевался оскорблениями в адрес учителя. Они говорят о его слабости, о том, что он позорный воин, что о нем забудут.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_85"><![CDATA[Из благородных уст просочилась самая интересная тайна. Учитель не умер. Они говорят, что он воскрес из мертвых, что катана, которая, как полагают, пронзила его сердце, на самом деле не достигла цели. Он молит у ног сегунов о прощении, но военачальников не так-то легко переубедить. Учитель уже умер, и его имя запятнано и опозорено. Они постановляют, что со своей второй жизнью он должен собрать 666 душ для сегунов, и только когда это невозможное дело будет завершено, его имя будет искуплено. Правда это или ложь, но это действительно самая интригующая тайна.]]></entry>	
	</language>  	
  <language id="schinese">
    <entry id="journal_page_title_82"><![CDATA[The Teacher and the Student (1/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_83"><![CDATA[The Teacher and the Student (2/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_84"><![CDATA[The Teacher and the Student (3/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_85"><![CDATA[The Teacher and the Student (4/4)]]></entry>
	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_82"><![CDATA[Words hang in the air. My courtesans loosen lips and secrets flow like wine from a bottle. There is talk of a new warrior generation being trained. The Shoguns are preparing for war and they have assigned the best of the elder generation as mentors for their bloody art. Many are harsh and unforgiving, but there is talk of a different kind. A Teacher that shows compassion for his students. One that teaches through kindness rather than cruelty.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_83"><![CDATA[Men and women talk, and they speak of a budding secret from the kind Teacher. Whispers of the Teacher and the Student. No one knows who the Student is, but he arrived one day to train under the Teacher. “The Student is a skilled swordsman”, one would whisper. “He has much to learn from the Teacher”, another would say. As time passed, the Teacher would spend more and more time with the Student, neglecting his other pupils. Then, sweetened lips let loose talk of the two seen under a blossom tree, sharing a kiss.]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_84"><![CDATA[The Pleasure District remains quiet tonight, for a great tragedy has arisen. The kind Teacher and his pupils have been slaughtered. Words found in dark places tell that the Student has vanished, that perhaps he was an assassin sent to sabotage the Shoguns’ plans. Perhaps the Teacher could not face that his lover was not who he thought he was, and that his heart led him to failure. Whispers among the rats spit insults at the Teacher. They speak of his weakness, that he is a shameful warrior, that he will be forgotten.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_85"><![CDATA[A most interesting secret has been leaked from noble lips. The Teacher did not die. They speak that he has returned from the dead, that the wound believed to have pierced his heart had actually missed. He begs at the Shoguns’ feet for forgiveness, but the warlords are not so easily swayed. The Teacher had already died, and his name tarnished and shamed. They decree that with his second life, he must collect 666 souls for the Shoguns, and only when this impossible deed is complete will his name be redeemed. Whether it is truth or lie, this is a most intriguing secret indeed.]]></entry>	
	</language>  
  <language id="spanish">
    <entry id="journal_page_title_82"><![CDATA[El maestro y el estudiant (1/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_83"><![CDATA[El maestro y el estudiant (2/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_84"><![CDATA[El maestro y el estudiant (3/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_85"><![CDATA[El maestro y el estudiant (4/4)]]></entry>
	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_82"><![CDATA[Las palabras tensan el ambiente. Mis  cortesanos hablan demasiado y los secretos fluyen como el vino de arroz desde una botella. Se habla de que se está entrenando una nueva generación de guerreros. Los Sogún se están preparando para la guerra y han asignado a los mejores guerreros veteranos de la anterior generación como mentores de su sangriento arte. Muchos son duros y despiadados, pero se habla de uno diferente. Un maestro que muestra compasión por sus estudiantes. Uno que enseña a través de la bondad en vez de la crueldad.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_83"><![CDATA[Hombres y mujeres hablan, y cuentan un secreto incipiente sobre el buen maestro. Susurros sobre el maestro y el estudiante. Nadie sabe quién es el estudiante, pero un día llegó para que le entrenara el maestro. “El estudiante es un espadachín habilidoso”, susurró uno. “Aún tiene mucho que aprender del maestro”, dijo otro. A medida que pasaba el tiempo, el maestro pasaba más y más tiempo con el estudiante, descuidando a sus demás pupilos. Entonces, labios endulzados relajaron la charla entre los dos bajo un almendro florecido, compartiendo un beso.]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_84"><![CDATA[El distrito del placer permanece tranquilo esta noche, a pesar de la gran tragedia que ha ocurrido. El buen maestro y sus pupilos han sido masacrados. Dicen las malas lenguas que el estudiante se ha desvanecido, que probablemente era un asesino enviado para sabotear los planes de los Sogunes. Puede que el maestro no pudiera enfrentar que su amante no era quien el creía, y su corazón le llevó al fracaso. Susurros de las ratas que insultan al maestro. Hablan de su debilidad, de que es un guerrero vergonzoso, que será olvidado.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_85"><![CDATA[Un secreto mucho más interesante se ha filtrado de la boca de los nobles. El maestro no murió. Hablan de que volvió de entre los muertos, que la herida que supuestamente le había atravesado el corazón, en realidad, no lo hizo. Suplicó clemencia a los pies de los Sogunes, pero no es fácil convencer a un señor de la guerra. El maestro murió, y su nombre fue mancillado y deshonrado. Han decretado que para su segunda vida, debe recolectar 666 almas para los Sogunes, y solo cuando esta imposible labor sea completada su nombre será redimido. Si es verdad o mentira es el mayor secreto, por supuesto.]]></entry>	
	</language>  
  <language id="tchinese">
    <entry id="journal_page_title_82"><![CDATA[The Teacher and the Student (1/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_83"><![CDATA[The Teacher and the Student (2/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_84"><![CDATA[The Teacher and the Student (3/4)]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_title_85"><![CDATA[The Teacher and the Student (4/4)]]></entry>
	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_82"><![CDATA[Words hang in the air. My courtesans loosen lips and secrets flow like wine from a bottle. There is talk of a new warrior generation being trained. The Shoguns are preparing for war and they have assigned the best of the elder generation as mentors for their bloody art. Many are harsh and unforgiving, but there is talk of a different kind. A Teacher that shows compassion for his students. One that teaches through kindness rather than cruelty.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_83"><![CDATA[Men and women talk, and they speak of a budding secret from the kind Teacher. Whispers of the Teacher and the Student. No one knows who the Student is, but he arrived one day to train under the Teacher. “The Student is a skilled swordsman”, one would whisper. “He has much to learn from the Teacher”, another would say. As time passed, the Teacher would spend more and more time with the Student, neglecting his other pupils. Then, sweetened lips let loose talk of the two seen under a blossom tree, sharing a kiss.]]></entry>
    <entry id="journal_page_text_84"><![CDATA[The Pleasure District remains quiet tonight, for a great tragedy has arisen. The kind Teacher and his pupils have been slaughtered. Words found in dark places tell that the Student has vanished, that perhaps he was an assassin sent to sabotage the Shoguns’ plans. Perhaps the Teacher could not face that his lover was not who he thought he was, and that his heart led him to failure. Whispers among the rats spit insults at the Teacher. They speak of his weakness, that he is a shameful warrior, that he will be forgotten.]]></entry>	
    <entry id="journal_page_text_85"><![CDATA[A most interesting secret has been leaked from noble lips. The Teacher did not die. They speak that he has returned from the dead, that the wound believed to have pierced his heart had actually missed. He begs at the Shoguns’ feet for forgiveness, but the warlords are not so easily swayed. The Teacher had already died, and his name tarnished and shamed. They decree that with his second life, he must collect 666 souls for the Shoguns, and only when this impossible deed is complete will his name be redeemed. Whether it is truth or lie, this is a most intriguing secret indeed.]]></entry>	
	</language>  	
 
</root>

