<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>D:/Hoang/Mod Steam/Guts class mod final/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>Guts the Black Swordman - Class Mod</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>public</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>1</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>9</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>0</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>New Class</Tags>
		<Tags>Berserk</Tags>
		<Tags>Guts</Tags>
		<Tags>Swordman</Tags>
		<Tags>Dragonslayer</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>
[h1]THE BLACK SWORDMAN CLASS MOD[/h1]

Support Color of Madness: Yes.
Support Crimson Court: Yes.
Mod Version: 1.9
Language: English, Russian, French, Chinese.

[h1]RECOMMENDATION[/h1]

Skull Knight skin by NumbBears:
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1298595390

[h1]CLASS INTRODUCTION[/h1]

This class mod based upon Guts, the main anti-hero protagonist of Berserk (by Kentaro Miura) who carries the names &quot;Hungred Man Slayer&quot; and &quot;The Black Swordman&quot;. He is introduced as a wanderer with a grudge, bent on hunting down and slaying the beings known as Apostles with a gigantic sword known as the Dragonslayer.

The idea itself is to build Guts as a warrior class mod with high damage output abilities, can be used as a semi-tanker and main dps of the team. However, to use him effectively, you have to manage his stress.

[h1]BASIC STATS[/h1]

[b]Resistances[/b]
stun 60% poison 30% bleed 30% disease 20% move 30% 
debuff 10% death_blow 75% trap 10%

[h1]COMBAT SKILLS[/h1]
	
[b]Chop[/b]
(xxOO - OOxx)
The Blackswordman chops the enemy with a chance of decrease his stress.

[b]Slash[/b]
(xxOO - O~Oxx)
The Blackswordman swing his huge Dragonslayer, slash enemies with a chance of decrease his stress.	

[b]Repeated Crossbow[/b]
(OOOx - xO~O~O)
The Blackswordman shoots enemies with his crossbow, dealing extra damage to marked enemies. However, he receives dodge debuff and protection debuff.

[b]Rage[/b]
(Limited 1 per battle)
(Self cast)
The rage bursts out of the Blackswordman, gives him additional protection and additional resistances against debuff and move but self marked target. 

[b]Brand of Sacrifice[/b]
(Self cast)
With the cost of stress and self mark target, the Blackswordman heals himself and apply riposte effect.

[b]Cannon Arm[/b]
(Limited 1 per battle)
(OOOx - OOOO)
The Blackswordman uses the cannon from his steel left-arm, receives additional speed buff, crit buff. His massive explosion ignores protection, dealing extra damage and decrease his own stress. However, the Blackswordman receives self mark target.

[h1]CAMPING SKILLS[/h1]

[b]Maintain Equipment[/b] cost 4, self only, +15% PROT (4 battles) +15% DMG (4 battles).
[b]Night Moves[/b] cost 2, self only, +20% Scouting Chances.
[b]Bandit&apos;s Senses[/b] cost 4, self only, prevent nightime ambush, -20% chance party suprised (4 battles), +20% chance monster suprised (4 battles).
[b]Quarantine[/b] cost 3, self only, suffer 30% HP DMG, 50% chance - 20 stress, 50% chance -15 stress

[h1]UNIQUE TRINKETS[/h1]

[b]Throwing Knife[/b]
(Common)
+ 8 ACC. 
+ 4% CRIT.

[b]Miniature Bomb[/b]
(Uncommon)
+ 10% Armor piercing.
+ 5% DMG.

[b]Badge of the Falcon[/b]
(Rare)
+ 10 ACC.
+ 10% DMG.
- 3 stress/hit.

[b]Puck[/b]
(Rare)
+ 6 SPD.
+ 50% Healing Received.
+ 50% Stress Healing Received.
+ 3% PROT.

[b]Berserker Armor[/b]
(Very rare)
+ 60% DMG (melee only).
+ 4 SPD.
+ 4% CRIT.
+ 10% PROT.
+ 10% DEF.
- 50% bleed resist.
- 2hp/hit.

[b]Behelit[/b]
(Very rare)
+ 10% deathblow resist.
+ 20% def.
+ 20% prot.
+ 2 stress/hit.

[h1]CoM TRINKET[/h1]

[b]Vengeful Spirit[/b]
(160 shards)
+ 2 SPD
+ 10% DMG
+ 10% DMG vs Husk
+ 20% DMG vs Eldritch
+ 50% Armour Piercing.
Self: attacks +3 stress on hit.

[h1]THANK YOU![/h1]

Thanks yddgra for supportive ideal about combat skills.
All new art assets reworked and enhanced by RAiDEN2142.

If you find any bugs/glitches or spelling errors please let me know in the comment section below.
All the positive feedback is really encouraging.

[h1]CHANGELOG[/h1]

1.9 combine town event, com trinket.
1.8c arts reworked by RAiDEN2142, fix fx bug, add french, russian, chinese language support, add new trinkets. 
1.8b add chance of reduce stress to chop and slash.
1.8a add town event dialogue + hotfix animation.
1.7 fix camping trainner dialogue + balance stats.
1.6 fix crash when upgrading armors + weapons.
1.5 fix all crash errors (caused by new skills); change icon, effects and skill sounds.
1.4 rework and improve arts; rework skills.
1.3 fix camping skill error.
1.2 fix audio error.</ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>1425243237</PublishedFileId>
</project>

