<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>E:/ProjectAndStuff/Darkest Dungeon Mods/Mods/Trinket Variety Project/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>Trinket Variety Project</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails>
		Updated Loc for other languages
	</UpdateDetails>
	<Visibility>public</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>1</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>1</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>0</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>Trinket</Tags>
		<Tags>Trinkets</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>
		Welcome to Trinket Variety Project. A mod aiming to bring more variety in the trinkets you can find when playing.
		The goal was to add more universal trinkets since some class mods lack interesting trinkets.
		
		[h1]Features[/h1]
		- 170 trinkets for you to collect
		- Craftable trinkets. Collect Unidentified weapons and use them on a curio in the Hamlet to create weapons trinkets with Enchantements and Traits
		- Collect powerful Lost Relics by going on a though missio. These are aimed at the late game
		- New quest in the Cove where you collect lost shipments which have a chance to give Enchanted Trinkets or Unidentified Weapons
		- Brigand Scavenger that drops Unidentfied Weapons if you manage to kill him quickly enough
		- Class Equipments for vanilla + dlc classes that aim to make less interesting skills viable and make interesting builds (atleast 2 per class)
	
		[h1]Trinket Damage Types[/h1]
		You will notice that some of the trinkets have damage of a certain type like &apos;Fire&apos;.
		Each damage type gives a hidden damage boost based on a condition.
		Below are all the current damage types:
		
		- FIRE: 10% more damage vs Beast
		- LIGHT: 10% more damage if torch above 50
		- SHARP: 10% more damage vs Bleeding
		- TOXIC: 10% more damage vs Man
		- MAGIC: 10% more damage vs Eldritch
		- DARK: 10% more damage if torch below 50
		- HOLY: 10% more damage vs Unholy
		- POISON: 10% more damage vs Blighted
		
		I added these damage types mostly for asthetic reasons as it looks nice on the tooltip xD.
		
		[h1]Synergies[/h1]
		[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1434005342]Monster Variety Project[/url]
		If you use both mods then you get the following things:
		- Ambusher on Relic quest can be one of the mini-bosses of Monster Variety
		- Some monsters from Monster Variety have chance to drop Unidentfied Weapons
		
		[h1]Moonlit Dungeon[/h1]
		Come by the [url=https://discord.gg/VkXB87M]Moonlit Dungeon Discord[/url], 
		the modding hub for Darkest Dungeon and the best place to see previews of upcoming mods, 
		learn to mod, find artists and animators, beta test mods, give feedback to mod authors 
		or generally hang out and talk about DD!
		
		[h1]Donation[/h1]
		If you like what I do and want to support me you are free to donate some cents to me using the paypal link below.
		My mods will always be free and you should in no way feel obliged to donate. 
		
		[url=https://www.paypal.me/JensSels]Donate via PayPal[/url]
	</ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>1882264198</PublishedFileId>
</project>

