<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>C:/Users/Vivian (Juni)/Desktop/Darkest Dungeon Mods/MAMBO/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>The Mambo Hero Class mod </Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>public</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>1</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>0</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>0</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>class mod</Tags>
		<Tags>new hero</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>[i]The Voodoo That You Do...[/i]

[b]Backstory
------------------------------------------[/b]

&quot;A mysterious and regal looking woman in humble clothing has arrived at the Hamlet. She claims that during a ritual, her Loa brought her a vision of a human face being enveloped in a mutilating annihilation. They have guided her here to heal this festering sore, she proclaims. And she’s not alone either. She has a pitch-black rooster in tow, which she believes to be the vessel of her late husband&apos;s soul. She may have come from low stature due to discrimination, but through the faith of her gods and cunning wit, she commands the respect of a queen.&quot; [i] - The Ancestor[/i]

[b]Role &amp; Abilities 
------------------------------------------[/b]

The Mambo is a Stress-Relieving, Enemy De-buffing Support Hero.

What she lacks in damage she makes up for in group-viability and longevity.

[u]Papa Ghede’s Blessing[/u]  -  Use: OOOX [b]I[/b] Target: XXXX
[img]https://i.imgur.com/DiO1CTu.png[/img]

[i] Let the power of the Loa heal your mind...[/i]

A simple group stress heal, [b]excluding the Mambo herself.[/b] 

[u]You Dare?![/u]  -  Use: XOOO [b]I[/b] Target: OOOO
[img]https://i.imgur.com/UieHR1J.png[/img]

[i] How dare you attack the Great Mam’zelle![/i]

Verbal ranged attack w/ debuff to target’s damage plus lowers Stun resist.

[u]Baron Samedi’s Tobacco[/u]  -  Use: XOOO [b]I[/b] Target: OOOX
[img]https://i.imgur.com/aOqG1uu.png[/img]

[i] Baron Samedi&apos;s vices must be indulged...[/i]

Ranged blight attack w/ DODGE debuff

[u] Papa Legba’s Shadow[/u]  -  Use: XOOX [b]I[/b] Target: XXXX
[img]https://i.imgur.com/3UcRFMt.png[/img]

[i] Papa Legba will protect you from the Crossroads![/i]

A guard ability where the [u]entire group[/u] is guarded by her and by a Papa Legba sprite for 2 rounds and can only be used twice per battle. The more stressed she has the more PROT she has upon activation of the ability. She does, however, gain an uncurable Horror 2 rounds after the guard duration is over.


[u] Husband’s Embrace[/u]  -  Use: OOOX [b]I[/b] Target: XXXX
[img]https://i.imgur.com/30bPBR3.png[/img]

[i] Mon cher, Christophe…[/i]

Maire hugs her [strike]husband[/strike] rooster, Christophe Glapion for a self-heal and stress-heal

[u] Baron Kriminel’s Whip[/u]  -  Use: OOOX [b]I[/b] Target: OOOO
[img]https://i.imgur.com/WZBsgWb.png[/img]

[i] Baron Kriminel knows what lies in your hearts![/i]

Marie’s shadow whips a single target enemy. +15% DMG vs Eldritch

[u] A Little Pinprick[/u]  -  Use: OOOX [b]I[/b] Target: XXXX
[img]https://i.imgur.com/LNS1fHu.png[/img]

[i] You must give to get, it’s the law of things.[/i]

Marie stabs herself with a dagger which removes a small portion of health and a possibility of Bleed DoT, but gives a single group member substantial stress relief and minor stress buff. Mambo also receives a healing buff for 2 rounds. [b]Mambo herself cannot be a selected recipient of the single stress heal.[/b]

[b]Camping Skills
------------------------------------------[/b]

[u]When the Rooster Crows[/u]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/YSaPbaI.png[/img]
Time Cost: 4

[i]Wake us if you see somethin’, mon cher...[/i]

Effect: No chance of surprise ambush while camping, 15% chance of surprising enemies (4 battles) and 10% PROT to all companions (2 battles)

[u]Gumbo Zabe[/u]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/emHH80i.png[/img]
Time Cost: 4

[i]This here is my Mama’s gumbo, you gon’ have the best sleep of yo’ life.[/i]

Effect:  -15 stress relief (party), +10% health raise (party), +10% stress healing received and -2 ACC for next 4 battles (party)

[u]Lucky Feather[/u]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/8T0qKxL.png[/img]
Time Cost: 2

[i]“SQUAK!”
“Oh quit yo’ fussin’, it’s just one feather.”
[/i]

Effect: Gives one companion (Mambo, herself cannot be selected) +15 DODGE &amp; +15% chance of virtue for 4 battles.

[u]Lemme Do Yo’ Hair[/u]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/clbxLuX.png[/img]
Time Cost: 3

[i]People always be surprised that I used to be a hairdresser.[/i]

Effect: +5 ACC to a single companion, removes morality debuff from Marie and gives her -10 stress relief.

[b]Other Information
------------------------------------------[/b]

~ Mambo is not religious 
~ Provisions: Medicinal Herbs 
~ District: Outside Bonfire
~ [u]Two Mambos cannot be paired together in one party[/u]
~ Mambo comes with 5 new custom Quirks: Mystic, Bokor, Inquisitor, Loa Possessed, &amp; Samedi&apos;s Plaything
~ She is inspired by Marie Laveau and my paternal great-great-grandmother, Ma Mazey
~ Her canon default name is Marie
~ Crit Buff: +40% stress healing received
~ This mod comes with 10 class specific trinkets for Mambo: 2 common, 1 uncommon, 1 rare, 1 very rare, 2 Crimson Court and 1 Color of Madness
~ She has a town event so you can get one immediately
~ This mod is fully compatible with all 3 DLCs
~ Mambo currently only supports English translation but please message me if you wish to include your language in localization! 

[b]Credits
------------------------------------------[/b]

~Concept Art/Main Art Assets: [url=https://www.artstation.com/ti-rex]Vladimir Slobtsov[/url]
~Addtional Art Assets: [url=https://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561197984892423]Muscarine[/url]
~Coders: [url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/shaylockholmes]Shay[/url], [url=https://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198143986901]Sasiji[/url], [url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/TheHolyChicken]The Holy Chicken[/url],
[url=https://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198049787407]Smarmy Mormon Jesus[/url] 
~Animators: [url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/Anonymous_Koala]Anonymous_Koala[/url],
[url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/slightlystartled]Slightly Startled Seal[/url],
[url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/AnActualBirdIRL] An Actual Bird[/url]
~ Additional Help: [url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/onimare]O&apos;Nightmare[/url]
~Playtesters: [url=https://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198143986901]Sasiji[/url],
[url=https://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198049787407]Smarmy Mormon Jesus[/url] 
~Localization: 

Special thanks to [url=https://www.twitch.tv/elementfive]ElementFive[/url] for promoting the mod via his Twitter and his Twitch channel, as well as [url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/TPLuna]Clair de Lune[/url] and everyone else on the [url=https://discordapp.com/invite/VkXB87M]Moonlit Dungeon Discord server[/url] who helped with bug fixing and general feedback as the mod developed. None of this would have been possible without any of you guys!

Mambo is, by no means, my last Darkest Dungeon mod and they will always remain 100% free. However, if you&apos;d like to help with the process, see the mods done quicker, or leave me a nice kudos; please consider leaving a tip! It would mean the world and really help out a novice (but hopefully upcoming) gamedev! 

[url=https://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_s-xclick&amp;hosted_button_id=MBP3LA2EGH4GS&amp;source=url][img]https://i.imgur.com/k53FXKP.gif[/img][/url]
 
[b]Legal Stuff
------------------------------------------[/b]
This item and its content are not authorized for posting on Steam, except under this Steam account. This mod is not an official Red Hook product. Darkest Dungeon and everything Darkest Dungeon related is entirely the property of Red Hook Studios. Red Hook is not responsible if this mod ends up damaging your game.</ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>1865154690</PublishedFileId>
</project>

