<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>c:/my_mods/barbarian/data/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>The Barbarian: by Ahmonza</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>private</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>0</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>0</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>0</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags/>
		<Tags>Character Mod</Tags>
		<Tags>Class Mod</Tags>
		<Tags>New Class</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>He was born in an age of doom, a time when the first of men had found fire and made it a slave. This Promethean action had angered the first masters of fire. The first of men went to war with these Titans of might and fury. Man progressed to steal, mastered fire, and only the strongest of those fire breathing beast remained. The Barbarian now a young man sought out that wrathful Dragon. He engaged in a bloody fight with the beast. When that foal worm laid dead before his feet, he took its blood into himself and with it, a deep wrathful abyssal power. The power that made those old master of fire enlighten, long lived and strong, has now become the Barbarian. The knowledge of power has made the Barbarian hungry for more. Seeking greater strength he finds him in the Hamlet, its so close now he can smell it.

?(Smith)Though he may seem to be a simple savage, his mind is full of logic and fascination. Consistently in a state of thought plotting of ways to obliterating his foes. His blade, a product of his own design, meant to cleanly cut flesh from bone with one swift swing. His armor, for what is lacks in protection it compensates through its mobility

(Guild)?A mad man, powerful, chaotic, and yet somehow balanced in his mind. This war hunting wanderer seeks only the most terrible things to slay, that be a man, beast or cosmic horror. He gets up close to his enemies in order to inflict unimaginable destruction. With stone like flesh he can take what he can dish out. However the true power of this savage is his madness, too summon an old power that changes the very nature of his body and mind. A prehistoric abyss full of rage.

(survival)?He never drinks, he never eats, he never sleeps, or at the very least no living man or woman has seen him done so. Whatever keeps him going, keeps him alive is beyond any science we hold here.

?(town event)A strange man from the west, has come to the estate. He claims to be on a quest to dismantle the the abhorrent and ancient powers that haunt this forsaken place. He has been seen standing in front of the manor with his gaze transfixed on the lower floors. This man has not moved from that spot for seven days, and has been aggressively demanding entry. The people of the Hamlet fear him and want him gone, yet he may be of some use.

(shout out to &quot;Anonymous_Koala&quot; on the darkest dungeon discord: he help me change the size of the Barbarian)
(shout out to &quot;Edatlantic&quot; for Portuguese translation)
(shout out to &quot;Branch&quot; for Russian translation)
(shout out to &quot;SoulSmile for helping me with the sound bank)
(shout out to &quot;Metalocif&quot; for some grammers fixes on the English LOC)

the barbarian is heavy brawler type
there are two ways to play the barbarian either as a meat shield for your party or a heavy hitting glass cannon
hes best played in the front and 2nd rank
his skills reflect a force of nature that is like the melee equivalent of the Occultist

1:?his first skill &quot;Carve&quot; is a basic melee attack that can be used from the 1st and 2nd and can hit the 1st or 2nd

2:?the skill &quot;Sunder&quot; is a melee attacked that pushes the targets back can be used from 1st and 2nd and will hit the both the 1st and 2nd (will ignore prot)

3:?&quot;Cleave&quot; is a melee that can hit all targets at once, can be used from the 1st or 2nd rank /damage and ACC is low but all targets have a chance for bleed and shuffle

4:&quot;Claw&quot; is a reaching melee attack that pulls a target up front and moves the barbarian forward (moves one) while adding a weak reposte. can be used from the 1st rank only and can hit the 2nd,3rd, or 4th rank but the barbarian will pay a small blood price and mark himself?

5:?&quot;trample&quot; will lunch the barbarian from the back row (move 3 forward) and stun its target with low damage . can be used from the 3rd and 4th ranks and can hit the 1st, 2nd or 3rd


6:?&quot;Rage&quot; is dangerous to use you can gain a damage, Acc, speed, has a small change for weak regen and adds a strong reposte. but there is a heavy blood price (8 damage for level one)(24 damage for level 6) and a chance for bleed. this skill can only be used when Hp is below 75% and can be used from 1st,2nd and 3rd rank

7:?&quot;Iron Flesh&quot; is a defensive skill, it will add protection, one block and a weak stress heal. however there&apos;s a chance for blight and it marks himself. it can only be used when Hp is above 75% and from any rank

he gains passive buffs when low on HP

abusive. powerful. paranoid. courageous are the only stress states he can get
the lower his HP the more damage he can do but unlike most heroes, death is more eager to take if it has the chance.

Note(if you have a mod hero of the same name there&apos;s no need to worry you can still play both heroes in the same game)!)!</ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>1686591937</PublishedFileId>
</project>

