<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>C:/Users/Sean/Desktop/Darkest Dungeon Mods/Warden of the North/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>Warden of the North</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>public</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>1</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>0</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>1</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>New Class</Tags>
		<Tags>Game of Thrones</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>[i]The man who passes the sentence should swing the sword. If you would take a man&apos;s life, you owe it to him to look into his eyes and hear his final words. And if you cannot bear to do that, then perhaps the man does not deserve to die. [/i]

[h1]Theme[/h1]

The intention of this class was to stay reasonably close to vanilla Darkest Dungeon, but provide a chassis for Eddard Stark from A Song of Ice and Fire. He is a commander, guardian, and marks damage dealer. He also comes with a new district, the Weirwood Tree. To avoid cluttering people&apos;s districts, there is a separate link here: (Coming Soon)

[h1]Art[/h1]

Jezamine Tan drew the Warden! She did a phenomenal job, and you can find more of her work in the links below:

Instagram :  https://www.instagram.com/jezamine_tan/
Twitter :https://twitter.com/jezaminetan
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/artofjezaminetan/
DeviantArt: https://jezart12.deviantart.com/

[h1]Abilities[/h1]

1) Indictment: The Warden strikes at an enemy, doing half damage but marking an enemy.

2) Execution Sentence: The Warden slashes an enemy&apos;s neck. Bonus damage and accuracy to marked targets.

3) Call Direwolf: The Warden summons a direwolf to attack any singular enemy. Decent damage with a bleed.

4) Rally Bannermen: The Warden leads allies with his house banner, granting good stress resistance and accuracy. Several trinkets affect &amp; add to this ability.

5) Honor: True to his word, the Warden guards his allies. Special synergy with the Hand of the King trinket.

6) Prayer: The Warden prays to the Old Gods, regaining health &amp; healing stress.

7) Leadership: The Warden commands his allies to attack a marked target. Grants all allies damage vs marked targets, speed while guarded, and crit chance.

[h1] Trinkets [/h1]

1) Northern Armor: At the cost of some damage, grants some protection &amp; health.

2) Hand of the King: When guarding, provides good protection.

3) Weirwood Branch: Extra healing &amp; stress healing received.

4) Ned&apos;s Head: Huge stress damage received for lots of crit against marked targets.

5) Dawn, Sword of the Morning: Grants riposte on friendly effects. Minor dodge when riposting.

6) Ice: Grants damage. Armor pen on marked targets. More stress received.

7) War-Bred Direwolf: Direwolf damage increased.

8) Weathered Sigil: % chance to heal allies&apos; stress. Minor stress resist on holder.

Crimson Court Trinkets:

CC1) Walking Stick: Speed &amp; move resistance reduction, damage reduction, but massive virtue chance when above 75% health.

CC2) King&apos;s Final Letter: MASSIVE stress damage taken. Effect: Friendly actions give +1% crit and +1% prot until camp.

CC Set Bonus: 30% health bonus.

[h1]Camp Skills[/h1]

1) War Stories: The Warden shares stories from his military life. Useable up to 6 times at 1 point cost. Grants a % chance of several buffs &amp; stress damage. 

2) The Pointy End: The Warden gives his allies accuracy and critical chance as he instructs them how to use a blade.

3) Winter is Coming: The Warden warns of winter, increasing scouting chance and perhaps causing stress damage.

4) Experienced Commander: The Warden grants everyone damage against marked targets.

[h1] Future Plans [/h1]

The Arcanist will be the next class. Whereas this one is very vanilla-oriented, Arcanist will be radically different. 3 stances.

[h1] Known Issues [/h1]

None known at the moment.

[h1] Final Thoughts [/h1]

I&apos;m finished with front-liners. I&apos;m more interested in making support characters. The Arcanist will double as a support &amp; set-up damage-dealer, and it will be radically different than vanilla.</ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>1709484026</PublishedFileId>
</project>

