<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>C:/Users/Sean/Desktop/Darkest Dungeon Mods/Arcanist/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>Arcanist</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>public</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>1</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>0</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>0</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>New Class</Tags>
		<Tags>Mage</Tags>
		<Tags>WoW</Tags>
		<Tags>Utility</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>

[h1] Class Introduction:[/h1]
The Arcanist is a mage with a tragic past. He is strictly a utility/set-up damage class. He relies upon crits and Frost Nova to activate his full damage potential.

[h1] Arcanist Comic:[/h1]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/w5J5wrb.png[/img]

[h1]Credit:[/h1] Jezamine Tan drew this character, and I think she did a fantastic job. Here&apos;s a link to more of her work: https://www.deviantart.com/jezart12

A Slightly Startled Seal really renewed vigor for this project by helping with some custom animations. Thank you, buddy! Check out his Sunward Isles dungeon mod. Aside from being incredible, it holds an Arcanist trinket!

https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1689234891

[h1] Combat Skills: [/h1]

[b]Crit effect: Ignite[/b]: Gain minor torchlight and extra damage. Can stack with each crit.

[b]Frostfire Bolt:[/b] 
[img]https://i.imgur.com/OhnFWG9.png[/img]

Used from any rank. Hits any rank. Costs 6 torchlight. 75+ torchlight strengthens the fire aspect, giving extra damage. Torchlight equal to or less than 25 strengthens the frost aspect, granting armor pen.

[b]Dragon&apos;s Breath:[/b] 
[img]https://i.imgur.com/DIFjFU0.png[/img]

Used from ranks 1, 2. Hits the first 2 enemies. This fire spell benefits from higher torch, gaining extra damage and stun chance. With or without the torch, it shuffles enemies. It loses 50% stun chance in the Farm or Courtyard.

[b]Frost Nova:[/b] 
[img]https://i.imgur.com/aLB6mnK.png[/img]

Used from ranks 1, 2, or 3. This spell freezes and immobilizes enemies. It also destealths them, and increases crit received. Gain damage when shattering enemies with an attack.

[b]Decurse:[/b] 
[img]https://i.imgur.com/03rY9rB.png[/img]

Used from any rank. Cleanses targets of debuffs. Each rank gains a new cleanse effect (stun, mark, bleed, blight).

[b]Invisibility:[/b] 
[img]https://i.imgur.com/Abn06QX.png[/img]

Used from any rank. The Arcanist turns invisible. Any ability breaks stealth. Gains a buff to damage while stealthed.

[b]Time Warp:[/b] 
[img]https://i.imgur.com/ORy5kBP.png[/img]

Used from any rank. Grants all party members immense speed for 4 turns. Grants a chance to add another turn.

[b]Arcane Knowledge:[/b] 
[img]https://i.imgur.com/6ZDRzd0.png[/img]

This changes stances from Arcane to Elementalist. When changing to Elementalist stance, gain a multiplier to crit chance. It lasts 3 additional turns. When changing to Arcane stance, gain some dodge. Lasts 3 additional turns.

[b]Blink[/b]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/AMNj2ed.png[/img]

Move is replaced with Blink. Blink can be used twice per turn to teleport away from enemies. One space per use. Free action.

[h1]Camp Skills:[/h1]

In addition to the normal camp skills, the Arcanist has...

[b]Conjure Refreshments:[/b] 
[img]https://i.imgur.com/UpXjEzy.png[/img] 

The Arcanist summons provisions. Croissants, specifically.

[b]Combustion:[/b] 
[img]https://i.imgur.com/nr8SDtn.png[/img]

The Arcanist gains large crit chance on the first turn of combat.

[b]Arcane Intellect:[/b] 
[img]https://i.imgur.com/IVW2IXh.png[/img]

The Arcanist grants stealth-sight and accuracy to an individual.

[b]Presence of Mind:[/b] 
[img]https://i.imgur.com/33uUKca.png[/img]

The Mage grants good speed to an ally for the first turn of combat.

[h1]Trinket Pictures &amp; Descriptions:[/h1]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/YkPMEBJ.png[/img]

[b][Sunward Isles] Spellbook: Ice Barrier:[/b] Gain an entirely new spell! Activate a non-damage riposte with each friendly ability with a 20% chance of gaining a block. The riposte has a chance to stun attackers.
[b]Black Ice Shard:[/b] A lack of heat grants bonuses to ice abilities. Extra damage, armor pen, and debuff chance in the darkness. Stress received increases.
[b]Eternal Candle:[/b] Lose some speed to gain a stress heal on friendly abilities &amp; torchlight on offensive action.
[b]Enchanted Compass:[/b] Gain extra scouting chance and reduced surprise chance with minor accuracy. Extra stress damage taken.
[b]Cauterizing Frostfire:[/b] Slightly injure allies, but grant regeneration. Minor torchlight gained on positive &amp; offensive actions.
[b]Red Dragon Ring:[/b] Lose all stun chance on Dragon&apos;s Breath to greatly enhance its damage, and receive greater strength from torchlight. This does grant Dragon&apos;s Breath normal stun chance in the Farm and Courtyard.
[b][CC]Frozen Skull:[/b] The Arcanist gains a permanent mark. The skull grants protection and damage per attack. Set bonus with Frozen Robes.
[b][CC]Frozen Robes:[/b] Lose all dodge chance and some speed, but gain good protection and health. Set bonus with Frozen Skull.
[b][CoM]Time Lord&apos;s Pocket Watch:[/b] Attempt to travel back in time to a better state. 25% chance for several effects, one of them quite terrible. Set bonus with Unstable Prism.
[b][CoM]Unstable Prism:[/b] Each attack &amp; friendly action reduces speed &amp; dodge, but enhances damage and crit. Set bonus with Time Lord&apos;s Pocket Watch.
[b][CoM]Crystal Ice Shard:[/b] Black Ice Shard, but for the Farm.

[h1]Final Thoughts:[/h1]

For those of you who don&apos;t recognize any of this, it&apos;s a mod based upon the WoW Mage class. I had a great time making this class, and I really appreciate the feedback Pencil and Hjordis gave along the way, among other contributors.

It&apos;s reasonably lore friendly. 

I like feedback. Please keep it to the forums, though-- comments for my mod are intended to be short messages, or urgent ones about bugs. 

[h1]Future plans:[/h1] 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RZVyHH-voR8
</ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>1800025310</PublishedFileId>
</project>

