<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>C:/Users/Sean/Desktop/Darkest Dungeon Mods/Wolf Knight/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>Abysswalker</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>public</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>3</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>0</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>0</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>Dark Souls</Tags>
		<Tags>Class Mod</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>Now updated for CoM! Synergy with Lord&apos;s Blade! https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1433161277
	
	Thank you, MOZHEM POVTORIT&apos; , for the Russian translation!
	
	Abysswalker 3.0 Brings: New animations, new stance, new buffs in the darkness, new trinkets, and a new consumable item to help manage the transformation.

[i]Abysswalkers are knights who follow the precedent set by Wolf Knight Artorias: halt the spread of evil through any sacrifice. Unmatched with greatswords, these legendary knights confront monsters and provinces reminiscent of the Abyss. Their exposure to the Abyss corrupts their souls, affecting their demeanor and fighting style. Elegant swordsmen? Raging berserkers? The line blurs depending on the severity of their corruption...[/i]

You are highly encouraged to play inside the affliction, and dance between 100 and 200 stress with this character. He gains damage every +25 stress above 100, and gains good bonuses in total darkness during his affliction.

[h1]Theme[/h1]

This mod gives the option of stance-swapping between two ideals: a defender of the realm, and a berserker bolstered by the Abyss. Stress represents the Abyssal corruption, and the more you have, the more damage you do. The character&apos;s corrupted stance gets benefits when under his special affliction, Heroic Struggle. 

[h1]Abilities[/h1]

Abilities are inspired by Abysswalker Artorias&apos; lore and boss fight in Dark Souls. They change a bit depending on whether you&apos;re afflicted.

[b]Pure Form[/b]

1) Darkwraith&apos;s Bane: The Abysswalker strikes with his enchanted sword, doing extra damage to Eldritch monsters. Minor stress heal.

2) Swordsman&apos;s Gambit: The Abysswalker sacrifices his form and stance to bash an enemy with his pauldron, stunning them. Moves the Abysswalker back and pushes the enemy.

3) Gliding Thrust: The Abysswalker glides towards his enemy, thrusting with his enchanted sword. Used from back ranks. Stress heal.

4) Loyalty: The Abysswalker, true to his knighthood, defends the Realm of Light. He guards an ally, brandishing himself for enemies&apos; attacks. This act of intense loyalty inspires the chosen comrade.

[b]Corrupted Form[/b]

5) Savage Strike: The Abysswalker dashes towards his enemy, striking it. Armor pen when afflicted. Used from positions 23. 

6) Savage Leap: The Abysswalker leaps at his enemy from the back, landing atop it with a forceful blow. Gains extra damage when afflicted. Targets back ranks.

7) Counterattack: The Abysswalker feints, entering a parry stance and retreating backward. Gains dodge. Gains more dodge when afflicted. 

8) Hurricane Slash: The Abysswalker swings at the middle enemy ranks, shuffling them. Bleeds both enemies. Moves back 1. Used from 12. Gains additional bleed chance when afflicted.

[h1] Trinkets [/h1]

1) Wolf Ring: Gain move resist, stun resist, and minor prot.
2) Covenant of Artorias: Gain crit &amp; stress resist in the dark.
3) Silver Pendant: Gain minor stress resist, good stress healing bonus, and debuff resistance.
4) Cleansing Greatshield: Gain large prot, but -4 speed when afflicted.
5) Red Abyssal Tear: Boosts damage and accuracy when afflicted. Greatly increases stress taken. Shares a set bonus with Blue Abyssal Tear.
6) Blue Abyssal Tear: Boosts prot by 15% and dodge by 15% when afflicted. Greatly increases stress taken.

[b]Abyssal Set Bonus[/b] Reduction to virtue chance.

[h1]Media [/h1]

Slayer1557 made a great video about this class, talking about the abilities and how he experienced it. It is out-of-date, though. Link here: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8HrOzZI3pwg

[h1] Future Plans [/h1]

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RZVyHH-voR8

[h1] Known Issues [/h1]

Sound doesn&apos;t work for the stance change. Can fix reasonably soon.

[h1] Huge Thanks [/h1]

Big, big thank you to SkeleDragon for recoloring the new animations for us!  </ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>1225113804</PublishedFileId>
</project>

