<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>C:/Users/Sean/Desktop/Darkest Dungeon Mods/Dragonslayer/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>Dragonslayer</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>public</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>2</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>3</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>3</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>New Class</Tags>
		<Tags>Dark Souls</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>Now Updated for CoM! Big thanks to Typical Arthas for his Russian translation!
	
	[h1]Class Introduction:[/h1]

Dragonslayer is based on Ornstein from Dark Souls, though I interpret him more broadly. He&apos;s primarily a damage dealer which specializes in killing size 2 targets, and armored targets. He has access to some support skills, too. A variety of trinkets allow him to fill multiple roles, and you can play him as a shuffler or stationary character.

[h1]Art Credit:[/h1]

AceroSteel drew this, based on another artist&apos;s work. Praise him as you would the Sun!

[h1]Combat Skills:[/h1]

[b]Swift Strike:[/b]

- - O O  v  X X - -

Dragonslayer&apos;s standard attack. It gains damage against size 2 targets, and builds electricity to empower his Lightning Impale.

[b]Lightning Spear:[/b]

O O O -  v   X X X -

Dragonslayer hurls lightning at his enemies, piercing armor with it. This attack builds electricity to empower his Lightning Impale. Moves Dragonslayer back 1.

[b]Princess&apos; Guard:[/b]

O O O O  

Dragonslayer defends an ally as he would his Princess of Light. He gains some dodge and activates a weak Riposte.

[b]Lightning Impale:[/b]

- O O O v X X - -

Dragonslayer impales his enemy. Without electricity gathered from other attacks, this attack is merely a low-damage stun. Moves Dragonslayer forward 1.

[b]Lightning Dash:[/b]

O O - -  v X X X X

Dragonslayer charges at the enemy, piercing their armor with his spear. This attack builds electricity to empower his Lightning Impale.

[b]Golden Glint: [/b]

- - O O  v  X X X X

Dragonslayer dodges backwards, ready to riposte.

[b]Bountiful Sunlight:[/b]

O O O O 

Dragonslayer calls upon one of his Princess&apos; miracles to heal an ally.


[h1]Camp Skills:[/h1]

In addition to the normal camp skills, Dragonslayer has...

[b]Dynamic Duo:[/b] Dragonslayer creates a tag team with a partner from the party, bestowing similar stats the Executioner had.
[b]Lion&apos;s Assault:[/b] Dragonslayer amplifies his crit.
[b]Captain&apos;s Vigil:[/b] Dragonslayer provides watch, removing threat of ambush and reducing surprise chance.
[b]Sacred Oath:[/b] Dragonslayer casts a miracle held by two of his old companions, increasing his damage and protection.

[h1]Trinkets:[/h1]

Dragonslayer Soul: Bonus damage on ranged attacks and virtue chance.
Ring of the Firstborn: Bonus damage on ranged attacks. 
Ring of the Sun Princess: Gains great bonus healing at the large cost of melee damage.
Leo Ring: Gains riposte damage.
Dragonslayer Band: Gains bonus damage from position 1, and against size 2 targets.

Dragonslayer Swordspear: CC trinket. Gain melee damage and strong virtue chance at the cost of much more stress.
Shield of the Rock: CC trinket. Gain immense protection, health, and move resistance at the cost of speed.

[h1]Final Thoughts:[/h1]

I&apos;ve wanted to revisit the Dragonslayer for a long time. It was my first mod. 

I think my skills have come a long way, and my ability to deliver quality has improved. 

This uprade to Dragonslayer is very simple, but I have absolutely crazy things planned for Sir Alonne. He will likely be my final mod. I had to resist the urge to implement his ideas into the Dragonslayer 2.0. The principle goal was to provide solid quality for the people who liked my more support-based Dragonslayer.

I think I&apos;ve succeeded. I&apos;m sure I&apos;ll hear whether I have or not.

If I revisit this guy again, he&apos;ll likely have stances.

[h1]A Friendly Request:[/h1]

I like feedback. Please keep it to the forums, though-- comments for my mod are intended to be short messages, or urgent ones about bugs. 


[h1]Future plans:[/h1]

None. </ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>1207974198</PublishedFileId>
</project>

