<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>D:/Exavault/My Modding Projects/Darkest Dungeon Modding/Scourge Class Mod/data/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>Exaelus&apos; Scourge Class Mod</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>public</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>0</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>0</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>0</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>Character Mod</Tags>
		<Tags>Class Mod</Tags>
		<Tags>New Class</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>[h1]The Scourge Class Mod[/h1]
Supports Color of Madness: Yes
Supports Crimson Court: Yes
Mod Version: 3.1c
Language: English, Russian, Korean


[h1]Latest News[/h1]

Mod now supports Color of Madness DLC!

Scourge now receives a buff when he crits. (+20% Blight Chance)

Scourge now has his own district building called &quot;Fountain of Pestilence&quot;!
Scourge receives a disease resist, blight amount and blight duration buffs.
Blight amount and duration buffs only work if the Scourge is blighted.

SCOURGE REWORKED!
2 new Crimson Court trinkets. (Screenshot added!)
1 new Color of Madness trinket. (Screenshot added!)
Infectious Offering now has a chance to transfer poison from all enemies to one target.
Infectious Offering attacks no longer penetrate armor.
Noxious Raze now has a chance to apply a weak blight effect on the other 2 targets.
Excoriate now applies a buff to Scourge that reduces all damage taken.
Purge now transfers all poison from your allies to the Scourge and then cures it.
Purge and Deathlock blight skill chance debuffs removed.
Purge now reduces blight amount applied to enemies.
Deathlock now reduces the blight duration applied to enemies.
Purge and Deathlock debuffs can no longer be removed with herbs.
Abyssal Havoc no longer applies horror but a slightly increased instant stress instead.
Un. Torment self plague removed, Scourge receives the shared ally group plague instead.
Aby. Havoc and Un. Torment are now on a 3 round cooldown.


[h1]Class Introduction[/h1]
Class has been heavily reworked. This would be my forth class on the workshop.
It took me 3 weeks to create, about 6-8 hours a day, some days even more.

The point of the scourge was to create a chaotic class. The idea behind him is that every time he attacks he plagues himself. Some of his attacks plague his enemies which do damage over time. Keep an eye on your plague stacks and use Purge or Infectious Offering when needed. Purge transfers all your group plague on the scourge, cures the plague on you, heals you and decreases his plague amount and dodge for a short period so be careful during that time. Infectious offering however gives all your current plague stacks to the enemy with a small chance to transfer poison from all enemies to a single target. There are multiple ways to deal with the plague stacks, you can also get some more antivenom or a plague doctor to cure you.

If you checked the screenshots you can see that 2 of his abilities have a purple outline which represents a very strong, high risk / high reward ability, however the entire group gets plagued and stressed when Unfathomable Torment is used and they get stressed when Abyssal Havoc is used, you can only use one of these every three rounds. He summons a creature of the abyss that resembles Cthulhu but it&apos;s not Cthulhu, this class is very &quot;Lovecraft&quot; inspired. I would also like you to ignore the amount of abilities and stats on the screenshots because i just wanted to display the visual effects that is all.

I spent a lot of time on visuals and audio which i hope you guys will enjoy, i wanted him to be satisfying to play. I also had to do quite a bit of math to come up with acceptable numbers which will probably change over time. Balancing him was very difficult but he is in a pretty good spot right now. Two additional abilities that I have to mention are Excoriate, which steals the plague stacks on enemies after it does extra damage to them and Deathlock which guards the entire team for a short period of time but be very careful during that time because he is going to be taking a lot of hits. He cannot travel with religious types and Revenant, which is one of my other classes. This is mostly for balance purposes.


[h1]Combat Skills[/h1]
[b] Infectious Offering: [/b] Attack position: 1,2 / Targets 1,2,3 / Effect: Dmg. gives blight to enemy
[b] Noxious Raze: [/b] Attack position: 1,2 / Targets 1+2 / Effect: Dmg, blight enemy and self
[b] Excoriate: [/b] Attack position: 1,2 / Targets 1+2+3 / Effect: Small dmg, if blight +dmg, steal plague
[b] Un. Torment:[/b] A. Position: 1 / Targets ALL / Effect: Dmg, plague all.
[b] Ab. Havoc:[/b]A. Position: 2 / Targets: 1,2,3,4 / Effect: Dmg, if blight +dmg, horror on team
[b] Purge:[/b]A. Position: ALL / Targets: SELF / Effect: Heal, steal ally blight and cure, debuff
[b] Deathlock:[/b] A. Position: 1,2 / Targets: ALL ALLIES / Effect: Guard all + prot buff and debuff

Noxious Raze and Deathlock poison you, Excoriate also blights you by stealing enemy plague.


[h1]Camping Skills[/h1]
[b] Rev. Draught: [/b]Self-Buff, if mortality debuff gain more buffs, stress others.
[b] Pestilent Tenacity: [/b] Self-Buff, virtue chance debuff
[b] Toxic Infusion: [/b] Group blight and desease resistance, does small dmg and stress others.
[b] Nefarious Feast:[/b] Heal group 50%, no need to eat until next camp, stress others.

I have to mention all of scourge camping skill last until the next camp instead of 4 battles.

If you find any bugs/glitches or spelling errors please let me know in the comment section below or just add me to your friends list, i do not bite and i will try to address the issues as soon as possible. All the positive feedback is really encouraging. This is yet another complete class pack, with upgrade sprites, sound effects, trinkets etc.

Here are my other classes if you want to try them out:

[url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=913178378][img]https://i.imgur.com/B8Duftl.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=924245318][img]https://i.imgur.com/a1YoES1.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=934967620][img] https://i.imgur.com/EvnjeGp.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=970030269][img]https://i.imgur.com/QX5m0ux.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1100450515][img]https://i.imgur.com/bBYf01L.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1138503289][img]https://i.imgur.com/Wccrwn4.png[/img][/url][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1441036778][img]https://i.imgur.com/Ratr9w8.png[/img][/url]


[h1]Known Issues:[/h1]
Scourge is in the Outsider&apos;s Bonfire district, he receives the bonuses from it but the game doesn&apos;t display him as a part of it for some reason. It should be fixed at some point.


[h1]Support[/h1]
Due to health issues my modding has been put on hold, but If you like what you see and you want me to do more in the future, you can support my mods by donating here:

[url=https://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_s-xclick&amp;hosted_button_id=PC3886U2YM8C6][img]https://i.imgur.com/6qUg1Xz.gif[/img][/url]


Thank you for all the positive feedback and your support, it does motivate me quite a bit!

Special thanks to &quot;Uncle Seifer&quot;(Russian) and &quot;halfmoon515&quot;(Korean) for translating my mod.

Special thanks to RedHook for making this great game and giving players the ability to mod it!

This mod is not an official Red Hook Studios product or product modification, and Red Hook Studios Inc. is not responsible in any way for changes or damages that may result from using the mod. Furthermore, “Darkest Dungeon” and the Darkest Dungeon logo are trademarks of Red Hook Studios Inc. All content in the game is Copyright Red Hook Studios Inc. All rights reserved.
</ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>947715735</PublishedFileId>
</project>

