<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>C:/Mods/The Fool/The Fool/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>The Fool -  Class Mod</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>public</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>1</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>601</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>0</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>character mod</Tags>
		<Tags>new class</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>WARNING - THIS MOD FEATURES MILD NUDITY

+-+-+

[img]https://i.imgur.com/ltZsZWU.png[/img]

[url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1203645088][img]https://i.imgur.com/xtOC9Sq.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1123633838][img]https://i.imgur.com/lC2BlsJ.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1109179698][img]https://i.imgur.com/v9sBefj.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1119908263][img]https://i.imgur.com/udn1RVX.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1115865609][img]https://i.imgur.com/ekPq6cR.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1157520643][img]https://i.imgur.com/DOvbTe7.png[/img][/url]
[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1464177353][img]https://i.imgur.com/aAEUSGD.png[/img][/url]

1.Description
2.Known Issues
3.Credits and Permissions
4.Changelog

-----------------
1.Description
-----------------

Washed ashore on the Hamlet coast, the Fool is lost in a haze, impossible to communicate with. 
Impaled by a spear to a small corpse by some strange indefeasible ritual, she desires only for the child&apos;s salvation.
She wants to free the poor unknown little wretched soul, and she will die trying, again and again. 
And it will never be done.

The Fool is a twisted stealthy heavy hitter.

Additional info on skills and mechanics - https://docs.google.com/document/d/1qXO7-fOGRmPNp5bnBgWu6q7nsk2YKo02uhNyhfLZSWI/edit?usp=sharing

Full Changelog - https://docs.google.com/document/d/1DMC87Wk9kGzDlUvlI2ecwi_rkyAIm19puFiApoGMI2Q/edit?usp=sharing

-----------------
2.Known Issues
-----------------

//All included
&gt; No need for additional patches unlike Muscarine&apos;s other characters, the Fool has the complete package. Does not require CC or CoM, but those trinkets will not spawn without the relevant DLC.

//Boobs
&gt; Palette A for the normal mod
&gt; Palette B for SFW

//Despair

This move is meant for killing the Fool if you end up in a battle that&apos;s unwinnable because the Fool is your last living hero and retreat is disabled. This can only occur in the following places:

Shrieker Fight
DD3 and DD4
Camping Ambushes

It CANNOT occur during flashbacks. Don&apos;t use it if you&apos;re not 100% certain you&apos;re stuck.

If she&apos;s in &quot;combat mode&quot; (other skills besides Wail available) it moves her back one rank with no ill effects. If she&apos;s in &quot;Wail mode&quot; it damages her and debuffs her healing received; spam it in order to kill her if softlocked.

-----------------
3.Credits and Permissions
-----------------

Copyright 2017-2019 Adrian Silvera. This item and its content are not authorized for posting on Steam, except under the steam account named &quot;psash&quot;, username Muscarine, or by Clair de Lune.

Original assets by Muscarine @ http://muscarine.org
Darkest Dungeon and everything Darkest Dungeon related is entirely the property of Red Hook Studios.
Red Hook is not responsible if this mod ends up damaging your game.

Coding by Clair de Lune

Writing by Rakked, a retired writer of erotic fiction. You can read his Darkest Dungeon fanfiction, including the Vestal&apos;s Salacious Diaries and his completed Darkest Dungeon Diaries project, here: 
http://rakkedyman.tumblr.com/post/165865685839/rakkeds-darkest-dungeon-epistolary-microfiction

Background art by eo, video game artist : https://www.artstation.com/eooo

SFX from Dark Souls
FromSoftware, Inc
BANDAI NAMCO Entertainment
All Rights Reserved

Translations:
Brazilian Portuguese - Dasmodeus, VinayssusMan, and Hooded Lay
Chinese - 双葉
German - Carnifex
French - Dedexy (Ghostliner) and Soul Smile
Italian - nobodysferpect and Laplace
Polish - Evilelandra and Abelitus
Russian - Citizen P., Whyimhere, Artishpalk, Mika_fr, and TrilliumInfernum
Spanish - Angel di Soufre and awscxd123
Korean - Nickel

If you plan to do anything with this mod you must ask Clair or Muscarine and be granted permission first.
You may contact Muscarine here : http://www.nexusmods.com/darkestdungeon/users/330348/?
You may contact Clair either on Steam or through the modding Discord: https://discord.gg/aDARnqG

- This is Muscarine&apos;s last DD mod to celebrate Fawn&apos;s birthday, and a gift for all of you who supported these mods.

- Wanna see modded DD streams ?
&gt; Element Five&apos;s Modded Darkest Dungeon streams @ 
https://www.twitch.tv/elementfive
&gt; Baron&apos;s Darkest Dungeon streams @ 
https://www.twitch.tv/rivalcastmedia 

Have fun ya all~

-----------------
4.Changelog - see patch notes linked above for more detail
-----------------

1.1 - added Death Whistle to avoid softlocks, added 10% Stress debuff to party on death

1.2 - updated Death Whistle for clarity, Banshee now applies -10 SPD debuff, Fool base SPD lowered by 2, Broken Lyre now inflicts 5 Stress on kill rather than healing stress, The Dead&apos;s Mouth heal from 3 to 2

1.3 - Death Whistle removed, Move skill replaced with Suicide to avoid softlocks

1.4 - updated Suicide to Despair to mitigate accidental suicides but still prevent softlocks, also now allows her to move back 1; The Dead&apos;s Mouth no longer heals

1.5 - +1 DMG, Wail Blight from 3/3/4/4/5 to 3/3/4/5/6, First Circle is now a free action but debuffs your next attack, Downpour and Burrowing Blight/Debuff Chance increased by 10%

1.6 - Fifth Circle DMG mod now 10% at all levels, fixed tooltips, Weeping Song is now a guaranteed stealth + &quot;taunt&quot;, Banshee stun chance increased by 5%, Celtic Knot Blight Amount reduced by 15%, added barks, fixed bugs
</ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>1464177353</PublishedFileId>
</project>

