<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>C:/Users/mckinneypitts/Desktop/Alraune mod folder/alraune mod/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>Alraune - Modded Class</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>public</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>1</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>1</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>0</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>New Class</Tags>
		<Tags>Custom Class</Tags>
		<Tags>Tank</Tags>
		<Tags>Stress Heal</Tags>
		<Tags>Hero</Tags>
		<Tags>Pets Compatible</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>Hi! Welcome to the Alraune modded class!  
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
This class is a stress healer/ tank character with potential to function as a blight damage dealer. He is particularly effective at tanking stress and bleeding attacks. 

This class is mine (Kwarma) and mine alone as far as publication goes.  If you want to feature this class in videos, streams, modpacks, go nuts as I would love to see them.  Message me on discord Kwarma#8954 or get in touch with me through the moonlit dungeon discord so I can watch as well and see what you think.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Crit Buff- 1/2 regeneration

Combat Skills
1. Strike- basic attack with a medium blight and decent crit chance
_ _XX   -   XXX_

2. Shunt- lower damage AOE attack with low blight
_XX_   -   X-X-X_

3. Petrify- self prot. buff, self cure, moves self back 2
_XXX

4. Shelter- 2 turn, single target guard and moderate stress heal on target, slight stress resist buff on self
XXXX
XXXX

5. Brambles- single target, single use, battle long buff that adds prot. and damage reflect to a friendly target and moderate damage reflection to self
XXXX
XXXX

6. Brace- team wide, friendly AOE low stress heal and -crit received buff
_ _XX
X-X-X-X

7. Timber- medium-high damage AOE attack that moves self forward 3 with a 66% chance to guard each teammate for 1 turn, this attack gains more range the higher its level
lvl 0: X_ _ _    -    X-X_ _      lvl 2: X_ _ _    -     X-X-X_  lvl    4: X_ _ _    -    X-X-X-X

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Camp Skills

Uproot- cost 1
increase self speed

Reminisce- cost 3
reduce self stress, 50% chance to reduce each party member&apos;s stress

Growth- cost 4
fully heal self and cure, increase healing received for 4 battles

Bird Song- cost 5
3 rolls of 50% to reduce party member&apos;s stress by 10

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
This class comes with 8 custom trinkets for the Alraune himself including a trophy and a pet that you have to find :)

CC and CoM trinkets are coming soon!

This mod also introduces 2 new quirks that will increase or decrease the stress healing received from the Alraune&apos;s stress healing abilities.

It also adds 3 new camping ambushes to the party if the Alraune is in the party on a weald mission (this is the only way to get 3 of his slightly stronger trinkets)

A town event accompanies this mod in order to introduce your first alraune, but he can also appear in the stagecoach at the same frequency as a man at arms.

NAME AND LORE EXPLANATION https://docs.google.com/document/d/1yOdlQISZqDiTh946lu8bl8vuxjFr6SDsJJ3K5HTL5r4/edit?usp=sharing
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

FUN FACTS!
The Alraune&apos;s default name is Jakob after the scientist in the book after which he is so named.

He doesn&apos;t talk much. This is partially due to him being sad and out of his own time, but also due to the infection controlling an unspecified amount of his body and also his mind.

The alraune loves animals and therefore his favorite class to pair up with is houndmaster. This is canon as I have just now made it so. you&apos;re welcome

^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^

I am but a measly American who only speaks like 1.5 languages, so if you want to do localization for any other languages just let me know through the comments here or the discord channels I have mentioned previously!

check out my other mods.  You may like them or you may not, but you&apos;ll never know until you download them and try

SHOUTOUT MLD DISCORD COME JOIN LINK AT THE BOTTOM

Translations: English (myself), Russian (Holodilnik), PM me if you want to translate to other languages

special shoutouts to SolarNougat, Peppy (the god), Dem, PrplTrash, TheHusky, HjordisTBM, ParadiseBell, IndiePhunq, Voodoo (netsilana), and everyone else in the super cool testing channel in the discord!

[h1]Pets Compatible[/h1]
    [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1779509342][img]https://i.imgur.com/Cb2vcbh.jpg[/img][/url]
    NOW LIVE! Help free &quot;Ruby&quot;, the Alraune&apos;s Pet Bird who was captured by the Pet Patrol in the [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1779509342][b]Pets (Trinkets + Monster Mod)[/b][/url]. Optional mod.

^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^
DISCLAIMERS
I do not own any of these art files or assets
Everything belongs to Red Hook
If you want to use my mods in any playthroughs, streams, modpacks, etc. please feel free to do so, but do ask permission or do not steal credit.
If any ideas from this mod inspire you to do something similar, feel free to do so.
I am not an artist nor a game designer so I do the best with what I can :) Feel free to contact me about any changes you want to see happen as I love talking balance and design

IF THIS CRASHES YOUR GAME OR CAUSES ANY PROBLEMS IT IS NOT MY NOR THE FAULT OF RED HOOK!

ALSO come join the Moonlit Dungeon discord if you have not already -&gt; https://discord.gg/VkXB87M
It is full of cool people who also love this game and love to answer questions about modding, darkest dungeon, darkest dungeon 2, or just life in general.  They are cool mostly.

If you have questions, comments, balancing suggestions, or just want to talk, feel free to comment on this mod or get in touch with me on discord through the Moonlit Dungeon community!
</ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>1739004957</PublishedFileId>
</project>

