<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>F:/SteamLibrary/steamapps/common/DarkestDungeon/mods/monk/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>Monk Class Mod</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>Public</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>0</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>0</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>0</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>New Class</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>Chat
[[Support Info]]
This mod support Color of Madness
This mod support Crimson Court
This mod can be played without dlc&apos;s

[[LOCALLIZED]]
English, Spanish, Polish, Russian, Korean, French, Brazilian, Chinese

[[Intro]]
Hello! 
This is the first mod that i have created for Darkest Dungeon (and my life!)
I love darkest dungeon, and you can maybe expect to see a other mod of me again.

Beside i did get someone help to translate from Korean to english. 
So it can be support english version, Thank you very much!!

[[INFORMATION]]
The class name is &quot;Monk&quot;.
It&apos;s inspired from Kharazim - HOS/Diablo3.
There are also CC, COM Trinkets.

When you build the district called &quot;outsider&apos;s bonefire&quot; (crimson court)
The monk will recieve a buff/effect 

[[Combat skill sets / Brief effects]]

0. Crit effect / Heal Other allies 4% of HP
It is his identity, it can be buffed his another skill or Trinkets.

1. Dragon tail (XXOO - OOOX)
Foward 1 / Next round buff except &quot;Dragon Tail&quot;

2. Howling fist (XXXO - OOXX)
Back 1 / Next round buff except &quot;Howling Fist&quot;
Higher Crit Chance / litle heal himself / Enemy PROT debuff (next round)

3. Iron mountain (XOOX - O-OXX)
Foward 2 / Ignore PROT /Push them 2

4. Sweeping kick (XXOO - OOXX)
Stun / Speed debuff / Next round buff except &quot;Sweeping Kick&quot;

5. Transfer (OOOO - individual ally except self)
Heal 20 ~ 25% of max HP + / Self damage / Self restoration smaller than damage
Exhaust Self

6. Mantram (OOOO - Allies exept self)
Little heal / PROT buff
Self Buff / DMG - 40% CRIT +100% / Exhaust Self / Next round Hit - to - heal ally expect himself

7. Inner fire (OOOO - Self)
0 ~ x heal himself / Riposte / Next Attack DMG buff / 3rounds little DMG buff / Stress heal chance

8. Riposte
Heal other allies 3% of HP on chance.

[[Trinkets]]

Common - CRIT +3 / Dodge +6
Uncommon 1 - Stun / Debuff chance +20%
Uncommon 2 - SPD -3 / &quot;Inner Fire&quot; Hp Heal Amount +2 / &quot;Riposte&quot; Hp Heal amount +1
Rare - &quot;Transfer&quot; DMG Received percent - 50% / &quot;Transfer&quot; Hp Heal percent - 40%
Very Rare - HP Heal amount +2 / CRIT -8 / DMG -15%

CC Trinket 1 - HP Heal amount -1 / CRIT +8 / MAX HP +30% / Dodge -10
CC Trinket 2 - HP Heal amount -1 / DMG +30% / ACC +10
CC Set Effect - &quot;Howling Fist&quot; DMG +33% / &quot;Inner Fire&quot; HP heal amount +3

COM Trinket - HP Heal percent +60% / CRIT +8 / MAX HP -10% / SPD -3
------------------

Feb 26 2019 UPDATED --

REBALLANCE: &quot;Inner fire&quot; - Riposte CRIT rate is decreased by 10%.
REBALLANCE: &quot;Inner fire&quot; - Riposte DMG is very slightly increased .
REBALLANCE: &quot;Inner fire&quot; - Stress heal effect chances don&apos;t increased by rank-up (always 67%).

REBALLANCE: &quot;transfer&quot; - Self DOT heal is decreased.
REBALLANCE: &quot;transfer&quot; - Self DMG is decreased in final upgrade by 1.

REBALLANCE: &quot;Mantram&quot; - Heal amount from &quot;howling fist&quot; decreased by 1.
REBALLANCE: &quot;Mantram&quot; - Crit with this skills buff cannot heal stress himself.
REBALLANCE: &quot;Mantram&quot; - Heal amount by upgrade is changed.


REBALLANCE: &quot;Howling Fist&quot; - it can heal self when used in first rank basically. Some special accessory makes it can heal less than normal in second rank.
REBALLANCE: Base CRIT stats decreased by 3%.

[[SPECIAL THANKS]]

Slayer1557 - He make a video that spotlight of monk!
El Jakob - He had translate it English to Spanish! and, inspect english!
Ilsamurai - He had help inspect to Spanish!
hero of dwarfs - He had translate it English to Polish!
Solidus - He had translate it English to Russian!
LotsZ - He had translate it English to Brazilian!
Tocity - He had translate it English to French!
unknown someone had translate Korean to English!
rainfoxest, foxical - They have translate English to Chinese!
Sifr Ivangellis, R20LEGEND, TheMLGReploid, Shay, 󠀡󠀡󠀡󠀡󠀡󠀡󠀡󠀡󠀡󠀡󠀡LotsZ
- they gave me advices on balancing!

Thank you very much, guys!! ♡♡

----
안녕하세요!
지난 6월 말쯤부터 만들기 시작해서 이제야 베타버전을 공개할 수 있게 되었네요.
뭐 어려운 것 있겠어 하고 맨땅에 헤딩했다가 진짜 평생 안만져봤을 프로그램들도 잔뜩 만져보고 재밌기도 했네요 ㅋㅋ
난생 처음 이런 걸 만들어보는거라 좀 어색한 부분이나 구멍이 꽤 많을 수도 있지만 재밌게 즐겨주시길 바라요.
영어를 잘 못해서 어떻게 업로드를 해야할 까 싶었는데 어떤 분의 도움을 받아서 모드 언어들을 영어로 바꿀 수 있었어요!
정말 감사... 압도적 감사!

일단 이 캐릭터는 히오스와 디아3의 카라짐을 모티브로 작업했습니다! 신박한 딜힐일체로 만들고싶었어요!

시스템 문제 상 설명글에 적혀있지는 않지만 이 캐릭터는 문둥이나 괴인 등이 속한 &quot;외지인의 모닥불&quot; 시설에 영향을 받습니다.

재미있게 즐겨주시기 바랍니다!

- 2019년 2월 26일 업데이트됨

REBALLANCE: &quot;내면의 열정&quot; - 반격의 치명타 확률이 전 구간에서 10% 낮아집니다.
REBALLANCE: &quot;내면의 열정&quot; - 반격의 기본 피해량이 조금 증가합니다.
REBALLANCE: &quot;내면의 열정&quot; - 스스로 스트레스를 해소할 확률이 랭크에 따라 증가하지 않습니다. (항상 67%)

REBALLANCE: &quot;전이&quot; - 자기 자신에 대한 도트힐 효과가 감소합니다.
REBALLANCE: &quot;전이&quot; - 스스로 받는 피해가 최대 랭크에서 1 감소합니다.

REBALLANCE: &quot;진언&quot; - 전 구간에서 공명타 회복량 증가량이 1 감소합니다.
REBALLANCE: &quot;진언&quot; - 3랭크에서 모든 공격으로 인한 회복량이 1 감소합니다. (최대랭크엔 변화가 없습니다.)
REBALLANCE: &quot;진언&quot; - 3랭크에서 축퇴로 인한 회복량이 1 증가합니다. (최대랭크엔 변화가 없습니다.)
REBALLANCE: &quot;진언&quot; - 진언으로 인한 치명타는 스스로의 스트레스를 해소할 수 없습니다.

REBALLANCE: &quot;공명타&quot; - 스스로 회복하는 효과가 1열에서 사용했을 때에만 적용됩니다. 일부 장신구의 효과로 2열에서 회복 가능합니다.
REBALLANCE: 기본 치명타 확률이 3% 낮아집니다.


	</ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>1442225067</PublishedFileId>
</project>

