<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>C:/Users/rabus/OneDrive/Desktop/DD Mod Stuff/The Keeper/Keeper Final/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>The Keeper Class Mod</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>public</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>0</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>0</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>0</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>New Class</Tags>
		<Tags>New Hero</Tags>
		<Tags>Keeper</Tags>
		<Tags>Condena</Tags>
		<Tags>Religious</Tags>
		<Tags>Horror</Tags>
		<Tags>Nudity</Tags>
		<Tags>Memes</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>[i]&quot;The human mind, fragile, like a robin&apos;s egg...&quot;[/i]

[h1][b]Introduction[/b][/h1]
[h1]------------------------------------------[/h1]
[b]DISCLAIMER: This mod is not directly connected to the already existing Condena hero mod, apart from using the same skin with permission from both Seta Nagato and AceroSteel. It features gore, body horror, and mild nudity.[/b]

The Keeper is a mod project that adds a brand new hero to Darkest Dungeon. This hero is completely custom, with all new sprites, skills, sounds, and animations, as well as a complete set of unique trinkets, alternate color palettes and team combos. 

The Keeper is a support hero, with powerful single target heals, buffs and debuffs. She is a highly defensive hero, having a mediocre damage output on her own, but enabling herself or other heroes to retaliate against enemies by reflecting damage towards them, as well as allowing the creature in her body to lash out and inflict heavy bleeds. She is also able to take a tremendous amount of stress, many of her skills becoming more powerful the higher her stress level. This is balanced by her unique affliction, Tormented, which has her begin to quite literally tear herself apart. 

[i]&quot;A waif cursed with a monstrous burden, the Keeper is host to an otherworldly horror beneath her skin. She bends the creature to the Light&apos;s will in combat, sacrificing herself for the good of her allies, and becoming all the stronger for it; however, should she be pushed to her limits, it will seize control.&quot;[/i]

[h1][b]Comic[/b][/h1]
[h1]------------------------------------------[/h1]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/udqYZt4.jpg[/img]
[url=https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/480545827610427392/555558867107315733/the_keeper_comicHD.png]Full Resolution Comic[/url]

[h1][b]Combat Skills[/b][/h1]
[h1]------------------------------------------[/h1]

[b]Writhe[/b]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/6LO7i6U.png[/img]
XOOO OOOX
[i]The creature within the Keeper stirs, lashing out at its vessel&apos;s attackers.[/i]

Standard melee attack. Low damage and low bleed. +1 bleed amount applied per 25% stress. Self stresses for 3.

[b]Convalescence[/b]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/D3PBl2h.png[/img]
OOOO
[i]The Keeper takes a moment to recover, healing her wounds and soothing her fractured mind.[/i]

Self only. Applies a 1 turn heal over time. Heavy self stress heal.

[b]Rebirth[/b]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/NdFIhXx.png[/img]
OOOX
[i]The Keeper heals her teammate with magic both divine and profane, relinquishing some of her own life force in the process.[/i]

Single target heal for a smallish percentage of their HP. +20% heals per 25 stress. Self bleeds for a small amount. Self stresses for 3.

[b]Daemon&apos;s Yoke[/b]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/NrI74as.png[/img]
OOOO OOOO
[i]The creature inhabiting the Keeper conjures an ally for a brief moment, grasping and clawing at them from below.[/i]

Low damage. Debuffs target&apos;s dodge and increases the amount of damage they take from Writhe. Low chance to stun. +20% stun chance per 25 stress. Self stresses for 3.

[b]Phantom Wail[/b]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/bUDcsCx.png[/img]
OOOO
[i]The creature reveals itself, releasing a piercing shriek that warps reality.[/i]

Strong damage reflect buff on ally. Stresses ally moderately. Debuffs the ally by giving them an increased chance to hit a random target instead. Self stresses for 3.

[b]Cacophony[/b]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/tAqqPud.png[/img]
OOOX O+O+O+O
[i]The creature screams, disorienting the enemy team momentarily.[/i]

Low damage. +25% damage per 25 stress. Slightly debuffs enemies&apos; stun resistance. Guaranteed crit vs stunned enemies, activating her riposte via her crit buff (see Other Information). Self stresses for 3.

[b]Sacrifice[/b]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/EvRxv6s.png[/img]
OOOO
[i]The Keeper puts herself on the line for her allies, curing their wounds and guarding them with her life.[/i]

Small heal on allies. Guards all allies for 2 turns. High chance to apply a 5 over 3 horror. Cannot be used again for 3 rounds.

[h1][b]Camping Skills[/b][/h1]
[h1]------------------------------------------[/h1]

[b]Baneful Pact[/b]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/UtqE6YP.png[/img]
Time Cost: 3
[i]The creature within the Keeper makes a pact with one of her allies, at a dire cost.[/i]

One ally gains +25% damage, but -20% max hp, and takes 5 stress. Lasts 4 battles.

[b]Martyr&apos;s Touch[/b]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/xMpsYan.png[/img]
Time Cost: 4
[i]The Keeper performs a miracle, relieving her allies&apos; burdens at the expense of her own body.[/i]

Ally is healed for 25% HP, buffed for +25% max hp, and cleared of Death&apos;s Door debuffs. The Keeper gains a bleed of 1 pt/rd for 12 rds.

[b]Lonesome Communion[/b]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/6psFiRG.png[/img]
Time Cost: 3
[i]The Keeper prays for deliverance, sequestered from the rest of the group for a time.[/i]

Self buff for +25% prot. Heals 10 stress.

[b]Self-Exorcism[/b]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/KuS3DOf.png[/img]
Time Cost: 3
[i]The Keeper battles the monstrosity inhabiting her in a horrific display, keeping it at bay for a time.[/i]

Keeper stress heals for 25, and another 25 if afflicted. Other teammates have a 50% chance to take 10 stress if not religious, and 100% chance if religious.

[h1][b]Other Information[/b][/h1]
[h1]------------------------------------------[/h1]
[list]
[*]The Keeper is religious.
[*]She refuses to go to the Brothel for stress relief.
[*]She uses the Altar of Light district.
[*]She starts with 1 Laudanum as provisions.
[*]Her default name is Cristabel.
[*]She will not travel with a second Keeper.
[*]On crit, she activates riposte.
[*]This mod comes with 9 class specific trinkets for the Keeper: 2 common, 1 uncommon, 1 rare, 1 very rare, 2 Crimson Court and 1 Color of Madness, along with 1 extra trinket for the Sunward Isles mod.
[*]The Keeper has a town event so you can get one immediately.
[*]This mod is fully compatible with all 3 DLCs.
[*]This mod currently supports English, Russian, Czech and Spanish localization. If you can help translate this mod, please contact either me on Steam or (preferably) on Discord: Shay#9164.
[/list]

[h1][b]Credits[/b][/h1]
[h1]------------------------------------------[/h1]
[list]
[*]AceroSteel: Original Condena Vestal skin
[*]Seta Nagato: Original Condena hero mod/inspiration
[*]Shay: Coding, sound design, writing
[*]RedDye: Trinket and icon art
[*]Mhnlo: FX, event art and additional animations
[*]Von Krolock: Comic, wallpaper, concept brainstorming
[*]Rothag, SoulSmile: Concept brainstorming
[*]Taro, EbonyBetty: Additional writing
[*]Mad_bucket.png: Russian localization
[*]ULTIMATE: Czech localization
[*]Mafe: Spanish localization
[/list]

Special thanks to Icathios, Karyuen, and everyone else on the [url=https://discord.gg/VkXB87M]Moonlit Dungeon Discord server[/url] who helped with beta testing, bug fixing and general feedback as the mod developed. Special thanks also has to go to [url=https://www.twitch.tv/elementfive]ElementFive[/url] for reviewing and promoting the mod on Youtube and Twitch. This would never have been possible without any of you, and I will always be incredibly grateful for all your support.

If you like this mod, you might also like my other mod, the Exorcist!

[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1607991008][img]https://i.imgur.com/rwBfsez.png[/img][/url]

[h1][b]Legal Jargon[/b][/h1]
[h1]------------------------------------------[/h1]
This item and its content are not authorized for posting on Steam, except under the Steam account Shay. This mod is not an official Red Hook product. Darkest Dungeon and everything Darkest Dungeon related is entirely the property of Red Hook Studios. Red Hook is not responsible if this mod ends up damaging your game.</ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>1688250816</PublishedFileId>
</project>

