<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>D:/Exavault/My Modding Projects/Darkest Dungeon Modding/Revenant Class Mod/data/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>Exaelus&apos; Revenant Class Mod</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>public</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>0</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>0</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>0</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>Character Mod</Tags>
		<Tags>Class Mod</Tags>
		<Tags>New Class</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>[h1]The Revenant Class Mod[/h1]
Supports Color of Madness: Yes
Supports Crimson Court: Yes
Mod Version: 3.7e
Language: English, Spanish, French, Polish, Brazilian, Russian, Korean


[h1]Latest News[/h1]

Mod now supports Color of Madness DLC!

Revenant now receives a buff when he crits. (+20% Bleed Chance)

Revenant now has his own district building called &quot;Crimson Shrine&quot;!
Revenant receives Crimson Curse death immunity, bleed amount and bleed duration buffs.
Bleed amount and duration buffs only work if the Revenant is affected by the Crimson Curse.

2 new Crimson Court trinkets. (Screenshot added!)
1 new Color of Madness trinket. (Screenshot added!)

Class restrictions changed to: Leper, Crusader, Vestal, Man-At-Arms, Scourge and Harbinger.
Revenant is now a part of the district and also provides a skeleton key on every mission.
Created 1 set of trinkets out of existing trinkets. (Screenshot updated!)
You can now only have 1 Revenant per group.


[h1]Class Introduction[/h1]
Revenant is a class that i worked on for about 4 weeks about 6-8 hours a day. This was my very first mod on the steam workshop and it&apos;s heavily inspired by Dragon Age, Warcraft and Darkness the video game. I spent a lot of time polishing the sprites so there are no graphical issues/glitches, in my opinion the class fits into the world and looks like its a part of it now.

My original goal was to make a class that feels like an official class expansion by respecting the rules of the game such as resistances, damage, upgrades and art. I&apos;ve tried my very best to replicate the art of DD and the end result is decent. I&apos;ve also made 5 Revenant specific trinkets that are no longer separate and are now included in this class mod. 

On the balance side of things I&apos;ve done a lot of number crunching and a decent amount of testing and this is not the strongest class against the undead but good enough for everything else. 

He is primarly a tank that is capable of doing really decent damage once his enemies start to bleed. He can heal and transfer all bleeds from all enemies to a single target. He also provides a skeleton key when embarking on a mission.


[h1]Combat Skills[/h1]
[b] Sanguine Strike: [/b] Attack position: 1,2 / Targets 1+2 / Effect: Small dmg, bleed
[b] Obliterate: [/b] Attack position: 1,2 / Targets 1,2 / Effect: Small dmg, high dmg to bleed, push +1
[b] Bloodfury: [/b] Attack position: 1,2 / Targets 1,2 / Effect: Small dmg, bleed + riposte + mark
[b] Crimson Unity:[/b] A. Position: ALL / Targets 1,2,3,4 / Effect: all enemy bleeds on one target + dbf
[b] Immortality:[/b]A. Position: 1,2 / Targets: Self / Effect: Increases prot. to you and the group
[b] Siphon Life:[/b]A. Position: ALL / Targets: ALL / Effect: Attack all foes and heal for every enemy hit
[b] Vampiric Embrace:[/b] A. Position: 1,2 / Targets: Ally / Effect: Heal, apply heal buff + stress


[h1]Camping Skills[/h1]
[b] Sanguine Potion: [/b]Buff self, add prot., blood res. and plague res., stress party slightly.
[b] Blood Ritual: [/b] Self-heal and self-stress removal, add small amount of stress to party.
[b] Appaling Apathy [/b] Self-stress removal, stress reduction buff, stress party a bit.
[b] Drain Life:[/b] Damage your allies and heal-self, stress the rest for a decent amount.

As you can see he is quite a selfish class. The other 3 camping skills are the standard ones everyone else has.

If you find any bugs/glitches or spelling errors please let me know in the comment section below and i will try to address them. I hope you enjoy playing this class as much as i had fun making it and if a lot of people like it, i might make another one.

Here are my other classes if you want to try them out:

[url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=924245318][img]https://i.imgur.com/a1YoES1.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=934967620][img] https://i.imgur.com/EvnjeGp.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=947715735][img]https://i.imgur.com/wtvL4QS.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=970030269][img]https://i.imgur.com/QX5m0ux.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1100450515][img]https://i.imgur.com/bBYf01L.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1138503289][img]https://i.imgur.com/Wccrwn4.png[/img][/url][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1441036778][img]https://i.imgur.com/Ratr9w8.png[/img][/url]


[h1]Support[/h1]
Due to health issues my modding has been put on hold, but If you like what you see and you want me to do more in the future, you can support my mods by donating here:

[url=https://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_s-xclick&amp;hosted_button_id=PC3886U2YM8C6][img]https://i.imgur.com/6qUg1Xz.gif[/img][/url]


Thank you for all the positive feedback and your support, it does motivate me quite a bit!

Special thanks to &quot;SnakePriest&quot;(Spanish), &quot;jmakiela&quot;(Polish), &quot;Alfarr, The Lionheart&quot;(Brazilian), 
&quot;Uncle Seifer&quot;(Russian), &quot;halfmoon515&quot;(Korean) and &quot;Chocostar&quot;(French) for translating my mod.

Special thanks to RedHook for making this great game and giving players the ability to mod it!

This mod is not an official Red Hook Studios product or product modification, and Red Hook Studios Inc. is not responsible in any way for changes or damages that may result from using the mod. Furthermore, “Darkest Dungeon” and the Darkest Dungeon logo are trademarks of Red Hook Studios Inc. All content in the game is Copyright Red Hook Studios Inc. All rights reserved.
</ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>913178378</PublishedFileId>
</project>

