<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>D:/Exavault/My Modding Projects/Darkest Dungeon Modding/Seer Class Mod/data/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>Exaelus&apos; Seer Class Mod</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>public</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>0</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>0</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>0</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>Character Mod</Tags>
		<Tags>Class Mod</Tags>
		<Tags>New Class</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>[h1]The Seer Class Mod[/h1]
Supports Color of Madness: Yes
Supports Crimson Court: Yes
Mod Version: 3.1f
Language: English, Spanish, Polish, Korean


[h1]Latest News[/h1]

Mod now supports Color of Madness DLC!

Seer now receives a buff when she crits. (+40% Stress Healing)

2 new Crimson Court trinkets. (Screenshot added!)
1 new Color of Madness trinket. (Screenshot added!)

Slight trinket rework!

Seer is now a part of the district and also provides 2 laudanums on every mission.
Created 1 set of trinkets out of existing trinkets. (Screenshot updated!)
You can now only have 1 seer per group.


[h1]Class Introduction[/h1]
Say hello to my third class that i worked on for about 2 full weeks, she is the Seer.

So far i have made a tank (The Revenant), a dps (The Prodigy) and it was only fitting to make a much needed healer/support class. Most people drag healers around because they are nice to have for survival and in most cases they aren&apos;t that fun, the biggest challange making this class was making a support/healer that is still quite fun to use. So i had to think hard how to make a class that will feel satisfying to use and still have the uniqueness that isn&apos;t too complex, i also wanted her to be a different and a unique class so i made a mixed class, a mixture of a dark moon priest / spiritualist that can talk to the dead and control her own spirit/soul. This class also has no restrictions and can travel with any other class.

The Revenant is the hybrid &quot;jack of all trades&quot; but still having his own blood thing going on.
The Prodigy is all about movement and positioning, executing enemies from specific locations.
The Seer however cannot crit but instead she multi casts spells that are strong enough to stun her.

You shouldn&apos;t worry though, with every spell that she casts she increases her stun resistance, so the more she casts the more reliable she becomes, think of it as resource generation. So it&apos;s recommended to use the abilities that do not stun first to build up some stun resistance in order to cast the stronger spells which can stun, that way you reduce the stun risk. Balancing this character was not easy, but she should be in a good spot, i will be tuning the numbers as time goes on, so feel free to give some feedback on how the class performs. 


[h1]Combat Skills[/h1]

[b] Touch of Death: [/b]Attack position: 3,4 / Targets 2,3,4 / Effect: No damage, amplified by status effects.
[b] Hypnosis: [/b]A. position: 3,4 / Targets 3,4 / Effect: dmg, pulls 1,2 or 3 spots, can also stun enemy.
[b] Spectral Blast: [/b]A. position: 3,4 / Targets 2+3 / Effect:  dmg, reduces ACC (can spread) + self stun.
[b] Celestial Renewal: [/b]A. Position: 3,4 / Targets 1 ALLY / Effect: Heals, can heal ×2 ×3 + self stun.
[b] Tranquility: [/b]A. Position: 3,4 / Targets: ALL ALLIES / Effect: - stress, can reduce ×2 + self stun.
[b] Rejuvenating Surge: [/b]A. Position: 3,4  / Targets: ALL ALLIES / Effect: Heals, can h. ×2 ×3 + self stun.
[b] Ethereal Blessing: [/b]A. Position: 3,4  / Targets: 1 ALLY (NOT SELF) / Effect: +dmg, can proc ×2.

As you can see abilities 3,4,5 and 6 have a chance to stun her, the rest don&apos;t.

The idea behind Touch of Death is to give players more control over damage, instead of just a regular critical strike chance you can increase her damage reliably by stacking status effects, for each status effect this ability does more and more damage. If your enemy has all 3 effects that are allowed (Bleed, Stun, Plague), they will take a lot of damage.


[h1]Camping Skills[/h1]
[b] Eclipse: [/b] Heals all to max hp, reduces torch and causes small stress to all.
[b] Clairvoyance: [/b] Reduces ambush chance, increases scouting, causes some stress.
[b] Forgotten Heritage: [/b] Gives random heirloom(s).
[b] Spectral Shroud:[/b] Increases resistances (Bleed,Debuff,Blight,Desease) and protection by 15%.

If you find any bugs/glitches or spelling errors please let me know in the comment section below or just add me to your friends list, i do not bite and i will try to address the issues as soon as possible. All the positive feedback is really encouraging however my motivation has slightly dropped and i need a small break before i make another class. I will take some time off and see what the DLC will have to offer on the 19th then i will see what i will do from there. This is yet another complete class pack, with upgrade sprites, sound effects trinkets etc.

Here are my other classes if you want to try them out:

[url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=913178378][img]https://i.imgur.com/B8Duftl.png [/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=924245318][img]https://i.imgur.com/a1YoES1.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=947715735][img]https://i.imgur.com/wtvL4QS.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=970030269][img]https://i.imgur.com/QX5m0ux.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1100450515][img]https://i.imgur.com/bBYf01L.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1138503289][img]https://i.imgur.com/Wccrwn4.png[/img][/url][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1441036778][img]https://i.imgur.com/Ratr9w8.png[/img][/url]


[h1]Known Issues:[/h1]
Currently there is an issue with the stun chances on healing spells not being displayed properly, for some reason the game does not display the stun chances that are past 99% for spells that heal/target allies. If you need to see the chances you can look up Spectral Blast for reference, that works fine.


[h1]Support[/h1]
Due to health issues my modding has been put on hold, but If you like what you see and you want me to do more in the future, you can support my mods by donating here:

[url=https://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_s-xclick&amp;hosted_button_id=PC3886U2YM8C6][img]https://i.imgur.com/6qUg1Xz.gif[/img][/url]


Thank you for all the positive feedback and your support, it does motivate me quite a bit!

Special thanks to &quot;Urisan23&quot;(Spanish), &quot;jmakiela&quot;(Polish) 
and &quot;halfmoon515&quot;(Korean) for translating my mod.

Special thanks to RedHook for making this great game and giving players the ability to mod it!

This mod is not an official Red Hook Studios product or product modification, and Red Hook Studios Inc. is not responsible in any way for changes or damages that may result from using the mod. Furthermore, “Darkest Dungeon” and the Darkest Dungeon logo are trademarks of Red Hook Studios Inc. All content in the game is Copyright Red Hook Studios Inc. All rights reserved.
</ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>934967620</PublishedFileId>
</project>

