<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>C:/Users/Sean/Desktop/Darkest Dungeon Mods/Royal Aegis/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>Royal Aegis - New Class - Torchless Guardian</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>public</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>1</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>2</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>0</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>New Class</Tags>
		<Tags>Dark Souls</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>Now updated for CoM!
	
	[h1]Class Introduction:[/h1]

The Royal Aegis is a guardian renowned for his strength. For many years, he defended his king&apos;s tomb in the darkness. It warped his faith, and imbued him with unique strengths when light disappears. He fights with a bell mace. Once, it acted as a chime for holy miracles. Now, it tolls for death.

Foremost, he defends his allies by stepping between them and harm, then cleaving enemies away from them. In the darkness, his strength grows immensely.

[h1]Art Credit:[/h1]

Huge thanks to EiraQueenofSnow for drawing this character art. She is fantastic to work with.

Huge thanks to Carnifex for helping with promotion art, trinket art, and general feedback.

Huge thanks to SkeleDragon. She made the recolors.

Huge thanks to Foxical for the Chinese translation!

[h1]Combat Skills:[/h1]

[b]Two Handed Smash:[/b]

- - O O  v  X X - -

This is the Royal Aegis&apos; standard attack. He damages enemies&apos; armor with his bell mace, and gets armor pen in low light.

[b]Overhead Slam:[/b]

- - O O  v  X+X - -

This attack stuns the front two enemies. Gets armor pen in low light.

[b]Multi-Hit:[/b]

O O O -  v  X X - - 

The Royal Aegis performs a quick strike which does not chime his bell. It does not consume a turn. Gets armor pen in low light.

[b]Dark Solace:[/b]

O O O O

The Royal Aegis casts a miracle in the darkness, granting extreme power and speed when the light is gone. Reduces dodge to 0, and reduces stress for self.

[b]Launch:[/b]

- - O O  v X+X - -

The Royal Aegis cleaves the first two enemies, sending them flying toward the back of the room. Enemy speed is reduced from such an attack.

[b]Oath: [/b]

O O O O  v  X X - -

The Royal Aegis stands between his allies and each enemy. He does not dodge, but gains decent protection, and more in the darkness. In future updates, he will gain different buffs per position.

[b]Dark Barrage:[/b]

O O - -  v  X X X X

The Royal Aegis swings his bell mace in the air, summoning dark orbs to wreck the enemy. Hits through stealth and destealths enemies. Gains power in low light.


[h1]Camp Skills:[/h1]

In addition to the normal camp skills, the Royal Aegis has...

Burden: Stresses himself to heal allies&apos; stress.
Save the King!: Reduces melee damage to boost protection.
Dark Blessing: Remove all light. Increase allies&apos; speed and accuracy in the dark.
Tranquil Walk of Peace: Reduces allies&apos; speed and increases their protection.

[h1]Trinkets:[/h1]

Soul of the Royal Aegis: Increases stun and move chance. Reduces chance to be moved or stunned.
King&apos;s Ring: Greatly increases ranged damage. Also increases stress taken.
Rebel&apos;s Greatshield: Greatly increases your protection at the expense of some damage.
Royal Soldier&apos;s Ring: Minorly increases protection.

[h1]Final Thoughts:[/h1]

This is Velstadt, the Royal Aegis from Dark Souls 2. I tried to keep things directly specific to his lore and place in the world, and how I think he&apos;d play in Darkest Dungeon. We don&apos;t have many characters who cleave the front row with CC, so I hoped to fill that niche while giving players a good excuse to do torchless runs. They&apos;re really fun, and I&apos;m not sure that enough players have done it. I hope this mod helps encourage them.


[h1]A Friendly Request:[/h1]

I like feedback. Please keep it to the forums, though-- comments for my mod are intended to be short messages, or urgent ones about bugs. 


[h1]Future plans:[/h1]

-Sir Alonne will be my masterpiece. He&apos;s coming soon.</ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>1391514231</PublishedFileId>
</project>

