<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>D:/Exavault/My Modding Projects/Darkest Dungeon Modding/Fury Class Mod/data/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>Exaelus&apos; Fury Class Mod</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>public</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>0</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>0</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>0</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>Character Mod</Tags>
		<Tags>Class Mod</Tags>
		<Tags>New Class</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>[h1]The Fury Class Mod[/h1]
Supports Color of Madness: Yes
Supports Crimson Court: Yes
Mod Version: 2.2c
Language: English, French , Polish, Korean


[h1]Latest News[/h1]

Mod now supports Color of Madness DLC!

Fury now receives a buff when he crits. (+20% Damage)

2 new Crimson Court trinkets. (Screenshot added!)
1 new Color of Madness trinket. (Screenshot added!)

Color variations added!

Fury has been released!


[h1]Class Introduction[/h1]
Another day, another class. This is my sixth class here on the workshop that i&apos;ve been working on for the past 3 weeks. This mod is pretty much inspired by berserkers and warriors from various games that you are probably thinking of right now, his look was slightly inspired by Darth Malak from the original KOTOR game. The goal with this class was to create a very RNG pure DPS class that can attack multiple times per round based on players luck.

This class has 2 stances, Order and Chaos. You can go into Chaos stance by using &quot;Primal Impulse&quot; it can only be used below 66% health. You can use this same ability to go back to Order stance as long as your health is below 66%. If your health goes above 66% of your maximum health Order stance is automatically activated.

In Order stance, the Fury can increase his protection, debuff enemy damage and stun resistance, as he fights his chance to stun enemies goes up, once his stun chance is high enough, he can stun 2 enemies in the front row.

In Chaos stance, every time the fury attacks he receives an additional free attack that only has an aprox. 40% chance to hit. If that attack hits you get another free attack and lose some health. Your turn is over when your attack misses. In this stance he also builds up bleed skill chance instead of stun skill chance and debuffs enemy bleed resistance and dodge instead of stun resistance, damage and protection. This stance also has a bleed ability that does a decent amount of damage in two rounds and one that amplifies damage done to bleeding targets.

He is a very fun class to play and i think people will enjoy him quite a bit. This class will give opportunities for those &quot;OMG&quot; moments where you get 3 attacks in a row, but the chances of that happening are pretty low. You can expect in most cases to get 2 attacks per round. He also provides free medicinal herbs on every mission and does not like to go to church. As you know balance is very important to me, so don&apos;t hesitate to add me on steam to give feedback and help me make Fury as balanced as he can be. You can also post your feedback in the comment section below. Screenshots are there only for visual effect display, nothing more. 


[h1]Combat Skills[/h1]

Order:
[b] Primal Impulse:[/b] A. Position: 1,2,3,4 / Targets: SELF / Effect: Chaos s., +DMG, +CRIT.
[b] Composed Slash: [/b] A. position: 1,2,3 / Targets 1+2 / Effect: DMG, buff/dbf PROT, +STUN.
[b] Disciplined Thrust: [/b] A. position: 1,2 / Targets 1,2,3 / Effect: DMG, MOVE, +STUN chance, dbf.
[b] Poised Cleave: [/b] A. position: 1,2 / Targets 1+2 / Effect: SELF MARK, DMG, MOVE, STUN, +STUN c.

Chaos:
[b] Primal Impulse:[/b] A. Position: 1,2,3,4 / Targets: SELF / Effect: Order s., +PROT, +DODGE, +HOT
[b] Raging Sunder:[/b] A. Position: 1,2,3 / Targets 1,2 / Effect: DMG, dbf DMGTAKEN r., +BLEED c.
[b] Vicious Rip:[/b] A. Position: 1,2 / Targets: 1,2,3 / Effect: DMG, +DMG on BLEED, +BLEED chance.
[b] Ferocious Laceration:[/b] A. Position: ALL / Targets: 1,2,3,4 / Effect: DMG, BLEED, +BLEED chance.


[h1]Camping Skills[/h1]
[b] Wavering Demeanor: [/b] Chance for +MAX HP / +PROT / +DMG / +CRIT
[b] Staggering Technique: [/b]+MOVE CHANCE / +STUN CHANCE / +BLEED CHANCE
[b] Critical Lesson: [/b]All non-religious party members receive +10% CRIT, +10% ACC
[b] Exhilarating Inspiration:[/b] Entire party receives -20 STRESS, +20% STRESS RESIST

If you find any bugs/glitches or spelling errors please let me know in the comment section below and i will try to address them. I hope you enjoy playing this class as much as i had fun making it and if a lot of people like it, i might make another one.

Here are my other classes if you want to try them out:

[url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=913178378][img]https://i.imgur.com/B8Duftl.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=924245318][img]https://i.imgur.com/a1YoES1.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=934967620][img]https://i.imgur.com/EvnjeGp.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=947715735][img]https://i.imgur.com/wtvL4QS.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=970030269][img]https://i.imgur.com/QX5m0ux.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1138503289][img]https://i.imgur.com/Wccrwn4.png[/img][/url][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1441036778][img]https://i.imgur.com/Ratr9w8.png[/img][/url]


[h1]Support[/h1]
Due to health issues my modding has been put on hold, but If you like what you see and you want me to do more in the future, you can support my mods by donating here:

[url=https://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_s-xclick&amp;hosted_button_id=PC3886U2YM8C6][img]https://i.imgur.com/6qUg1Xz.gif[/img][/url]


Thank you for all the positive feedback and your support, it does motivate me quite a bit!

Special thanks to RedHook for making this great game and giving players the ability to mod it!

Special thanks to &quot;Finezyjny&quot;(Polish), &quot;halfmoon515&quot;(Korean) 
and &quot;Chocostar&quot;(French) for translating my mod.

This mod is not an official Red Hook Studios product or product modification, and Red Hook Studios Inc. is not responsible in any way for changes or damages that may result from using the mod. Furthermore, “Darkest Dungeon” and the Darkest Dungeon logo are trademarks of Red Hook Studios Inc. All content in the game is Copyright Red Hook Studios Inc. All rights reserved.
</ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>1100450515</PublishedFileId>
</project>

