<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort>BARB</ItemDescriptionShort>
	<ModDataPath>C:/Users/T/Desktop/Darkest_Dungeon_Modding/000_X_barbarian/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>Barbarian (Class Mod)</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>public</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>2</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>3</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>24357</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>character mod</Tags>
		<Tags>new class</Tags>
		<Tags>Stun</Tags>
		<Tags>Multi Stun</Tags>
		<Tags>Bleed</Tags>
		<Tags>Guard</Tags>
		<Tags>Riposte</Tags>
		<Tags>Enraged Counterstrike</Tags>
		<Tags>Variable Tiered Buffs</Tags>
		<Tags>Herbs of the Wild Compatible</Tags>
		<Tags>Spider Nests Compatible</Tags>
		<Tags>Pets Compatible</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>V2.3
	
	[h1]July 2019 Update[/h1]
	*NEW! Compatible with [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1779509342][b]Pets (Trinkets + Monster Mod)[/b][/url] Details below.
	*Kegs now have a chance to Heal 1, 2, or 3 HP depending on Vintage!
	
	[h1]Class Description[/h1]
	The Barbarian is a clansmen who enjoys drinking, hunting and feats of strength. In battle, he wields a broadsword or can attack with a ferocious kick. He can harness a frenzied wild swing attack to release his rage, but risks stunning himself and requires a short break before he can do it again. Of course, he also enjoys drinking and good spirits, which brings its own risks and rewards! 
	
	A Barbarian can sometimes release [b]Enraged Counterstrike[/b], an adrenaline rush that grants a one-time-hit counterstrike. Unlike a Man at Arm&apos;s mace, a broadsword is too heavy for quick successive counterattacks, so after one confirmed strike, within an active round, Enraged wears off.
	
	Due to his natural strength, a Barbarian can carry extra shovels and he always brings his personal shovel with him (+1 shovel stack, +1 free shovel per dungeon). He can also carry extra loot (+2 Bust stack size). He will not pray in the Abbey and does not believe in organized religion, but instead reveres nature. He enjoys camping with friends, starting large bonfires for all-night raves, and -- of course -- drinking! Sometimes, he can sniff out Ale in unexpected places.
	
	[img]https://i.imgur.com/NMwikP5.png[/img]

	[h1]Combat Skills[/h1]
	[b]Indomitable Kick[/b]  xxxo oxxx
	Kick the vanguard, try to stun and provoke Enraged Counterstrike
	[b]Steady Slice[/b] xxoo ooxx 
	High accuracy, low damage swing, bonus versus Marked, blocks being Marked
	[b]Reckless Rage[/b]  xxoo ooxx 
	Low accuracy, medium damage swing, chance to Bleed
	[b]Wild Swing[/b]  xoox xoox
	A powerful swing with risks, chance to multi-stun, chance to self-stun, can lower enemy CRIT chance
	[b]Primal Champion[/b]  xooo
	For a short time, protect an ally. Trigger Enraged Counterstrike
	[b]Brutal Focus[/b]  oooo
	Anger can unleash erratic power! Variable tiered buffs.
	[b]Swig of Ale[/b]  oooo 
	Drinking brings risks and rewards. Variable tiered buffs. Chance for minor self heal.
	
	A few skills change parameters with mastery.
	
	[h1]Camping Skills[/h1]
	Melee Weapon Workshop
	Campfire Rave
	Drum Circle For A Hunt
	Solitary Stargazing
	
	[h1]Pets Compatible[/h1]
	[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1779509342][img]https://i.imgur.com/Cb2vcbh.jpg[/img][/url]
	NOW LIVE! Help &quot;Agatha&quot; escape! The Barbarian&apos;s loyal Owl was caged by the Pet Patrol in the [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1779509342][b]Pets (Trinkets + Monster Mod)[/b][/url]. Optional mod.
	
	[h1]Herbs of the Wild Compatible[/h1]
[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1390782905&amp;searchtext=herbs+of+the+wild][img]https://i.imgur.com/Lhn3Whb.jpg[/img][/url]
The Barbarian&apos;s experience in the wild allows him to sometimes discover natural supplies with the optional Herbs of the Wild (HotW) Resource Mod. Barbarians have a chance to identify and harvest wood, mushrooms, fungus, and moss in most areas. In the Warrens, Barbarians have a chance to identify a larger range of helpful Herbs. Carnifex&apos;s [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1390782905&amp;searchtext=herbs+of+the+wild][b]Herbs of the Wild Resource Mod[/b][/url] is recommended (and fun!) but is NOT required. Chance to trigger while interacting with curios or while searching after a battle. NOTE: When loading mods, just place HotW Resource Mod ABOVE/ON TOP OF all participating Class Mods.
[spoiler]Slim chance to find Herbal Trinkets in Weald[/spoiler]

[h1]A Spider Hunter[/h1]
A Barbarian&apos;s training can aid the party against Spiders found in the [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1717651804][b]Spider Nests 2 (Monster Mod)[/b][/url]. The Camping Skill &quot;Drum Circle For a Hunt&quot; has a 25% chance to increase speed against Spiders, and grants Barbarian +15% crushing damage. On long dungeons this will aid your party. Optional mod.
[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1717651804][img]https://i.imgur.com/A1uo7iU.jpg[/img][/url]  
	
	[h1]Class Trinkets[/h1]
	Carved Bone Pipe
	Frayed Raven Feather
	Summer Pale Ale
	The Surly Lager
	Hamlet Dark Brew
	Necklace of Teeth
	Bracelet of Stability
	Blood Fangs Crampon
	Riddle of Steel, set
	Valhala Horn, set
	Hunter&apos;s Corrupted Headband, COM trinket
	Clovis&apos; Head, Collector
	Complete History of the Clans, CC Set
	Dark Magical Heirloom, CC Set
	
	[h1]Quirks[/h1]
	[spoiler]Chance at developing drinking-related quirks:
	Good-Natured Drinker
	Funny Drinker
	Forgetful Drinker
	Clumsy Drinker
	
	[b]Additional Quirks[/b]
	Blessed Bloodline
	Cursed Bloodline
	Eyes Wide Open
	Minor True Seeing[/spoiler]
	
	[h1]Other[/h1]
	New Custom Sounds
	Custom Town Events
	3 New Supply Items [spoiler]Tavern&apos;s Budget Brew, Good N&apos;uff, Rose Label: Barbarian gets one free, and chance to find other Kegs. Chance for +HP, +Healing Received, +CRIT chance, but -Move Resist, -Stun Resist[/spoiler]
	
	[h1]Overstress States[/h1]
	[spoiler]Glorious (Virtue)
	Furious (Affliction)[/spoiler]
	
	[h1]Languages[/h1]
	English, Chinese(S)
	Other languages show English strings
	
	[h1]Playstyle[/h1]
	A versatile stunner, his drinking makes him vunerable to stun, and he has no protection, so keep him healed. Kick, although does no damage, can be a battle changer with its move and stun. Plan when best to use Wild Swing! It has a 2 round cooldown and risks stunning himself. Barbarian&apos;s random tiers of offense and defensive buffs can change the course each battle, prepare then attack in a variety of combos. Good synergy in a variety of groups, like Man at Arms, Houndmaster, Shieldbreaker, and Highwayman. Stay in Ranks 1 or 2 mostly. Note: a few trinkets, skills, and quirks have unlisted side effects.
	
	[h1]Other Classes[/h1]
	Explore the [b]Picaroon, Harlot, Shadow Walker, and Spartan Class Mods[/b]
	
	[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1856292904][img]https://i.imgur.com/5vhllybl.jpg[/img][/url] 
	
	[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1860840141][img]https://i.imgur.com/N3ulOBQl.jpg[/img][/url]
	
	[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1542315540][img]https://i.imgur.com/PL1uROGl.jpg[/img][/url]    
	
	[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1540264875][img]https://i.imgur.com/8xnTd3fl.png[/img][/url]

	[h1]Credits[/h1]
	My third DD class mod and third collobration with [url=https://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198032072324/myworkshopfiles/?appid=262060][b]Kahvipannu[/b][/url] (from Finland) who illustrated the awesome base artwork, most trinkets, and armor and weapon icons! Kahvipannu was inspired by various Barbarian creations. Check out skin-only artwork at [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1530906625][/url]
	
	Additional support artwork by [b]RedDyeNo5[/b], from  Trinket Art Asset Pack.
	
	Coding support by [b]CarifexX, Clair de Lune, O&apos;Nightmare, + Alexis[/b]. Thank you! 
	
	*Thanks to [b]Moonlit Dungeon (MLD)[/b] Community Discord Channel! Support [b]Clair de Lune&apos;s[/b] awesome ambitious MLD project at [url=https://www.patreon.com/ClairDeLuneModding][/url]
	Join the MLD discord at [url=https://discord.gg/VkXB87M][/url]
	*Thanks [b]FrankWest21[/b] for Beta Testing!
	*Chinese(S) Translation by [b]小凯先生[/b]!
	
	[h1]Disclaimer[/h1]
	This item and its contents may not be uploaded on any website, except on Steam under the profile Dem22.This mod is not an official Red Hook Studios product or product modification, and Red Hook Studios Inc. is not responsible in any way for changes or damages that may result from using the mod. Furthermore, “Darkest Dungeon” and the Darkest Dungeon logo are trademarks of Red Hook Studios Inc. All content in the game is Copyright Red Hoo</ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>1600449003</PublishedFileId>
</project>

