<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>C:/Users/T/Desktop/Darkest_Dungeon_Modding/000_X_spartan/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>Spartan (Class Mod)</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>public</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>2</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>7</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>24357</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>character mod</Tags>
		<Tags>new class</Tags>
		<Tags>Defensive</Tags>
		<Tags>Stun</Tags>
		<Tags>Mark</Tags>
		<Tags>Herbs of the Wild Compatible</Tags>
		<Tags>Spider Nests Compatible</Tags>
		<Tags>Pets Compatible</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>V2.7 
	
	[h1]July 2019 Update[/h1]
	*NEW! Korean(A) Translation by [b]Nickel[/b]. Thank you!
	*NEW! Compatible with [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1779509342][b]Pets (Trinkets + Monster Mod)[/b][/url] Details below.
	
	[h1]Class Description[/h1]
	A versatile defensive and support soldier class, the Spartan was raised to be loyal to his state military. He is well educated and instilled with a mantra of duty, discipline, and endurance. Due to his experience with contracts, property deeds, and maps, he can hold 3 extra deeds per inventory slot. He&apos;s willing to die to protect his group.

	[img]https://i.imgur.com/fFzA3N3.png[/img]	
	
	[h1]Combat Skills[/h1]
	Spear Lance
	Shield Slam
	Into the Fray
	Work Together
	Backline Tactics
	Mysterious Viscous Liquid
	Phalanx
	
	Some of his skills grow in reach, duration, or starting location with practice.
	
	[h1]Camping Skills[/h1]
	Candle for Artemis
	Hearty Meal
	Night Watch
	Repack the Supplies
	
	[h1]Pets Compatible[/h1]
	[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1779509342][img]https://i.imgur.com/Cb2vcbh.jpg[/img][/url]
	NOW LIVE! Help find &quot;Warden&quot;, the Spartan&apos;s Pet Armadillo who was taken by the Pet Patrol in the [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1779509342][b]Pets (Trinkets + Monster Mod)[/b][/url]. Optional mod.
	
	[h1]A Spider Hunter[/h1]
A Spartan&apos;s spear is especially effective against Spiders found in the [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1717651804][b]Spider Nests 2 (Monster Mod)[/b][/url]. The Skill &quot;Into the Fray&quot; receives +DMG +ACC +CRIT to pierce 8-legged freaks. Optional mod.
[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1717651804][img]https://i.imgur.com/A1uo7iU.jpg[/img][/url]  

	
	[h1]Herbs of the Wild Compatible[/h1]
[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1390782905&amp;searchtext=herbs+of+the+wild][img]https://i.imgur.com/Lhn3Whb.jpg[/img][/url]
A Spartan&apos;s military training also allows him to find a few helpful natural supplies when using Carnifex&apos;s [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1390782905&amp;searchtext=herbs+of+the+wild][b]Herbs of the Wild Resource Mod[/b][/url] which is recommended (and fun!) but is NOT required. Chance to trigger while interacting with curios or while searching after a battle. Spartans are ONLY trained to identify fruit, flowers, mushrooms, or wood in certain locations. NOTE: When loading mods, just place HotW Resource Mod ABOVE/ON TOP OF all participating Class Mods.
[spoiler]Slim chance to find Herbal Trinkets in Cove[/spoiler]
	
	[h1]Trinkets[/h1]
	Bracer of Speed
	Legion Necklace
	Mysterious Powder
	Centurion Cloak
	Page from Ancient Warfare Book
	Ares Spear, Set
	Ares Shield, Set
	Bioluminescent Shield, COM
	Aged Corinthian Helm, CC Set
	Winged-Horse Coin, CC Set
	Leonidas&apos; Head, Collector
	
	[h1]Roles[/h1]
	Defensive, Marking, Low Bleed, Minor Heal, Stunner
	
	[h1]Other[/h1]
	12 Color/Helmet/Armor Variations [6 light armor (A-F) and 6 full body armor (G-L)]
	Custom sounds
	Town Event
	Custom Virtue Protectorate
	Custom Heirloom Inventory Stack Limit (Deeds 9)
	New Quirks +Arterial Authority -Royal Hemophilia
	
	[h1]Languages[/h1]
	English, Chinese(S), Korean(A)
	Other languages show English strings
	
	[h1]Compatibility[/h1]
	Shieldbreaker not required.
	Color of Madness Yes
	Crimson Court Yes
	[note: Should work okay without DLCs, since the trinkets are segregated]
	
	[h1]Playstyle[/h1]
	Spartan can be used in a variety of ways, with some longer battles and an element of chance too. Can fit into a variety of party configurations, including Mark (Arbalest, Bounty Hunter), Bleed (Houndmaster, Flagellant) and Shuffle (Grave Robber, Highwayman, Thrall) teams. He gets better at some skills the more he progresses, but some skills move him around. He is more defensive and support. He has a very weak, risky heal. Willing to sacrifice himself (lower death blow resist). Sometimes critical hits will relieve a little group stress. Defensive in nature with helpful camping skills.
	
	[h1]Thanks[/h1]
	JAN 2019 Update: 6 new breastplate designs! The #1 top request! Awesome artwork by [b]Kahvipannu![/b] who gave permission for a  full class! Some icons adapted from other artwork and trinkets. If you don&apos;t want a custom class, play with original skin-only version at https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1513257858 or the armoed skin-only version at https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1590465899
	
	*Thanks to DD Modding community. I have greatly enjoyed this game with their amazing contributions, including Exaelus, Hellintz, Nodappjung, CarnifeX, Clair de Lune, ActionJack, Maester Silvio, Poljanan, Mhnlo, Tasty, Marvin Seo + O&apos;Nightmare! 
	*Chinese(S) Translation by [b]小凯先生[/b]!
	*Korean(A) Translation by [b]Nickel[/b]!
	
	[h1]Other Classes[/h1]
	Explore the [b]Picaroon, Harlot, Shadow Walker, and Barbarian Class Mods[/b]
	
	[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1856292904][img]https://i.imgur.com/5vhllybl.jpg[/img][/url] 

	[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1860840141][img]https://i.imgur.com/N3ulOBQl.jpg[/img][/url]
	
	[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1542315540][img]https://i.imgur.com/PL1uROGl.jpg[/img][/url]   
	
	[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1600449003][img]https://i.imgur.com/T5eLLYUl.png[/img][/url]

	[h1]Running out of Mod Space?[/h1]
	Just delete unwanted color variations! search for folder 1540264875 &gt; Heroes &gt; Spartan &gt; Delete entire letter folders. 6 light armors are A-F and 6 full body armor are G-L. We are working on compressed PNG, still on the TO DO list though!
	
	[h1]Disclaimer[/h1]
	This item and its contents may not be uploaded on any website, except on Steam under the profile Dem22. This mod is not an official Red Hook Studios product or product modification, and Red Hook Studios Inc. is not responsible in any way for changes or damages that may result from using the mod. Furthermore, “Darkest Dungeon” and the Darkest Dungeon logo are trademarks of Red Hook Studios Inc. All content in the game is Copyright Red Hook Studios Inc. All rights reserved.
	</ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>1540264875</PublishedFileId>
</project>

