<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>C:/Users/T/Desktop/Darkest_Dungeon_Modding/000_X_shadow_walker/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>Shadow Walker (Class Mod)</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>public</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>2</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>6</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>24357</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>character mod</Tags>
		<Tags>new class</Tags>
		<Tags>Stealth</Tags>
		<Tags>Shuffler</Tags>
		<Tags>Blight</Tags>
		<Tags>Treasure Hunter</Tags>
		<Tags>Herbs of the Wild Compatible</Tags>
		<Tags>Spider Nests Compatible</Tags>
		<Tags>Pets Compatible</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>V2.7 
	
	[h1]August 2019 Update[/h1]
	*NEW Russian Translation by HjordisTBM
	*Compatible with [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1779509342][b]Pets (Trinkets + Monster Mod)[/b][/url] Details below.

	[h1]Class Description[/h1]
	The Shadow Walker is an agile ninja and treasure hunter, with mysterious connections to the black market. His contact pays him a nice bonus for fine jade and unique antiques. The Shadow Walker eventually hand-crafted a travel case to store additional gemstones (9 jade stones and 2 trapazohedrons). In addition, his keen eyes can often spot loot others would miss. 
	
	He can attack with his katanna, venomous shurikens, or entangle opponents with a chain. He can also slap or pinch enemies. He can slide into the shadows and tries to attain a healing meditative state. He usually carries two small, glass globes that are Smoke Bombs which can reveal stealthy monsters. His treasure hunting skills and black market connections make him a valuable companion.
	
	[img]https://i.imgur.com/yjCMDFG.png[/img]
	
	[h1]Combat Skills[/h1]
	Ken-Jutsu (Katana Strike)
	Kiai-Jutsu (Chain Entangle)
	Kuji-Kiri (Gesture Slap)
	Venom Tipped Shurikens
	Blood Boil
	Pressure Point
	Shadow Slide
	
	Some of his skills grow in reach, duration, or starting location with practice.
	
	[h1]Camping Skills[/h1]
	Dark Meditation 
	Sabotage
	Assassination
	Guerilla Warfare
	
	[h1]Pets Compatible[/h1]
	[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1779509342][img]https://i.imgur.com/Cb2vcbh.jpg[/img][/url]
	NOW LIVE! Help free &quot;Sting&quot;, the Shadow Walker&apos;s Pet Spider who was captured by the Pet Patrol in the [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1779509342][b]Pets (Trinkets + Monster Mod)[/b][/url]. Optional mod.
	
	[h1]Herbs of the Wild Compatible[/h1]
	[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1390782905&amp;searchtext=herbs+of+the+wild][img]https://i.imgur.com/Lhn3Whb.jpg[/img][/url]
	A Shadow Walker has extensive training as an herbalist: the study of botany and plants for medicinal and other uses. This allow a Shadow Walker to take full advantage of Carnifex&apos;s [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1390782905&amp;searchtext=herbs+of+the+wild][b]Herbs of the Wild Resource Mod[/b][/url] which is recommended (and fun!) but is NOT required. It&apos;s especially helpful if you use Shadow Walker as your item collector. NOTE: When loading mods, just place HotW Resource Mod ABOVE/ON TOP OF all participating Class Mods.
[spoiler]Slim chance to find Herbal Trinkets in any of the four core areas.[/spoiler]

[h1]A Spider Hunter[/h1]
A Shadow Walker is skilled with pressure points and can help kill Spiders found in the [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1717651804][b]Spider Nests 2 (Monster Mod)[/b][/url]. The Camping Skill &quot;Assasination&quot; grants him a 22% damage versus spiders for 4 battles. Incidentally, the Shadow Walker has been searching for his lost Pet Spider &quot;Sting.&quot; Optional mod.
[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1717651804][img]https://i.imgur.com/A1uo7iU.jpg[/img][/url]  
	
	[h1]Trinkets[/h1]
	Vial of Good Memories
	Book of Poems
	Heavy Chain
	Dark Incense
	Assassination Contract
	Elio&apos;s Last Boots, Set
	Elio&apos;s Last Gloves, Set
	&quot;Constant Craving&quot; Katanna, COM
	Master&apos;s Mask, CC Set
	Master&apos;s Razor Bracers, CC Set
	Elio&apos;s Head, Collector
	Shadow Walker&apos;s Ring
	Blessed Chain
	
	[h1]Roles[/h1]
	Stealth, Shuffler, Blight, Treasure Hunter, Marking, Stunner
	
	[h1]Other[/h1]
	Custom supply item (Smoke Bomb)
	Custom sounds
	6 Color/Character Variations (A-F)
	Town Event
	Treasure Hunter Bonus: Hunts for unique item (Jade Chess Piece), slim chance at other loot too.
	Custom Gem Inventory Stack Limit (Jade/9 : Trapezohedron/2)
	New Quirks +Skilled Toxicologist -Toxic Hypersensitivity
	
	[h1]Compatability[/h1]
	Color of Madness Yes
	Crimson Court Yes
	[note: Should work okay without DLCs, since the trinkets are segregated]
	
	[h1]Languages[/h1]
	English, Chinese(S), Russian
	Other languages show English strings
	
	[h1]Playstyle[/h1]
	Shadow Walker can work with a variety of playstyles and other class configurations and gains extra loot for town and hero upgrades. He is not a huge damage dealer but can also stun, blight, and has a unique riposte. He works well with Graverobbers and teams that continually reposition. Nimble. Random stealth. Critical hits trigger a short Riposte. Rare meditative state group healing. His treasure hunting income can be a huge help.
	
	[h1]Other Classes[/h1]
	Explore the [b]Harlot, Picaroon, Spartan, and Barbarian Class Mods[/b]
	
	[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1860840141][img]https://i.imgur.com/N3ulOBQl.jpg[/img][/url]
	
	[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1856292904][img]https://i.imgur.com/5vhllybl.jpg[/img][/url] 
	
	[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1540264875][img]https://i.imgur.com/8xnTd3fl.png[/img][/url]   
	
	[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1600449003][img]https://i.imgur.com/T5eLLYUl.png[/img][/url]
	
	[h1]Credits[/h1]
	*[b]Kahvipannu[/b] created the awesome artwork  inspired by a ninja character. Working together, we&apos;ve also added other art variations! Play with original skin-only version at https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1502280297

	*Chinese(S) Translation by [b]小凯先生[/b]
	*Russian Translation by [b]HjordisTBM[/b]
	
	[h1]Disclaimer[/h1]
	This mod is not an official Red Hook Studios product or product modification, and Red Hook Studios Inc. is not responsible in any way for changes or damages that may result from using the mod. Furthermore, “Darkest Dungeon” and the Darkest Dungeon logo are trademarks of Red Hook Studios Inc. All content in the game is Copyright Red Hook Studios Inc. All rights reserved.
	</ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>1542315540</PublishedFileId>
</project>

