<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>e:/DDmods/ReaverClassMod/data/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>Reaver Class Mod</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>public</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>1</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>5</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>23886</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>Reaver</Tags>
		<Tags>New Class</Tags>
		<Tags>Hero</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>[h1]New in version 1.4[/h1]
	Replaced Take Aim with Expose.
	Nerfed ACC buff, now skill is used on enemy and bypasses stealth.
	Supports English, Polish, Spanish and Russian languages.
	
	[h1]Introduction[/h1]
	Hey everyone! This is my third class mod i&apos;ve been working on for past 3 weeks. Reaver is backline damager who can also support his team with buffs. 
	My point was to create something with features of arbalest and man-at-arms at one time.
	His high CRIT and medium damage make him powerful in focusing one enemy, but he also has an multiple targets skill.
	
	Also, it&apos;s my first class where EVERY sprite is custom and i hope you guys will like it. For now he has 4 colours.
	There is much work with balance and sprites so any feedback is welcome.
	
	P.S. When i almost finished making him, i noticed, that Aimed Shot and Buck shot skill name is same as Musketeer&apos;s. I edited Reaver skill&apos;s IDs and they will not conflict with each other.
	
	
	[h1]Lore[/h1]
	 One of many outlaws and bandits from the &quot;Brigands Brigade&quot; hired by Your Ancestor. Reaver is expert tracker and spend much time plundering roads and robbing travelers.
	 Unlike most other Brigands, Reaver rejects leadership of Vvulf, saying that he has abandoned his duty for Ancestor&apos;s Family. When he heard,
	 that Ancestor&apos;s Heir returned to the Hamlet, he realized that he can continue his service to Ancestor&apos;s house and finally take revenge on Vvulf, making himself rich in the process, of course.
	 
	 [h1]Trinkets[/h1]
	 Marksman Gloves: +2 CRT Ranged skills, +5 ACC Ranged skills, -20% DMG Melee skills. (Very Common)
	 Raider&apos;s Mask: +20% DMG Melee skills, +2 CRT Melee skills. (Uncommon)
	 Lucky Coin: +4 DODGE, +1 CRIT, -5% MAX HP. (Uncommon)
	 Looted Amulet: -15% Stress, +8 DODGE, +30% Bleed Resist, +30% Blight Resist, -6% Death Blow Resist, -33% Healing Received. (Rare)
	 Brigands Emblem: +40% Bleed Skill Chance, +35% DMG vs. Human, +2 SPD, +15% Stress. (Very Rare)
	 
	 [h1]Skills[/h1]
	 Aimed Shot: From pos. 34 to enemy 1234. Basic attack, has a good crit chance.
	 Buckshot: From pos. 234 to enemy 2+3+4. Lowered damage, causes targets to bleed.
	 Raid Commander: From pos. 1234. Buffs ally&apos;s DMG for 8/12/16/20/25%, SPD for 3/3/4/5/5 and ACC for 3/6/9/12/15.
	 Stand and Deliver: From pos. 123 to enemy 12. Reaver&apos;s only melee attack. Average bleed, as well as debuffing target&apos;s PROT.
	 Expose: From pos. 34. to enemy 1234. Buffs Reaver&apos;s ACC and CRIT. De-stealthes enemy.
	 Return Fire: From pos. 12 to enemy 123. Hits random target, moves Reaver back by 2 and activates Riposte for 2 Rounds.
	 Cowering Fire: From pos. 4. Guards ally for 3 rounds, activates Riposte and buffs Reaver&apos;s SPD.

 	 [h1]Camping Skills[/h1]
	 As well as Encourage, Pep talk and First aid, Reaver also has Gallows Humor(similiar to Highwayman and Grave Robber).
	 Reinforce Armor: +20% PROT, +10 Move Resist, -3 SPD. (Cost - 3)
	 Night Watch: Prevents Nighttime Ambush, -15% party surprised, +15% monsters surprised. (Cost - 4)
	 Adjust Aim: Self: +20 ACC. (Cost - 2)
	 
	 
	 If you find any bugs or syntax errors(english is not my native language), please let me know.
	 
	 [h1] Credit [/h1]
	 
	 Red Hook Studios for Darkest Dungeon
	 Huge thanks to [URL=http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198238010754]Vanguard[/URL] for allowing me to use some of his lines from the Nexus Forums for class.
	 Also thanks to [URL=http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198071171427]Phreeze [/URL] for checking text files for errors and redacting them!
	 Thanks to [URL=http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198173169214][ITS] Steve[/URL] for translating to Spanish.
	 Thanks to [URL=http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198065331266/] byzsla [/URL] for translating mod to Polish language.
	 Thanks to [URL=http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198049989594] lazyrus [/URL] for first version of Russian language/ Спасибо [URL=http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198049989594] lazyrus [/URL] за черновой перевод на русский язык, без него я бы не перевел мод.
	
	 </ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>948931447</PublishedFileId>
</project>

