<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>C:/Users/Sean/Desktop/Darkest Dungeon Mods/Cataclysmic Templar/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>Paladin 2.0</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>public</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>3</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>0</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>0</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>Class Mod</Tags>
		<Tags>WoW</Tags>
		<Tags>New Class</Tags>
		<Tags>Crusader</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>HUGE UPDATE for CoM! New Palettes, too!

[h1] Class Introduction:[/h1]
A pious knight, he supports his allies through faith-based spells while assaulting the enemy. He performs best in the front 2 rows, although his support spells can be cast from any position, and he can judge his enemies to move forward. His basic strikes empower other abilities, making him more effective as the battle progresses.

His support spells come with a cost. Enemies will notice the Paladin&apos;s altruism, and they will focus upon him to stop it.

[h1]Art Credit:[/h1] Huge thanks to Lunaros for drawing the comic and equipment. Here&apos;s a link to some of her work: https://lunaros.deviantart.com

Huge thanks to Bluezald for remaking the character animations. Here&apos;s a link to his work: https://www.bluezald.com/

Thanks to byzsla for the Polish translation.


[h1] Paladin Comic:[/h1]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/bEdxvp3.jpg[/img]

[h1] Combat Skills: [/h1]

[b]Passive - Avenging Wrath[/b]: When virtued, gain bonus damage and healing on relevant abilities.

[b]Crusader Strike[/b]: Used from ranks 1 or 2. Hits ranks 1 or 2. Empowers Holy Light and Divine Storm.
[b]Holy Light[/b]: Used from any rank. Targets any ally. Weak heal. Marks Paladin. 
[b]Judgment[/b]: Used from ranks 3 or 4. Hits any enemy for less damage. Empowers Holy Light and Divine Storm. Pulls the Paladin forward 2 spaces. Bonus damage on stunned target. Can get a trinket to remove the pull.
[b]Sacred Shield[/b]: Used from any rank. Targets any ally and marks them. Block effect. Buffs healing received &amp; cleanses blight and bleed.
[b]Divine Storm[/b]: Used from ranks 1 or 2. Hits ranks 1 &amp; 2. Penetrates some armor, but not all.
[b]Blessing of Freedom[/b]: Used from any rank. Clears stun. Makes immune to move effects. Marks the Paladin. Can use once per turn, 3 turns per fight.
[b]Hammer of Justice[/b]: Used from ranks 1, 2, or 3. Hits ranks 1 and 2. Stuns. Marks the Paladin.

[h1]Camp Skills:[/h1]

In addition to the normal camp skills, the Paladin has...

[b]Eye for an Eye[/b]: The Paladin gains 25% reflection and 25% increased damage on himself. Increases HP by 20% too.
[b]Hope[/b]: The Paladin grants everyone Virtue chance.
[b]Vengeance[/b]: The Paladin gains a crit bonus and accuracy.
[b]Cleanse[/b]: The Paladin removes poison and disease from himself and another.

[h1]Trinkets:[/h1]

[b]Seal of Blood[/b]: The Paladin gains damage, crit, and accuracy at the expense of 4 damage per offensive action.
[b]Seal of Insight[/b]: The Paladin does not pull on Judgment. Heavy loss of melee damage, but strong ranged damage crit buff. Strong healing buff.
[b]Seal of Command:[/b] The Paladin gains strong chance to stun, and extra damage on stunned enemies.
[b]Wistful Memory:[/b] The Paladin gains strong Virtue chance and stress resistance.
New with CoM! [b]Seal of Justice:[/b] The Paladin takes 50% more damage, but reflects 50% damage taken.
New with CoM! [b]Seal of Sanctuary:[/b] The Paladin gains health and protection at the expense of damage. His helpful spells guard targets.

[h1]Final Thoughts:[/h1]

For those of you who don&apos;t recognize any of this, it&apos;s a mod based upon the Retribution Paladin spec of WoW: Wrath of the Lich King, though the armor comes from Cataclysm. I played arenas at high levels for a few expansions, and this character is based upon my experience there as well as some character lore.

I&apos;ve made it lore-friendly, though. All&apos;s well in that regard. 

I like feedback. Please keep it to the forums, though-- comments for my mod are intended to be short messages, or urgent ones about bugs. 

[h1]Future plans:[/h1] 

-Sir Alonne is coming.
-Maybe a WoW Mage focused on low damage, extreme set-up burst damage, and tons of utility.
-Possibly an arena mod, though this is now a low priority with CoM here.

</ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>1332249328</PublishedFileId>
</project>

