<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>C:/Users/Jon/Documents/DD Mods/Warden V1.0/data/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>The Warden Class Mod</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>public</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>1</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>0</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>0</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>Warden</Tags>
		<Tags>New Class</Tags>
		<Tags>Crusader</Tags>
		<Tags>Custom Skin</Tags>
		<Tags>Balanced</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>
---- MANUAL INSTALLATION (FIXES ALL BUGS) ----
1. Navigate to your workshop folder here: C:\Program Files (x86)\Steam\steamapps\workshop\content\262060\906316834

2. Copy the effects, heroes, localization, raid, and upgrades folders.

3. Navigate to your Darkest Dungeon directorty here: C:\Program Files (x86)\Steam\steamapps\common\DarkestDungeon

4. Paste the copied folders here.

5. Go into the localization folder in your Darkest Dungeon directory and run the localization.bat file.

6. Play!

---- SKILLS -----
Rend: Rend the enemy with a well-placed chop from the Warden&apos;s blade.
Feint: Retreat to the backline command position, debuffing the target and dealing good damage all at once!
Pommel Slam: Using all available strength; sweep your pommel forward as you move, dazing the enemies, but exhausting yourself slightly as well.
Judgement: Blind the enemies with your judgement, lowering their accuracy and doing light damage.
Rallying Banner: Display a proud image and demoralize your enemies, lowering their ability to withstand your party&apos;s attacks by lowering DODGE and PROT! 
Steadfast Banner: Encourage your ally to stand fast, buffing them and lowering their stress.
Commanding Banner: Deliver a small heal as well as varied buffs to a target, and order them to go forth and destroy!

---- INSTALLATION ----
1. Subscribe.
2. That&apos;s it, yo.

---- THANKS ----
Thanks for downloading and I hope you enjoy the class! Please report any bugs to me in the posts as soon as they happen as well as the situation. I&apos;ve run with it quite a bit and haven&apos;t encountered any crash issues yet. All bugs seem to be entirely sprite-based and only occur during dungeon crawling. 

Also, thanks to Rocktopus64 on the Nexus for making the skin art available here.
</ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>906316834</PublishedFileId>
</project>

