<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>C:/Users/Vivian (Juni)/Desktop/Darkest Dungeon Mods/Steel Driver Mod/STEEL DRIVER/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>The Steel-Driver Class Mod</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>public</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>0</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>0</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>0</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>Class mod</Tags>
		<Tags>New hero</Tags>
		<Tags>New class</Tags>
		<Tags>Color of Madness</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>[i]They called him a steel drivin&apos; man...[/i]

[b]------------------------------------------[/b]
If you liked The Steel Driver, please try out my other mod(s)!
[b]The Mambo[/b], [b]The Harlot[/b]
[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1865154690][img]https://i.imgur.com/KVDs6td.png[/img][/url] [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1860840141][img]https://i.imgur.com/3oWryVu.png[/img][/url]

[b]Backstory
------------------------------------------[/b]

&quot;I may have...[i]neglected[/i] to tell that insipid Miller about how I sold the outskirts of his expendable land to the local government for some much needed financial gain. The bureaucrats sent these servants of steel - these gandy dancers - to level the uneven ground with explosives in order to lay the groundwork for a railroad that would inspire better trade routes. By foul luck, the section hands arrived the day where the explosion would not come from their sticks of dynamite but from the stars, leaving one man as the lone survivor. &quot; [i] - The Ancestor[/i]

[b]How to Play the Steel Driver (IMPORTANT READ) 
------------------------------------------[/b]

The Steel Driver is a frontline tank &amp; offensive hero that comes with [b] 3 custom virtues &amp; 2 custom afflictions (charted in the Discussion below) meaning any trinkets or abilities that increase virtue chance [u]will NOT work [/u] on the Steel Driver.[/b]

The Steel Driver is a hero that the player may want to hit his resolve check since his Virtue chance set at 75% &amp; his Affliction chance set to 25%. Like the folktale he hails from, when the Steel Driver is pushed to his limits you can count on him pulling off the nigh-on-impossible. [i]However[/i], like the folktale he hails from, being virtuous is extremely stressful &amp; will most likely stay virtuous for only a little amount of time until his stress meter hits 200 &amp; resets. The player should also be aware of the 25% chance of getting SD’s affliction which will make him a [u]punishing[/u] detriment to the team, but on the flip-side, this is a stress-relieving moment for him &amp; will most likely not last too long until his stress meter resets.

[b]Role &amp; Abilities 
------------------------------------------[/b]

[u]Hammer Time[/u]  -  Use: XXOO [b]I[/b] Target: OOXX
[i]I&apos;ll die with this hammer in my hand![/i]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/ltlGsqp.png[/img]

Steel Driver&apos;s basic single melee attack, + DMG  vs. Husks, Armor Piercing.

[u]Steamroller[/u]  -  Use: OOXX [b]I[/b] Target: OXXX
[i]This train ain&apos;t got any brakes![/i]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/YDEg1JA.png[/img]

Steel Driver charges forward two spaces with the speed of a locomotive to knock the Position 1 enemy back three spaces along low chance to stun. Armor Piercing.

[u]Strike the Earth[/u]  -  Use: XOOO [b]I[/b] Target: OOOO
[i]I make the Earth quake![/i]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/7rJDusK.png[/img]

Steel Driver strikes the ground with such force that a crystal stalagmite breaks through the Earth&apos;s crust to impale a Random Target. Buff: +20% DMG to Strike the Earth for 5 rds.

[u]Bring the Thunder[/u]  -  Use: XOOO [b]I[/b] Target: XXXX
[i]I&apos;ve got thunder in my bones![/i]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/5I01R8Y.png[/img]

Steel Driver calls upon the thunder in heaven giving him +PROT &amp; +CRIT for the entire battle while also marking himself.

[u]Reconstruction[/u]  -  Use: OOOO [b]I[/b] Target: XXXX
[i]I can feel the crystal creepin&apos; through my veins...[/i]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/P8GgIPs.png[/img]

Steel Driver’s crystal heals his wounds but at the cost of great pain &amp; stress. Cures Blight &amp; Bleed.

[u]Crystalline Conductor[/u]  -  Use: XOOO [b]I[/b] Target: XOOO
[i]The Comet...plants...another...seed...[/i]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/7YQc9SG.png[/img]

Steel Driver summons a crystalline growth to appear on a single enemy which will always burst after 2 rds. The burst will do minor DMG to the enemy as well as debuff their PROT &amp; SPD. The Steel Driver is given 1 aegis &amp; [b]the ability then has a 3 round cooldown.[/b]

[u]Crystal Shrapnel[/u]  -  Use: XOOO [b]I[/b] Target: O-O-O-O
[i]Fire in the hole![/i]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/5RYgJ9M.png[/img]

Steel Driver summons a crystal “bomb” on the enemy’s side [b](one enemy slot must be open)[/b] &amp; will do AoE DMG &amp; -ACC/Blight Resist debuff to enemies when the crystal is hit by the next attack(by either an ally or himself). Clears corpses.

[b]Camping Skills
------------------------------------------[/b]

[u]Chip Off The Ol’ Block[/u]
[i]No matter how much I chip away, it always grows back...[/i]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/uRYW8pN.png[/img]
Time Cost: 1

Effect: Produces 2 Comet Shards, -10% hp from Steel Driver, +5 stress

[u]Work Song  [/u]
[i]Watch Me. You need to keep in rhythm when you swing.[/i]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/kfJYgOz.png[/img]
Time Cost: 4

Effect: [b]One Ally[/b] of +15 ACC &amp; +25% DMG to Melee skills for 4 battles.

[u]Spaced Out[/u]
[i]The Comet leaks secrets into my mind…[/i]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/aafUPve.png[/img]
Time Cost: 3

Effect: [b](Steel Driver only)[/b] +20% DMG, +20% stress received, ignores stealth for 4 battles

[u]Back to Center[/u]
[i]This Comet ain’t gon’ control me. This Comet ain’t gon’ control me... [/i]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/fqOWqxb.png[/img]
Time Cost: 2

Effect: [b](Steel Driver only)[/b] - Removes Mortality Debuffs plus (40%) - 40 stress or (60% chance) +15% stress received for 4 Battles

[b]Other Information
------------------------------------------[/b]
~ Steel Driver [u]REQUIRES[/u] the CoM DLC in order to not crash.
~ Steel Driver is not religious 
~ District: Outsiders Bonfire 
~CRIT Bonus: +35% Healing Received 
~ Provisions: None
~ The Steel Driver is inspired by the African American folkhero, John Henry
~ Steel Driver&apos;s canon default name is Henry
~ This mod comes with 11 class-specific trinkets: vanilla, all DLCS &amp; [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1689234891]Sunward Isles[/url].
~ He has a town event so you can get him immediately.
~ This mod is fully compatible with all 3 DLCs
~ Steel Driver now supports Simple Chinese  &amp; English but message me if you wish to include your language in localization! 

[b]Credits 
------------------------------------------[/b]

~Concept Art/Main Art Assets: [url=https://www.artstation.com/ti-rex]Vladimir Slobtsov[/url], [url=https://twitter.com/RedDyeNo5]RedDyeNo5[/url]
~Animators: [url=https://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198064185426]GoldenYak[/url], [url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/slightlystartled]A Slightly Startled Seal[/url]
~Coders: [url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/slightlystartled]A Slightly Startled Seal[/url], [url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/shaylockholmes]Shay[/url]
~Additional Help: [url=https://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561197968046008]Baybot[/url]
~SFX Work: EbonyBetty, [url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/shaylockholmes]Shay[/url]
~Playtesters:  [url=https://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198138603871]TheGreenDigi[/url]
~Localization: nbb (Chinese), Aproksiy (Russian)

There are so many people to thank, but Steel Driver wouldn&apos;t have been possible had it not been for the wonderful folks over at [url=https://discordapp.com/invite/VkXB87M]Moonlit Dungeon Discord server[/url]. Please join if you&apos;re interested in making your own DD mod or if you want to stay updated on future upcoming mods.

[b]Tip Jar
------------------------------------------[/b]
Steel Driver is, by no means, my last Darkest Dungeon mod &amp; they will always remain 100% free. However, if you&apos;d like to help with the process, see the mods done quicker, or leave me a nice kudos; please consider leaving a tip! It would mean the world &amp; really help out a novice (but hopefully upcoming) gamedev! 

[url=https://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_s-xclick&amp;hosted_button_id=MBP3LA2EGH4GS&amp;source=url][img]https://i.imgur.com/k53FXKP.gif[/img][/url]

[b]Legal Stuff
------------------------------------------[/b]
This item &amp; its content are </ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>1999848432</PublishedFileId>
</project>

