<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>C:/Users/T/Desktop/Darkest_Dungeon_Modding/000_X_rescuer/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>Rescuer (Class Mod)</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>public</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>1</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>3</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>24357</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>character mod</Tags>
		<Tags>new class</Tags>
		<Tags>Healer</Tags>
		<Tags>Stress Healer</Tags>
		<Tags>Riposte</Tags>
		<Tags>Bleed</Tags>
		<Tags>Spider Nests Compatible</Tags>
		<Tags>Pets Compatible</Tags>
		<Tags>Herbs of the Wild Compatible</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>v1.3
	[img]https://i.imgur.com/96V6892.jpg[/img]
	
	*NEW! ChineseS Translation by 梦灵 + nbb!
	*NEW! [url=https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ks8IGUHK5ZY]Russian video review[/url] shows trinkets, skills, quirks
	
	[h1]Class Description[/h1]
	Educated as a military medic in the mountains, the [b]Rescuer[/b] and his faithful [b]Saint Bernard[/b] and [b]Pyrenees[/b] seek to aid those in need! Trained in medical sciences, he can heal health or stress, and cure medical conditions (bleed, stun, horror, blight). Using Nitrous Oxide heals group stress, but risks stunning himself. He has a unique rejuvenating hypnosis technique that can cleanse &quot;battle-limited&quot; skills from a teammate. In addition, the hounds can help with attacks, counter attacks, and bleeds. The Rescuer&apos;s self sacrificing nature is also his greatest weakness: his personal health is extremely low! With the right trinkets, his healing could match a Vestal&apos;s. The Rescuer may become your faithful companion.

	[img]https://i.imgur.com/IPyWDfv.jpg[/img]
	
	[h1]Combat Skills[/h1]
	[b]First Aid:[/b] From 3 or 2. Single Medium Heal with variable secondary effects. Highest chance to Cure Bleed, followed by Horror, while Blight is hardest for him to cure. Self stress heal.
	[b]Tonic Mix:[/b] From 3, 2 or 1. Party Low Heal with variable secondary effects. High chance to cure Stun, average chance to cure Bleed. Self stress heal.
	[b]Nitrous Oxide:[/b] From 4, 3, or 2. Medium-High Party-Other Stress Heal. Chance to Self Stun.
	[b]Motivational Hypnosis:[/b] All Ranks. Refreshes &quot;Uses Per Battles&quot; Skills on the target. Party buff Critical Up and increases Rescuer&apos;s heal or stress heal for next turn. 2 Use Limit. The Refresh effect can&apos;t target self. Self stress heal.  
	[b]Stay Away![/b] Staff attack from 2 or 1 with chance to Push enemy ranks 1 or 2 positions back. Also moves Rescuer Back 1. Chance to Stun Marked target. Extra critical chance v. Stunned target.
	[b]Herding Tactics:[/b] From 2 or 1, targets 2+3. Dogs attack and trigger Riposte. This is an evolving skill which gains starting ranks and/or targets with practice. Riposte effect can Bleed + Double DMG vs Spiders (Spider Hunter Ability).
	[b]Follow the Track:[/b] All Ranks to Any Rank. Single target medium-high dog attack. Extra Damage v. Bleeding target. Chance to Bleed Marked Targets. 

	[h1]Roles[/h1]
	[b]Primary Role:[/b] Stress Healer, Healer
	[b]Secondary Roles:[/b] Cleansing, Low Bleed, Riposte, Hybrid Roles (See Playstyle for Kits)	
	
	[h1]Camping Skills[/h1]
	[img]https://i.imgur.com/0HVQWf8.jpg[/img]
	Rescuer comes with 7 new camping skills that cost between 1-6 hours. The Hounds are happy to help too, when they can.
	[b]Scent in the Air[/b] 1
	[b]Hound Howl[/b] 2
	[b]Medical Studies[/b] 3
	[b]Canine Vigil[/b] 4
	[b]Apply Poultice[/b] 4
	[b]Reinforce Training[/b] 5
	[b]Vocation of Service[/b] 6
	
		[h1]Trinkets[/h1]
	[img]https://i.imgur.com/sMjFvsF.jpg[/img]
[b]Hypercubic Respirator
Advanced Diploma
Service Decoration
&quot;The 10&quot; (Acupuncture Needles)
&quot;Epinone&quot; the Pheasant (in Pets Mod)
Barry’s Barrel
Improvised Orthopedics Guide
Pyrenean Wool Dog Collar
Feathered Dog Toy
Surgical Instruments
Gas Canister
Stethoscope[/b]

	[h1]Quirks[/h1]
	[spoiler]A few quirks [b]permanently[/b] modify select skill effects. Discovery awaits!
	Advanced Medical Training
	Monks’ Body
	Monks’ Mind
	Pressure to Succeed
	Herding Master
	Expert Hunter[/spoiler]
	
	[h1]Notes[/h1]
	* Limit 1 Rescuer in party
	* 6 color variants
	* New Racetrack District: Houndmaster is eligible too
	* Cannon names: Einstein, Alina (Saint Bernard) + Gurutz (Pyrenees)
	* Chance at new Virtue [spoiler]Humanitarian[/spoiler]
	* 1 Free provision: Each dungeon grants 1 Monks of St. Bernard&apos;s Hospice Brandy (Extra Old): [spoiler]+25 CRIT chance (1 rd)(Effect Will Not Stack). Carry limit +1, Rescuer extra stack limit +1 (2 total)[/spoiler]
	* Compatible with [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1779509342][b]Pets Mod[/b][/url]
	* Will not party with Succubus
	* Custom party names below
	* Includes Collector&apos;s Head + Optional COM, CC, Sunward Isles Trinkets
	
	[h1]Playstyle[/h1]
	Jump right in and play however you want! Rescuer prefers Ranks 2 + 3, but can be used in Rank 1, while Rank 4 is his least favorite. His weakness is low health; he is VERY vulnerable to critical attacks! Starting kit ideas: 
	[spoiler][b]The Doctor:[/b] (defense) Healing + Stress medical skills: Pick First Aid, Tonic Mix, Nitrous Oxide, and Follow the Tracks (Place in Rank 2/3)
	[b]Team Build:[/b] (hybrid) Pick 1 Healing. Nitrous Oxide, Motivational Hypnosis. 1 Attack. (Rank 1/2)
	[b]Hunting Hounds:[/b] (offense) Staff and Hound Attacks: Pick Stay Away, Herding Tactics, Follow the Tracks. Plus 1 Healing. (Rank 1/2, depending on heal)[/spoiler]   
	
	Rescuer is a good stress healer! He does [b]not heal health as much as Vestal[/b], but is a viable full healer with unique healing properties + skills. The party may not be &quot;topped off&quot; at perfectly 100% HP, but using procedures, trinkets, quirks + cleverness you can succeed! 
	
	[h1]Procedures[/h1]
	Some Rescuer skills have enhanced effects when following procedures. Optional procedure info:
	[spoiler]*Use Motivational Hypnosis a turn before Healing or Stress Healing for bonus.
	*Use First Aid before Nitrous Oxide to help resist stun.
	*Trigger Riposte. Riposte can Bleed. Use Follow the Track on a Bleeding target for extra raw damage.
	*Have someone mark a target. Use the Stay Away on Marked for chance to Stun. Use Stay Away on Stunned for a critical chance hit!
	*Use Follow the Track on Marked target for a chance to Bleed. Use Follow the Track on a Bleeding target for extra raw damage![/spoiler]

	[h1]Spider Nests Compatible[/h1]
	[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1717651804][img]https://i.imgur.com/gALL813.jpg[/img][/url]
	[b]Spider Hunter Skill:[/b] The Rescuer&apos;s hounds have a strong instinct to crush giant spiders. Riposte deals Double Damage to base game spiders and optional [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1717651804][b]Spider Nests (Monster Mod)[/b][/url] spiders. Helpful on extra long Spider dungeons! Load: Spider Nests ABOVE Rescuer.
	
	[h1]Pets Compatible[/h1]
	[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1779509342][img]https://i.imgur.com/Cb2vcbh.jpg[/img][/url]
	Help find &quot;Epione&quot;, the Rescuer&apos;s&apos;s Pet Pheasant who helps the hounds hone their hunting skills in the [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1779509342][b]Pets (Trinkets + Monster Mod)[/b][/url] Load: Pets ABOVE Rescuer.
	
		[h1]Herbs of the Wild Compatible[/h1]
[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1390782905&amp;searchtext=herbs+of+the+wild][img]https://i.imgur.com/Lhn3Whb.jpg[/img][/url]
The Rescuer&apos;s experience in the outdoors and his Herbalist training, allow him to discover natural supplies with Carnifex&apos;s optional [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1390782905&amp;searchtext=herbs+of+the+wild][b]Herbs of the Wild Resource Mod[/b][/url]. Load: HotW ABOVE Rescuer
	
	[h1]Languages/Translations[/h1]
	*English
	*ChineseS by 梦灵 + nbb
	*Spanish Coming Soon!
	Other languages show English
	Contact to help w/Translation!
	
	[h1]Credits[/h1]
Selafio: Developer, Art (Hero, Trinkets, Effects, Animations)
Dem: Developer, Coding, Sounds
Smarmy Mormon Jesus: Support
Thanks to Pahv, Adon, O&apos;Nightmare, Sasiji, Mafe for art &amp; code support! Thanks MLD Discord.

[h1]Be a Patron[/h1] 
Support quality mods, including finishing Pet Cemetery, [url=https://www.patreon.com/user?u=26064807&amp;fan_landing=true] consider a tip to the Rescuer artist Selafio, from Chile.[/url] 

[h1]Pet Cemetery (Dungeon Mod): 2020[/h1]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/RPH469p.jpg[/img]

[h1]Party Names[/h1]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/DN01v6V.jpg[/img]

[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1860840141][img]https://i.imgur.com/N3ulOBQl.jpg[/img][/url]
	
 </ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>2053917390</PublishedFileId>
</project>

