<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>D:/Exavault/My Modding Projects/Darkest Dungeon Modding/Wraith Class Mod/data/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>Exaelus&apos; Wraith Class Mod</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>public</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>0</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>0</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>0</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>Character Mod</Tags>
		<Tags>Class Mod</Tags>
		<Tags>New Class</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>[h1]The Wraith Class Mod[/h1]
Supports Color of Madness: Yes
Supports Crimson Court: Yes
Mod Version: 1.3d
Language: English, S-Chinese, Korean


[h1]Latest News[/h1]

Wraith has been released!


[h1]Class Introduction[/h1]
Hello DD crawlers, it&apos;s been a while. When Color Of Madness DLC came out I had an idea for a character heavily inspired by World of Warcraft rogues, Malthael from Diablo and Morphling from Dota you will see why as I get into the class itself. This is my very last class I&apos;m releasing for DD, there is nothing else different or interesting to me at least that I can pull out of the game so this is it. 
I spent 3 weeks working on this guy, have fun!

This character is a high damage low survivability assassin that is capable of sapping and reaping souls. Every time he uses one of his abilites he is able to increase one of his stats for a long duration so technically, the longer the dungeon, the stronger he gets which is ideal for the endless dungeon. He is able to go stealth from which he receives a damage bonus similarly to grave robber except he also receives armor penetration and gives his &quot;Devious Ambush&quot; the chance to stun. 

Like most standard classes you get to pick 4 out of his 7 abilities, however there is a lot of depth and synergy to his abilities. His basic attack that can be used from all positions is called &quot;Phantom Strike&quot; which gives you different buffs depending on which position you stand in. He can be used in many different ways, as a stealth assassin from position 3 and 4  where most of his abilities increase the blight amount he applies to targets when he uses &quot;Soul Harvest&quot; or as a frontline bandit in positions 1 and 2 where most of his abilities increase bleed amount that can be applied with &quot;Reaping Evisceration&quot;. His stealth ability &quot;Grim Shade&quot; knocks him all the way to position 4 and his &quot;Devious Ambush&quot; moves him 2 positions forward, so as you can see you can also mix these strategies and create an early shadow assassin that can go frontline or a frontliner that can fall back when required. Evisceration also increases damage taken and Harvest depletes all initiative from all enemies.

There are 2 more things i need to mention. His camping abilities Writhe Soul: Pemanence and Fatality. This is where the morphling inspiration comes in. Since he is capable of sapping souls increasing his stats with every strike he can then in camp twist his own soul which makes him lose defensive stats and gain offensive ones and vice versa.

Wraith can&apos;t travel with highwayman and can only reduce his stress in the tavern, he doesn&apos;t like the church, he also provides 2 bandages on every mission. He has also been placed into the house of the yellow hand district.

Don&apos;t expect this class to be balanced on release so I&apos;m going to need some time and feedback to balance him properly so feel free to add me, I prefer it this way, I promise I don&apos;t bite! Also screenshots are only there for visual effect display nothing more. ^^


[h1]Souls[/h1]
As a little bonus on top I&apos;ve decided to create new items that have a chance to drop after every battle and these items are called souls. There are 3 types of souls that can be found. Tormented Soul, Serene Soul and Ambiguous Soul. By using these souls you reap them receive a small amount of stress and receive an increase to different resistances and special stats. Each use causes less stress and makes the buff stronger.

[img]https://i.imgur.com/KzJXVVX.png[/img]

From left to right:
[b]Tormented Soul: [/b]Bleed, Blight resist and Armor Piercing buff.
[b]Serene Soul: [/b]Stun, Stress resist and Damage Reflection buff.
[b]Ambiguous Soul: [/b]Debuff, Disease resist and Damage Received buff. 


[h1]Combat Skills[/h1]
[b] Phantom Strike: [/b] A. Position: ALL / Targets 1,2 / Effect: Dmg, pos. buff, bleed+dmg rcv buff.
[b] Reaping Evisceration: [/b] A. Position: 1,2 / Targets 1,2 / Effect: Dmg, bleed, debuff, dmg buff.
[b] Sinister Flurry: [/b] A. Position: 1,2 / Targets 1+2+3 / Effect: Dmg, +dmg, rpst, dmg reflect buff.
[b] Devious Ambush:[/b] A. Position: 3,4 / Targets ALL / Effect: Dmg, can stun  if slth, crit buff.
[b] Soul Harvest:[/b]A. Position: 3,4 / Targets: 3,4 / Effect: Dmg, blight, -initiative, max hp buff.
[b] Scattering Dread:[/b]A. Position: 3,4 / Targets: 2+3 / Effect: Dmg, buff, debuff, shuffle, acc buff.
[b] Grim Shade:[/b] A. Position: ALL / Targets: Self / Effect: Stealth, +dmg/crit buff, stun c., ar.pen.


[h1]Camping Skills[/h1]
[b] Reaper&apos;s Stratagem: [/b]Inc. blight duration, stun c., dread dmg, takes ambush dmg for 4 bttls.
[b] Writhe Soul Fatality: [/b]Reduces defensive stats and boosts offensive stats for 4 batles.
[b] Writhe Soul Permanence: [/b]Reduces offensive stats and boosts defensive stats for 4 battles.
[b] Cheat Death:[/b] Gives deathblow resistance and takes stress and damage taken for 4 battles.



If you find any bugs/glitches or spelling errors please let me know in the comment section below and i will try to address them. I hope you enjoy playing this class as much as i had fun making it.

Here are my other classes if you want to try them out:

[url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=913178378][img]https://i.imgur.com/B8Duftl.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=924245318][img]https://i.imgur.com/a1YoES1.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=934967620][img]https://i.imgur.com/EvnjeGp.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=947715735][img]https://i.imgur.com/wtvL4QS.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=970030269][img]https://i.imgur.com/QX5m0ux.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1100450515][img]https://i.imgur.com/bBYf01L.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1138503289][img]https://i.imgur.com/Wccrwn4.png[/img][/url]



[h1]Support[/h1]
Due to health issues my modding has been put on hold, but If you like what you see and you want me to do more in the future, you can support my mods by donating here:

[url=https://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_s-xclick&amp;hosted_button_id=PC3886U2YM8C6][img]https://i.imgur.com/6qUg1Xz.gif[/img][/url]


Thank you for all the positive feedback and your support, it does motivate me quite a bit!

Special thanks to &quot;Foxical&quot;(S-Chinese) and &quot;halfmoon515&quot;(Korean) for translating my mod.

Special thanks to RedHook for making this great game and giving players the ability to mod it!

This mod is not an official Red Hook Studios product or product modification, and Red Hook Studios Inc. is not responsible in any way for changes or damages that may result from using the mod. Furthermore, “Darkest Dungeon” and the Darkest Dungeon logo are trademarks of Red Hook Studios Inc. All content in the game is Copyright Red Hook Studios Inc. All rights reserved.
</ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>1441036778</PublishedFileId>
</project>

