<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>C:/Users/Sean/Desktop/Darkest Dungeon Mods/Sir Alonne/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>Samurai</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>public</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>1</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>8</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>0</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>New Class</Tags>
		<Tags>Dark Souls</Tags>
		<Tags>Samurai</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>[i]Samurai are warriors bound by honor and immediacy. They serve worthy lords, bringing their philosophy of Bushido, and its warfare, to their armies.[/i]

[h1]Theme[/h1]

This character is based on Sir Alonne of Dark Souls 2. He is a warrior who pits his noble soul against the bloodlusting curse of his bewitched blade. He shuffles around ranks (though some moves promote staying purely in the front ranks), and he has a unique bleed effect on most of his abilities. His moves also benefit from bleeding enemies, and whether he is bleeding. 

Passive Effect: Each strike builds bleed %, similar to the katana weapon class of the Dark Souls series. When it reaches full effect, it can bleed an opponent for massive damage on a single turn.

Passive Effect: The cursed blade fights the Samurai&apos;s soul with each swing. +6 stress per swing. If he surrenders to the blade&apos;s bloodlust via &quot;Bewitched Bloodlust,&quot; he can postpone self-destruction. Likewise with &quot;Zen,&quot; he can purify himself.

Like the Bewitched Alonne Sword moveset in Dark Souls 2, one may attempt seppuku to gain massive benefits. Be warned: the penalty is high.

[h1]Abilities &amp; Inspiration[/h1]

Abilities are inspired by the Sir Alonne boss fight, his weapon&apos;s moveset for the player, and his lore. A well trodden trope in Japanese storytelling (if not all human story-telling) is the sword as a conduit of bloodlust &amp; spiritual conflict, so that has massively inspired my class design as well.

1) Elegant Strike: The Samurai gracefully strikes, gaining a minor dodge bonus if he&apos;s bleeding, or bled the enemy. Carries the passive bleed effect mentioned above.

2) Backslash: The Samurai strikes while jumping backward 2 spaces, giving the enemy a normal bleed effect for 3 turns.

3) Gliding Stab: The Samurai engages a long-range thrust attack with his nagamaki, doing enhanced damage upon bleeding enemies. Moves forward 2. Carries the passive bleed effect.

4) Bewitched Bloodthirst: The Samurai impales himself with his bewitched blade, gaining massive damage and armor penetration for the remainder of the fight, but suffering damage, bleeding, and an incurable wound which reduces healing received for the remainder of the fight.

5) Piercing Assault: The Samurai commences a jumping attack which pierces any guard sheltering a target, striking directly and gaining massive damage at guarded targets. Moves forward 1. Carries the passive bleed effect.

6) Zen: The Samurai baits his opponent, gaining zen-like focus. His dodge increases, his accuracy increases, he moves back one, and he will riposte. Enjoy the sfx! Loses some dodge if he&apos;s currently bleeding. Good stress heal.

7) Lunge: The Samurai leaps at his enemy with a kick, knocking them back one space. They are dizzy, losing speed and dodge. This ability exposes the enemy to take more damage.

[h1] Trinkets [/h1]

1)Chloranthy Ring: Gains passive regeneration.
2)Dexterity Ring: Gains accuracy and dodge in exchange for stress damage taken.
3)Strength Ring: Gains damage in exchange for stress damage taken.
4)Steel Ring: Gains protection in exchange for stress damage taken.

5) Vanquisher&apos;s Seal: Gain an effect to move enemies with each strike, but lose damage.
6) Stone Ring: Gain an effect to stun enemies with each strike, but lose damage.
Set Bonus: Gain protection.

7) Samurai Soul: Gain virtue chance and accuracy.
8) Bewitched Blade: Gain damage on bleeding enemies, damage if you are bleeding, and bleed chance on enemies. Lose virtue chance.
Set Bonus: If virtued, gain minor protection, health, and speed. If afflicted, significantly lose health, but gain 100% chance to bleed the enemy.

[h1] Future Plans [/h1]

Link?


[h1] Known Issues [/h1]

None known at the moment.

[h1] Huge Thanks [/h1]

Big, big thank you Eira, Queen of Snow for doing almost all the art.

HUGE thank you to AceroSteel for finishing some errors &amp; providing recolors of the art. 


[h1] Final Thoughts [/h1]

I read the Hagakure for this mod. Since Sir Alonne had little dialogue, I looked to it for inspiration for Samurai&apos;s dialogue. It was incredibly enlightening, and I&apos;d recommend it to anyone.

This mod was stuck in development hell for 3/4ths of a year. I consider it unfinished. I&apos;ll finish it when the mood strikes me, but I think the General Feedback discussion is the best place to correct it.

I can&apos;t promise I&apos;ll continue modding in general. I&apos;m sure AceroSteel&apos;s art can persuade me in the future, especially that Link of his, but I&apos;m finished for now. </ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>1558105232</PublishedFileId>
</project>

