<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>F:/steam/steamapps/common/DarkestDungeon/mods/daughtersOfTheFours_pack/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>Daughters of the Fours Pack</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>public</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>1</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>14</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>0</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>Character Mod</Tags>
		<Tags>Class Mod</Tags>
		<Tags>New Class</Tags>
		<Tags>Pack</Tags>
		<Tags>Waifest Dungeon</Tags>
		<Tags>First daughter</Tags>
		<Tags>Second daughter</Tags>
		<Tags>Third daughter</Tags>
		<Tags>Fourth daughter</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>[h1]Daughters of the Fours[/h1]

Localization files: English(?)

Daughters of the Fours is a pack of 4 unique and complex classes designed with the purpose of giving a refreshing feel with their playstyle. Their learning curve and leveling is hard capped so be careful while using them.

That said, all daughters have been passed through several buffs until this point, but overall they&apos;re weak classes by their own but powerful when they coordinates with others (at max. upgraded). This means this classes are for those who already has the Darkest Dungeon core-gameplay known and wants experience other type of challenge.


The pack contains:
- [u]Daughter of the First[/u] - Guarder and Nuker
- [u]Daughter of the Second[/u] - Selfish stress healer and sub-dps
- [u]Daughter of the Third[/u] - Survivalist and utility (Antiquarian v.2)
- [u]Daughter of the Fourth[/u] - Glass canon Healer and crowd controller as a debuffer

The pack doesn&apos;t contains:
- [u]The Bloodline mechanic[/u]:
The Bloodline mechanic is an augmentations for max. upgraded First, Second and Fourth daughter which unlocks special behaviour for each daughter transformating them in more specific role once reached their max. Bloodline level.
This mechanic is currently in testing, but if you wanna try it out anyways you can check it in the Nexus:
[url=https://www.nexusmods.com/darkestdungeon/mods/602] The Bloodline mechanic[/url] 
- [u]Finished barks, lore and maybe some text[/u]
- [u]Trinkets[/u]: They don&apos;t require dedicated trinkets in my opinion, so they will not receive their trinkets most likely.

For more detailed information you can check their individual files in Nexus:
[url=https://www.nexusmods.com/darkestdungeon/mods/581] Daughter of the First[/url] 
[url=https://www.nexusmods.com/darkestdungeon/mods/575] Daughter of the Second[/url] 
[url=https://www.nexusmods.com/darkestdungeon/mods/576] Daughter of the Third[/url] 
[url=https://www.nexusmods.com/darkestdungeon/mods/577] Daughter of the Fourth[/url] 

[h1]Brief overview: Daughter of the First[/h1] 

Designed for those who likes playing defensively and the strategy in combat. Her playstyle requires coordination within her actions and her companions in order of compenetrate accordly with her conditional damage.
She requires receiven damage in order to deal extra damage in her next actions, while after dealing that damage she lose the capacity of finishing off that concrete target, which means she needs others to support her before or after acting.
She offers additionally, while she can&apos;t attack or when needed, protection and actions at high cost, meaning each action made by her requires meditation and taking &quot;safe&quot; risk as well.

Loves: healers, blighters and companions who deals extra damage againts marked.

Her Affliction increase a lot of stats but will make her act for her only own. Use her Affliction with caution.

[b]Skill Celling[/b]: Medium-hard



[h1]Brief overview: Daughter of the Second[/h1]

The most dynamic of them four who loves acting each turn to actually make her useful. Designed for those who likes dealing damage and supporting the team at same time with an unstop phasin. Her constant crits will provide a consistent source of stress healing, but she will prefer her own sanity instead of others.

She can provide additional damage by her own under centains circunstances and while she can connect her Crits. She also can provide global guard and self riposte when needed.

Her Kit is almost all ofensive skills with support capacities, but since she lack raw power its potential remains hidden somehow.

Loves: Stunners, others stress healers and dancing classes (who can relocate her again to her rank 2 position)

Her Affliction changes her role to monstrous damage dealer at cost of the group sanity. Use her Affliction with caution.

[b]Skill Celling[/b]: Medium-easy




[h1]Brief overview: Daughter of the Third[/h1]

The equivalent of the Antiquarian in usefulness but with end-game mindset instead. She&apos;s designed for those who likes resource management, gaining the best outcome and out-combat tools.

Insanely weak in early level but with the strongest Camping skills in game. She can provide a huge advantage to her allies with only camping (and since she provides an additional log, this means more camping opportunities), so losing her while going in dungeon doesn&apos;t means too much for your roaster.
She can stack additional provisions, heirmloos and can loot extra Crest for each curio looted. This means she can increase your upgrading speed by a great amount.

But unlikely the Antiquarian (and the others daughters) she can reach max. skill levels without upgrading the Guild and when she reachs her max. upgrade she becomes God-tier support class unlike her trash-tier low level phase. But keep in mind that her cost are &quot;specials&quot;.

Beware of her 0~4 skills (which can be reached in the begining without any upgrading requeriment) which instead improving, changes its effect to another different.

Loves: curios, resource, camping and not dying

Her Virtue (100% chance) is an Affliction in disguise, which will decrease her DD resistance to 0 (but will never suffer the consecuences of being stressed)

[b]Skill Celling[/b] Easiest 


[h1]Brief overview: Daughter of the Fourth[/h1]

The glass cannon healer within daughters. Designed for those who loves playing with the danger and feeling the risk at in every battle if that provides huge numbers at their favor.

Fourth is a meh healer in her fresh state but once she reach Death&apos;s Door she becomes a powerful and versatile support for the team. This means she doesn&apos;t gain DD debuffs but powerful buff instead, but once outside of DD she will becomes even weaker healer than before.
She have her special &quot;round cost mechanic&quot; which means she can gain additional actions per round, but each skill comes with &quot;round cost&quot; when her actions are bigger than 1. To excel this mechanic she requires normally being in DD so she can maximaze her utility.

She can alterate the flow of the enemies actions and their utility capacities, but some of her skills could backfire if she fails conecting the hit.
Fourth is, ironically like Second, a selfish support who can help allies but sometimes use them in order of losing her debuff to regain her comfort zone.

Loves: Being in DD, stress healers, self sustain dps and guarders.

Her Affliction changes her role from healer to stress healer instead. She could pass some turns if she wants to.

[b]Skill Celling[/b] Hard




[h1]End note[/h1]
They four are in the spot I wanted for them, but I can still receive feedback for better implementations (specially for the Bloodline). Sadly I&apos;m not an artist so some asthetical changes can&apos;t be done as requested (I tried my best in replicate the DD style without the desired result, so my apologies).

If you&apos;re insterested in my next (or others) mods, you can check the Darkest Dungeon mods in nexus where I usually use as a testing plataform before uploading thing in Steam.</ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>1342714768</PublishedFileId>
</project>

