<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>D:/Exavault/My Modding Projects/Darkest Dungeon Modding/Harbinger Class Mod/data/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>Exaelus&apos; Harbinger Class Mod</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>public</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>0</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>0</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>0</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>Character Mod</Tags>
		<Tags>Class Mod</Tags>
		<Tags>New Class</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>[h1]The Harbinger Class Mod[/h1]
Supports Color of Madness: Yes
Supports Crimson Court: Yes
Mod Version: 1.7c
Language: English, Polish, French, Russian, Korean


[h1]Latest News[/h1]

Mod now supports Color of Madness DLC!

Harbinger now receives a buff when he crits. (-33% Stress)

2 new Crimson Court trinkets. (Screenshot added!)
1 new Color of Madness trinket. (Screenshot added!)

Harbinger has been released!


[h1]Class Introduction[/h1]
Is it really that time again? This would be my 7th class here on the workshop that i&apos;ve been working on for over a month and a half because of my vacation. Screenshots are there only for visual effect display, nothing more. This mod is pretty much inspired by the three kings. The Lich King from Warcraft, Witch King from Lord of the Rings and Night King from Game of Thrones. Once again this class plays differently from the rest. I think a lot of people will enjoy this class a lot. I&apos;ve worked hard on visual and audio effects to make him super satisfying to play, he is my favorite so far. I wanted to challenge myself so i wanted to make a class that uses white color for their theme which is the opposite of darkest dungeon and make it work.

This class has 3 paths or stances that are swapped in and out of constantly. The three paths are Disparity, Decay and Frost. Every path has 2 different abilities and a different focus, there is a special ability called &quot;Mercurial Winter&quot; that is in every path or stance and it does different things based on which path it&apos;s used in. I also have to mention his abilities consume torch.


Path of Disparity is a hybrid type stance that focuses on moving the enemy target and reducing their speed, Rime Strike takes you to Path of Decay, Glacial Charge takes you to Path of Frost. Mercurial Winter heals the Harbinger&apos;s stress and also gives him a a big damage reduction buff for a few rounds in this path.

Path of Decay is the debuff and damage type of path that focuses on increasing damage taken by the enemies and decreasing your own by using Overpower. Overpower gives you a riposte for two rounds that with every attack decreases your damage taken and increases the enemy damage taken it also marks the enemy and gives Shatter the capability to stun. You can also bleed and blight enemies in this stance by using Grimbane which also amplifies the damage done by Tempest which is an ability in Path of Frost. Mercurial Winter heals the Harbinger&apos;s health by a small amount and also gives him a a big damage buff in this path. Any ability used in this path takes you back to the Path of Disparity.

Path of Frost is a nuke and stun type of path where you can stun all enemies with Tempest which also increases bleed and blight skill chance of Grimbane, you can also nuke the enemies from this stance with Shatter which also increases the critical strike chance of Overpower which is in the Path of Decay and also does a lot of damage to marked targets. Mercurial Winter heals the Harbinger&apos;s health over time and applies a healing received buff in this path. Any ability used in this path takes you back to the Path of Disparity.


You can get the Harbinger through a one time event that happens quite quickly but after that be careful because you will only find him in in the stagecoach every once and a while. If a harbinger dies his allies get touched by his soul which gives them a permanent positive quirk that is quite powerful. He also provides torches on every mission, he is only able to meditate and pray for stress relief and he cannot travel with: Revenant, Scourge, Fury and Crusader.

His trinkets and camping skills are also quite unique because they all last until the end of quest and they amplify specific paths or stances of the Harbinger.

[h1]Combat Skills[/h1]

Path of Disparity: 
[b] Rime Strike:[/b] A. Position: 1,2 / Targets: 1,2 / Effect: Decay, +DMG, -SPD, +SHUFFLE
[b] Glacial Charge: [/b] A. position: ALL / Targets 1,2,3 / Effect: Frost, +DMG, +MOVE, -SPD, +PUSH
Both abilities in this mode reduce torch.

Path of Decay:
[b] Grimbane:[/b] A. Position: 1,2 / Targets: 1,2,3 / Effect: Dsp., +DMG, +BLEED + BLIGHT, +BUFF
[b] Overpower:[/b] A. Position: 1,2 / Targets 1+2 / Effect: Dsp. , +DMG, +MARK, +RIPOSTE, +DBF/BUFF
[b] Riposte:[/b] Every hit increases damage taken by enemies and decreases damage taken by you.
Overpower increases chance to stun with Shatter.
Grimbane amplifies damage done by Tempest.

Path of Frost:
[b] Shatter:[/b] A. Position: ALL / Targets: 1,2,3,4 / Effect: Dsp, +DMG, +MARKDMG, +BUFF, +STUN
[b] Tempest:[/b] A. Position: ALL / Targets 1+2+3+4 / Effect: Disparity, +DMG, +STUN, +BUFF
Tempest increases bleed and blight skill chance of Grimbane and reduces torch by quite a bit.
Shatter increases accuracy of Overpower. 

All Paths:
[b] Mercurial Winter:[/b] A. Position: ALL / Targets: SELF / Effect: Different effect in every path.
[b]Disparity:[/b] Adds a shield block and reduces damage taken.
[b]Decay:[/b] Heals stress and increases damage done.
[b]Frost:[/b] Increases healing received and heals over time.
Mercurial Winter also reduces torch.


[h1]Camping Skills[/h1]
[b] Hiemal Ward: [/b] Reduces damage taken by group.
[b] Rune of Disparity:[/b] Gives you Stress resist and amplifies Rime Strike and Glacial Charge.
[b] Rune of Decay: [/b]Increases you ACC and amplifies Grimbane and Overpower skill chances.
[b] Rune of Frost:[/b] Increases you HP heal received and amplifies Shatter and Tempest.

If you find any bugs/glitches or spelling errors please let me know in the comment section below and i will try to address them. I hope you enjoy playing this class as much as i had fun making it.

Here are my other classes if you want to try them out:

[url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=913178378][img]https://i.imgur.com/B8Duftl.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=924245318][img]https://i.imgur.com/a1YoES1.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=934967620][img]https://i.imgur.com/EvnjeGp.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=947715735][img]https://i.imgur.com/wtvL4QS.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=970030269][img]https://i.imgur.com/QX5m0ux.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1100450515][img]https://i.imgur.com/bBYf01L.png[/img][/url][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1441036778][img]https://i.imgur.com/Ratr9w8.png[/img][/url]


[h1]Support[/h1]
Due to health issues my modding has been put on hold, but If you like what you see and you want me to do more in the future, you can support my mods by donating here:

[url=https://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_s-xclick&amp;hosted_button_id=PC3886U2YM8C6][img]https://i.imgur.com/6qUg1Xz.gif[/img][/url]


Thank you for all the positive feedback and your support, it does motivate me quite a bit!

Special thanks to &quot;jmakiela&quot;(Polish), &quot;Uncle Seifer&quot;(Russian), &quot;halfmoon515&quot;(Korean)
and my good friend &quot;Chocostar&quot;(French) for translating my mod.

Special thanks to RedHook for making this great game and giving players the ability to mod it!

This mod is not an official Red Hook Studios product or product modification, and Red Hook Studios Inc. is not responsible in any way for changes or damages that may result from using the mod. Furthermore, “Darkest Dungeon” and the Darkest Dungeon logo are trademarks of Red Hook Studios Inc. All content in the game is Copyright Red Hook Studios Inc. All rights reserved.
</ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>1138503289</PublishedFileId>
</project>

