<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>D:/Exavault/My Modding Projects/Darkest Dungeon Modding/Prodigy Class Mod/data/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>Exaelus&apos; Prodigy Class Mod</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>public</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>0</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>0</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>0</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>Character Mod</Tags>
		<Tags>Class Mod</Tags>
		<Tags>New Class</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>[h1]The Prodigy Class Mod[/h1]
Supports Color of Madness: Yes
Supports Crimson Court: Yes
Mod Version: 2.9e
Language: English, French, Russian, Spanish, Polish, Korean


[h1]Latest News[/h1]

Mod now supports Color of Madness DLC!

Prodigy now receives a buff when he crits. (+10 Dodge)

Prodigy is now a part of the district and also provides a holy water on every mission.
Created 1 set of trinkets out of existing trinkets. (Screenshot updated!)


[h1]Class Introduction[/h1]
Here we go again, this is my second class that took me 3 weeks to create, i wouldn&apos;t make this class if i did not have a good idea behind it. I wanted to challenge myself because for me it&apos;s not that hard to create good looking metallic surfaces but i struggle with muscles and cloth quite a bit. So i said to myself, what can i possibly make that would challenge me. That&apos;s how i came up with the Prodigy.

The Prodigy is a pure DPS class that was heavily inspired by Jade Empire. This class plays differently from the rest. The idea behind the class is that he has 2 stances, offensive (fist) and defensive (palm). 

Offensive stance abilities move you to the very front of the group and some of them can stun.
Defensive stance abilities always move you one space backwards and move the enemies around.

So the idea is, keep using defensive abilities until you reach the position you want to be in and move enemies to the desired position you want them to be in. Then swap the stance and execute the offensive ability of your choosing. Keep in mind every offensive ability can be cast from a different position.

He is a shuffler, all he does is move around constantly looking for the perfect spot to attack from. You chose what you want to do when and which ability you want to execute.

This character was hard to balance but i believe he is in a good spot right now. He is religious so he cannot travel with the Revenant or Abomination. He has access to all abilities and provides free Holy Water on every mission.



[h1]Combat Skills[/h1]
[b] Spirit Shift: [/b] Attack position: 1,2,3,4 / Swaps stance, each stance buffs you for 1 round.

[b]Defensive Stance:[/b] (Does more damage to men, also the starting stance)
[b] Paralysing Palm: [/b] Attack position: 1,2,3 / Targets 1,2,3 / Effect: DMG + DBF + PUSH 1
[b] Hallowed Kick: [/b] Attack position: 1,2,3 / Targets 1+2 / Effect: DMG + PUSH 2
[b] Righteous Fist:[/b] Attack position: 1,2,3 / Targets 1 / Effect: DMG + MARK + PUSH 3

[b]Offensive Stance[/b] (Does more damage to unholy)
[b] Heavenly Charge:[/b] A. Position: 2,3,4 / Targets: 1+2+3 / Effect: DMG+ DBF
[b] Sacred Strike:[/b] A. Position:  3,4 / Targets: 1+2 / Effect: DMG + STUN
[b] Divine Haymaker:[/b] A. Position: 4 / Targets: 1,2 / Effect: DMG+STUN+Mark DMG


[h1]Camping Skills[/h1]
[b] Fortune Cookie: [/b] Random Buffs in the pool, you get random ones, all of them or none of them.
[b] Gem Stash: [/b] Gives you one random gem to make you feel better.
[b] Serenity [/b] Removes a huge amount of stress from the party and himself but he is exhausted.
[b] Solemn Training:[/b] Buffs party with dodge and accuracy, increases monster surprise chance.

He is an interesting class, i also made sure the sound effects for kicks and punches feel satisfying to use. He is fun but needs some time to get used to, works really well with other shuffling classes like Grave Robber, Hellion and Jester.

If you find any bugs/glitches or spelling errors please let me know in the comment section below, this time i will need more feedback so i can balance him properly, i will do a lot of testing on my own. Next on the list is making color variations for both revenant and prodigy as well. Need a small break and some time to pass before i tackle a new class, if i come up with an interesting concept. 

This class mod is also complete like the revenant, i still have some polishing left to do, but it does have everything.

Here are my other classes if you want to try them out:

[url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=913178378][img]https://i.imgur.com/B8Duftl.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=934967620][img] https://i.imgur.com/EvnjeGp.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=947715735][img]https://i.imgur.com/wtvL4QS.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=970030269][img]https://i.imgur.com/QX5m0ux.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1100450515][img]https://i.imgur.com/bBYf01L.png[/img][/url][url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1138503289][img]https://i.imgur.com/Wccrwn4.png[/img][/url][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1441036778][img]https://i.imgur.com/Ratr9w8.png[/img][/url]


[h1]Support[/h1]
Due to health issues my modding has been put on hold, but If you like what you see and you want me to do more in the future, you can support my mods by donating here:

[url=https://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_s-xclick&amp;hosted_button_id=PC3886U2YM8C6][img]https://i.imgur.com/6qUg1Xz.gif[/img][/url]


Thank you for all the positive feedback and your support, it does motivate me quite a bit!

Special thanks to &quot;Dr McMescouilles&quot;(French), &quot;_AZOT_&quot;(Russian), &quot;SnakePriest&quot;(Spanish), &quot;jmakiela&quot;(Polish) 
and &quot;halfmoon515&quot;(Korean) for translating my mod.

Special thanks to RedHook for making this great game and giving players the ability to mod it!

This mod is not an official Red Hook Studios product or product modification, and Red Hook Studios Inc. is not responsible in any way for changes or damages that may result from using the mod. Furthermore, “Darkest Dungeon” and the Darkest Dungeon logo are trademarks of Red Hook Studios Inc. All content in the game is Copyright Red Hook Studios Inc. All rights reserved.
</ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>924245318</PublishedFileId>
</project>

