<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort/>
	<ModDataPath>C:/Users/dunca/Desktop/Demon_Trinkets_Upload/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>Demon Trinkets</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>private</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>direct_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>1</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>1</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>24839</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>Trinkets</Tags>
		<Tags>DLC</Tags>
		<Tags>Quirks</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>
    [img]https://i.imgur.com/XO00w25.jpg[/img]

	[b]v1.1[/b]
	
    [b]English only at this time.[/b]

    [b]THIS MOD INCREASES THE SHARD NOMAD WAGON COUNT. If you are having issues with multiple mods, try putting this at the top of your mod list in game (highest priority)[/b]

    [h1]Diablo-Fan Crossover Trinkets![/h1]
    Check out these 26 new powerful diablo-inspired trinkets. Can you solve the mysterious set pieces? These trinkets currently drop in all dungeons, with the socketed dropping in lvl 5, gems in lvl 3, 2-pc sets in the Crimson Court, and a special Colour of Madness trinket set. These were created without hero class limitations.

    [h1]Legendary Socketed Trinket Info[/h1]
    These trinkets will drop from champion level dungeons. They are meant to be uniquely powerful and resemble similar effects from inspired diablo items.
    
    [h1]Epic Gem Trinket Info[/h1]
    These trinkets will drop from lvl 3 dungeons and up. Theyare powerful but are very fragile, leaving your heros susceptible. Once you determine which socketable trinket they belong to, you will unlock the full potential.

    [h1]Green Set CC Trinket Info[/h1]
    These trinkets will drop from Crimson Court. They are meant to be class agnostic. Two of the sets require specific positive or negative quirks to unlock full potential. The quirks will not get overritten unless you do so in town.

    [h1]CoM Set Trinket Info[/h1]
    These trinkets will drive you mad. At least we are one step closer to a mobile platform.

    [h1]Future plans[/h1] 
    Unclear, this is my first mod. I am willing to create more crossover or new mods. If you like what I&apos;ve done here, leave positive feedback and rating on the workshop. This is the best way to support my ambitions to write future mods.

    [h1]Bugs/Feedback[/h1]
    Please lave bug reports and constructive feedback in the comment section, I will try to respond with fix and timeframe. You can contact me on the Moonlit Dungeon discord.

    Thanks to the MLD discord modders for support and answering noob questions!

    Join MLD Discord here: [url=https://discord.gg/VkXB87M][/url]

    [h1]Disclaimer[/h1]
    Please contact me before uploading anything this mod provides to any other website. This mod is a fan-created crossover from diablo-inspired items. I do not represent Red Hook Studios nor Blizzard Entertainment. Use this mod at your own risk, I&apos;m not responsible for any lost saves due to workshop issues.

    </ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>1830140721</PublishedFileId>
</project>

